There are influences in the unseen that
are dictating a lot of the way your life
goes. And these things are known as
pendulums or thought forms.
They exist in a reality, like I said,
that is unseen in a frequency that is
not within the same frequency as the
physical. And so, not a lot of people
are aware of them because a lot of
people think the only thing real and
what's influencing their life is the
physical. But thought forms and
pendulums are playing such a huge role
in everyone's life that it becomes of
great benefit to learn not only what
they are but how to get out of the
influence of pendulums or to select very
particular pendulums that actually
benefit you and serve you. And so today,
we're going to go over what pendulums
are, but more importantly, how to go
about selecting a pendulum that will
benefit you or to tune out completely
because it will make all of the
difference when it comes to achieving
what it is you want to achieve or just
living the kind of life you would like
to create for yourself. Now, the first
thing to recognize is that pendulums are
thought forms. And not all thought forms
are necessarily pendulums, but pendulums
uh pendulums are kind of like um group
levels of thought. many people or many
different thoughts uh accumulated create
what's known as a pendulum. Right? A
thought form can be sometimes singular.
We're not going to get too nuanced with
this kind of thing. Uh but a pendulum
you can think of like a mass thought
form because a lot of thought power has
gone to a particular idea or something
else. And we'll get into exactly what
that is in just a moment. But one thing
I want to bring your attention to first
is the idea that thoughts are things.
And I know you've heard this quote
before. most likely that thoughts are
things and it's a very true uh saying. A
lot of us again believe because we can't
see thoughts that we can't touch them,
we can't taste them, we can't engage our
five physical senses that they are not
real and don't have much influence in
our life. But it's the exact opposite.
In fact, most of how our life goes is
formed by how we are thinking and what
thoughts we entertain. Remember the
quote, you get what you think about most
of the time. And thought forms are going
to play a huge role in what you're
actually going to think about. So, let's
move on to what this is. Understanding
that thoughts come in different
frequencies.
And the frequency you're at is a lot of
times going to determine which pendulum
or thought forms you're going to have
access to or you're influenced by.
Right? Thoughts activate different
levels of frequency. If you think
certain thoughts or entertain certain
thoughts, it will put you on one
frequency and then other thoughts will
put you on different frequencies. Each
of these frequencies come with
corresponding effects or benefits or the
opposite of benefits depending on what
frequency you are on. So just as a
simple example, if you think more
negatively or allow yourself to be
swayed by what we could call a negative
pendulum, you will notice that you are
on a frequency that presents you with
more thoughts that are negative events
and circumstances that also correspond
with those thoughts. So understand not
all thoughts are the same. They
correspond at different levels of
frequencies and based on the frequency
or the resonance will determine what
you're receiving. Again, there are some
pendulums we could say are at a higher
frequency and there are some at a lower.
And then there are frequencies we can
even go to that do not contain pendulums
at all. We're going to go over, you
know, are pendulums good or bad and
everything like that. And just to kind
of give that away, they're not
necessarily good or bad. They are just
focused on survival and kind of growing
themselves. And we'll go over how that
actually works. You see, everything has
a thought form or a pendulum. Absolutely
anything you can think of has
essentially a thought form or pendulum
that a part of it, right? So any idea,
any kind of movement, any group, you
know, even things that seem innocuous um
you know, like um certain companies,
right? or or certain like ways of doing
things like sports, volleyball has a
thought form or a pendulum behind it.
You know, certain bands have thought
forms or pendulums behind them. Certain
political movements especially have
strong thought forms and pendulums
behind them, right? And what happens is
when you focus in on the sport, you
focus in on the political group, you
focus in on on whatever the thing is,
even certain objects like record players
for example, uh VHS sets, these are kind
of more inactive pendulums because as
time moves along, people take their
focus off them. They're still
technically active to a degree, but have
much less power. But when you start
thinking or activating the pendulum in
your life or accessing is a better way
of saying it, accessing the resonance
frequency of whatever the pendulum or
thought form is, you suddenly get kind
of influenced into its energy. Depending
on the pendulum, this can be either a
good or a bad thing on for you depending
on your goals. Some pendulums will
absolutely just extract your energy for
its own gain. Other pendulums may supply
you with energy again for its own gain,
but in this case, it also benefits you
and becomes a win-win. One thing to
really keep in mind when it comes to
pendulums is we'll go here first is
they're all about survival, right?
They're not really concerned about you.
So, when you're accessing any pendulum,
you have to be careful. Even ones that
seem good. Now there are c certainly
pendulums that we could observe as
harmless or even beneficial to you in
the moment. And so long as they are
serving you and those thought forms are
serving you, there is no problem in
accessing it, giving energy to it, and
it then returning whatever it's
returning to you. But for the vast
majority of pendulums, they tend to have
a negative um influence on people's
lives. This is stuff like political
parties. This is stuff like certain
movements and whatever else it is. It
tends to take your energy without giving
much in return or take your energy and
again influence your thoughts in a
certain direction or keep you at a
different resonance frequency. Now, this
part is very important and we'll put the
word resonance in there because that's a
very important word for us to have here
is that certain pendulums can only
extract your energy or or or kind of
feed off of you. That's essentially what
they're doing is they're feeding off of
your energy for survival
and can only do it if you are within
their resonance frequency. Meaning if
you're not within their resonance
frequency, you're beyond it. They can't
touch you. So for example, if you are
vibrating at a higher frequency or
consciousness, certain pendulums just
cannot access you because they cannot
survive in the environment you are
currently at. And again, its main goal
is survival and growing and kind of
expanding its own energy. So it's not
going to waste too much time in trying
to hook you if you're not within its
resonance frequency. it's not worth it
to the pendulum or the thought form. Um
I heard someone once say um a mentor
said um with thought forms or also known
as aggregors is another name for them is
they will try maybe about two or three
times to hook you into their resonance
frequency. And if you just don't cling
on to those thoughts, they move on.
Because if they stay in your energetic
field for too long and you are beyond
their reach and they can't get you to
come down, then it actually is
detrimental to them because you actually
start absorbing their energy versus them
being able to absorb yours. You're now
coming from a higher level of energy
that can't be touched by whatever this
thought form or pendulum is. And so they
then move on to whoever's next. And so
learning how to deal with pendulums and
thought forms also protects you from
harmful ones that mean to extract your
energy even though it gives you the
illusion of providing you with something
good. Again, a political movement is a
great one to focus on because a lot of
people believe that it's some some
people believe it's good to be in that
but a lot of times it is just a powerful
pendulum that is hooking people in and
extracting their energy for its own
means which is to expand to become more
powerful etc etc. So now going over
this, the goal again of all pendulums
pretty much is to access your energy.
This is how they survive and this is how
they expand their influence. Again, it's
almost parasitical unless you're very
very careful and specific about which
pendulums and thought forms you
entertain. Again, certain pendulums can
do a lot of good for you. But
understand, at the end of the day, this
is always their goal. Their goal is
always survival. Their goal is never to
elevate you unless it benefits them.
They have no heart in the sense of, oh,
they care for you, therefore they're
going to elevate you. They will only do
that if it also serves them to do so.
And so, within reality trans surfing,
where a lot of this comes, they'll talk
about how certain pendulums will have
favorites. And these favorites, they
actually give a lot of energy and kind
of elevate because it helps them as
well. So, always keep in mind, it's only
going to help you if you're helping them
in some way or there's some benefit to
this thought form or pendulum promoting
you or giving you energy or whatever
else. And so, we can think of certain
pendulums that would have more of a
positive influence that we can tune into
again because it's going to be a
win-win. But we still have to be careful
because as soon as it becomes a win-lose
in the sense that it will start
extracting energy and not giving back to
you, you want to cut ties from that
pendulum and get out of its resonance
frequency. Now remember, a pendulum
accesses you typically through thought
energy. Meaning it will try and hook you
and get you to a certain resonance
frequency via thought. And the way it
does this is you you have ever noticed
if you've had thoughts and I say you had
thoughts uh loosely here because it's
not really what's happening but certain
thoughts come into your mind and you
look at them and go I didn't think that
that's not me. I did not suggest that
thought that's not coming from me. It
seems to be coming from an outside
influence. That is most likely a
pendulum or thought form. If you go into
a room with a group of people and
especially let's say if the energy of
the room is slightly more negative and
you notice this happening, it is the
pendulum of the group or that room that
is trying to hook you into the energy of
that room so it can take your energy as
well and grow stronger. In a nutshell,
that's essentially what's happening. And
so you're going to have thoughts that
come in that try, if you're not already,
to get you within the resonance
frequency of the pendulum so it can then
feed or extract energy, right? And it
will do a lot, especially if it's got
you in its resonance frequency to keep
you there. So supplying you with
thoughts that make sense with the energy
you're currently in. So maybe getting
you to complain, oh that's unfair, this
person did this or that is is a
beautiful place for you to be for
certain pendulums because then it's very
easy to extract energy. Have you ever
noticed also when you're being like
that, let's say more of a victim level
consciousness, you're complaining,
you're moaning that you also seem to
feel low energy. You also seem to feel
drained. Maybe you haven't really done
much physically. There's nothing really
in the physical sense that should make
you tired, but maybe you feel tired all
the time when you're in these energies.
Yes. because your energy actually is
being in a sense harvested and extracted
by these pendulums. One analogy or
comparison I really love, if you've ever
seen the Harry Potter series, they have
something called um oh now I've
forgotten what they're called, but
they're the cloaked figures that kind of
suck the essence out of people and it
gets cold. Uh dementors, that's what
they're called. And I I kind of think
that either the author was aware of
pendulums or something similar and
brought that in or it was just some kind
of some kind of synchronicity that
happened there because they they act
actually very similar to how in the
thought realm pendulums act where they
kind of drain your energy. They they
suck your energy. They need it for their
survival. They you know I think in the
Harry Potter series dementors give you
all these crazy thoughts. They describe
it like the biggest feeling of despair.
you know, it's similar. It's it's more
Hollywood and kind of extreme because
this will be more subtle at times, but
it can be analogous to what's in that
book in that way. I always find that
very interesting that it's so close and
you can probably find it in other
stories and, you know, um fiction uh
similar ideas except this is a very real
thing. Again, thoughts are things,
pendulums and thought forms are real
things that exist. Uh they're not just
ideas. They exist within a certain realm
and they have a modus operandi. They're
trying to again survive like anything is
trying to do by extracting your energy.
Again, they do this through thought
trying to do that and they do this
through your attention. And this is a
very important part of it because you
might think, "Oh, I won't succumb to
this pendulum of this political party. I
will do the opposite." Well, you're
still actually giving it energy. A
pendulum again is not a moral character.
It does not care in which way you give
it attention. It need only require your
attention to take your energy or to
start influencing your life. And so one
of the solutions to removing certain
pendulums from our lives is to literally
turn our back to the pendulum. When the
thoughts come up, we just ignore them
and let them pass by. The suggestions
that try to hook you. When it tries to
get you to fight it in the sense of,
"Oh, you hate me. You don't want me, you
hate me. So why not fight me? Why not do
the opposite?" we just do not engage
because what it's trying to do is hook
you through opposition to it. So, you
know, whether it's Republican to
Democrat, Democrat to Republican, or you
know, this idea, you know, veganism to
carnivore, carnivore to veganism,
whatever it is, it's causing the battle,
but keeps actually those two groups in a
similar place of being able to harvest
their energy. And so the way we avoid
this with negative pendulums that would
influence you in this way that you don't
want is we simply turn our backs to them
and we do not give them our attention
while focusing our attention to
frequencies that actually benefit us.
Okay. So now we're going to go over some
of the main ways a pendulum tries to
hook or control you so you'll be more
aware of when this is going on. You may
find as we go through this that you're
already have these influences in your
life. And then we're going to go over
what you can do to defeat a pendulum.
And then we will also go over when you
should ride or allow a pendulum to take
you because it will be beneficial.
Right? So we'll have basically
everything involved here. Now, here are
some of the main ways in which a
pendulum, you know, is trying to control
you or perhaps is. The first thing is
they're going to do is they're going to
try and provoke you in some kind of way.
Again, this could be through thought.
This could even be through something
outside of you happening to you, someone
saying something to you. you know,
they'll absolutely use other people
within kind of their influence to do
this to you and get you into the
resonance they need you to be in or to
keep you in the resonance they need you
to be in. For example, again, with
political parties, you can see this
playing out because the pendulum doesn't
care which side of the aisle you're on.
It loves that they fight each other
because that's a way of provoking that
keeps everyone within its control, being
able to extract the energy. The next
thing is trying to make you feel either
right or wrong. A huge ego game. Trying
to get one up on someone else. You know,
spiritual oneupsmanship or anything
else. I'm right. You're wrong. Or the
other way going, "Nah, I'm wrong. You
know, I'm always wrong." Right? On the
other end of the spectrum, it will love
to use this one because it feeds into
our ego, which keeps us in lower
conscious states, which makes us
accessible for energy extraction. The
next is drama, which is another obvious
one. anything that's dramatic. You'll
notice maybe people around you getting
involved in drama, in gossip, in this
kind of stuff. Another favorite of the
pendulum because it keeps you right
within that range of their frequency to
just continually take your energy. Drama
is a huge one. The next is always
needing to be in arguments or fights or
online. Fighting and arguing with people
absolutely put you into their resonance
frequency. Again, it doesn't care what
side of the aisle you're on. only cares
that you're giving it attention. Um, and
especially if you're doing it
emotionally, it gives it more energy to
feed off of. Remember, emotion is energy
in motion. When you're angry and
frustrated, you're giving off more
energy. It absolutely laps that up. And
so, we'll keep you in that. Which brings
us to defend or attack, which is kind of
the same thing. Both require quite a bit
of energy. Both feed it quite a bit of
energy. So, it'll try and put you in
that place, show you things that it
thinks you'll attack or want to defend
against. and get you into that zone
again through urgency or fear. If you
ever find you're rushing, you're in this
urgent state, it feels like life or
death, even though after you know it's
not going to feel that way, this is
usually a pendulum trying to get you,
control you, or keep you within its
resonance. Fear is one of its favorite
um places to put people because it's
just one of the just easiest things to
put people on the planet. Again, fear
and pride, right and wrong would be with
pride, arguments, defend or attack,
usually with pride, obviously fear being
different. But ultimately understand
it's trying to keep you in low levels of
consciousness, low levels of frequency.
As you start going up the consciousness
scale, if you're aware of the Hawking
scale of consciousness, once you start
to get to level 200 and above, you start
to get out of the range of negative
pendulums and thought forms. And it
actually becomes a risk for those
pendulums to try and hook you or get you
because they then have to go into an
environment that doesn't support their
energy. and they can start losing
influence and energy if they stay in
that environment too long, which is what
we ultimately want to do, right? So, if
we're in low consciousness, we are
susceptible. When we raise our
frequency, we're not. And that's going
to be a part of the solutions is don't
try and get hooked into it or argue with
it or whatever else. Just aim to raise
your frequency and consciousness and you
will be out of the way or range of
influence by these pendulums. And the
other ones are news, content, conflict,
especially addiction to these things. If
you find you are addicted to the news,
addicted to content. So scrolling on the
internet, scrolling on Instagram. Again,
a lot of this is um if I can get this
pen off,
a lot of this usually calibrates at
drama or it calibrates at fear, even
urgency, right? These contents usually
are at this level of consciousness.
Again, you can ride good pendulums in a
higher level of consciousness, but if
you find that whatever you're being
influenced by is drama- based, it's
trying to provoke you into a reaction,
it's trying to put you in fear or low
consciousness, again, this is one of the
ways in which pendulums will go to
control you. Again, conflict being the
other. So, another one of I just put it
over here in big letters because this is
a big one. One of the favorite tools of
the pendulum is something called um
excessive potential or importance. They
will try and make you create all of this
importance around something. We can also
think of this as pedestalization. And if
you're trying to create things in your
life, there is nothing that will push
further away from you what it is you
want than raising importance. And this
is another favorite of the pendulum to
get you into its resonance frequency and
extract and harvest your energy. So,
when you're putting this inflated
importance on something in your life,
one of the first things you want to do
is something we're about to go over,
lower the importance. So, how do you
defeat a pendulum? Again, a pendulum
can't control you necessarily in the
sense of it can make you do exactly what
it wants you to do. It tries to
influence you, but at the end of the
day, you are the creator and you are way
more powerful than the pendulum. What
the pendulum aims to do is influence and
manipulate manipulate you in a way to
get you in range and then extract your
energy because you're very powerful. It
wants your energy, but can only do it if
it succeeds in manipulating you. If it
was more powerful than you, it would
just overwhelm you. It wouldn't need
your permission. It wouldn't need you to
basically disempower yourself. It would
just take your energy hook, line, and
sinker. That's not the way it is. You
can raise your energy because you're a
powerful being well beyond the influence
of a pendulum. A pendulum is only as
strong as the people it can bring into
its structure. And again, you are more
powerful than that structure. If those
people are removed, if those thoughts,
that energy that's being extracted is
removed. The pendulum falls and dies. It
stops. It can't keep going. It sway and
swing no longer as influential. Again,
we talked about some old pendulums, some
innocuous ones. But you can also look at
certain political movements that are no
more. Those pendulums are now
essentially dead. We can look at things
like again record players, VHS's might
be a certain sway. Those are more
innocuous for the most part. Um but
again the influence is gone. They have
no power because the power of the people
who use these things and thought about
these things is no longer there. So
moving on to what we can do. The first
one is we already mentioned but it's
don't react. That's the first one. When
it tries to provoke you, when it tries
to get you to argue and do all these
things, try not to react. Don't get
hooked in. Now, if you do react, then
best next thing to do is to take a step
back and get yourself out of the
reaction. So, let's say you react
immediately and you realize you reacted.
Wake up and take a step back. Get out of
the energy of the reaction because right
now you're quite literally being
harvested. You are having your energy
extracted and it's trying to get you to
spiral to be able to take your energy
for a longer period of time. You ever
notice when you do react that it can
sometimes dictate your whole day if you
allow it? Yeah. Because it is a pendulum
trying to keep that going to continually
have you in its frequency so it can take
your energy. So the first thing is don't
react. We already mentioned this next
one which is lower
importance.
Elevated importance is a pendulum's one
of its favorite tools or a thought
form's favorite tool to make you put
importance in all these things.
importance on money, importance on
health, importance on relationships. And
again, we have been convinced to believe
that the more importance we put on
something, again, because of the
influence of a pendulum, this is a
thought that is propagated by them, that
if we put more importance on something,
we're more likely to get it. Well, how's
that been working out? The more
important you put on something, the more
you push it away. So, if you're
desperate for more money, you usually
end up not having as much. If you're
desperate for a certain kind of
relationship, you usually don't get it.
kind of like being needy in a
relationship and it kind of repelling
the other person. Um, so long as
everything's healthy in that in that
situation, right? And so the way to
counter this is always lower the
importance. You can say something for
example, you know, everything is going
to work out in my favor um even if I
don't know how. Right? That takes away
the control element of needing it to
happen in a certain way. And the
pendulum is going to try and convince
you that it has to happen in a certain
way. You need to control this and
control that. when in reality we just
need to lower the importance. A great
quote is when you lower the importance a
solution will present itself because
when you lower the importance your
frequency automatically rises because
you're no longer in fear. You're no
longer in apathy. You're no longer in
drama because you don't need things to
happen in a certain way. So you move
beyond that. You move into typically at
least willingness and acceptance which
are high levels of consciousness. And
you can use that as a springboard to go
higher which will actually allow for
favorable results to happen. So we need
to lower the importance. The next is to
be the observer and to remind yourself
to do this often.
This is going to help you to not react
and also lower the importance. It's also
going to help you with the next one as
well. But you want to move more into the
role of the observer. Don't be a
participant yet. be an observer who then
will choose what they wish to
participate in after they've kind of
seen the lay of the land. Right? So
instead of just getting hooked and
hooked and hooked and react, react,
react, you take a step back and here's
this thought that's coming in. Okay,
here's a thought. It's just a thought.
So it's nothing yet, but is it something
that serves me or is it something that's
trying to extract from me? And you see
this thought that's trying to provoke
you drama- based arguments or whatever
else. And now that you're the observer,
you see that it's separate from you. You
see, one thing the pendulum will try and
do is it will try and get you to
identify with the thought. So you think
it's you. You think this thought is
coming from you. You think you are the
thought. And then hook, line, and
sinker. You're in one of these. And the
pendulum has you in its resonance
frequency. But when you're the observer,
you're the one watching the thought.
Therefore, you can't be the thought. You
are not the thought. It is just a
thought. You are someone experiencing a
thought or it is coming to your
awareness and attention and you
recognize as the observer you get to
make a choice in what relationship you
would like to have with this thought or
idea or energy or whatever is coming up.
This works for emotions as well. You're
the observer and you now get to make a
choice. And so you can now choose this
is something I will take on or this is
something I will allow to pass by. It
won't get hooked. And remember, with
pendulums or thought forms, it will try
two or three times to get you into its
resonance frequency. And if it can't,
because you're you're at a higher
frequency, it will move on because it is
at risk. Remember, it's self-centered.
It is at risk by continuing to try and
hook you. So, it's not going to take
that risk. Right? If you're in an
elevated frequency, it will try maybe a
couple times, but if it can't get you,
it will move on. Right? So, the next
thing is to redirect your focus. So,
you've been the observer.
You've observed. Now you want to choose
differently.
I did not give myself enough space
there. So there you go. So now you
redirect your focus. So you have
observed, you've not reacted, you've
lowered the importance. Now you still
want to make a choice. You are a
creator. You are making choices. Now you
can choose either to use a thought to
get onto a pendulum that benefits you or
just to choose how what direction you
want to go in. Right? So this thought
comes up. this thought comes up. And
what's great about these thoughts when
you're not reacting is you can look at
them and through contrast be better
directed in which way you want to go.
And what I mean is let's say you have a
thought and you're like, "No, I don't
want to do that. No, I don't want to do
that." It brings up the question, well,
what do you want to do? And those other
thoughts actually help to birth what it
is you do want. And then you can move in
that direction and focus by choosing
differently what you want. Notice this
isn't change something. It's not trying
to change the thought because then the
egregor or the pendulum's won because
you're now wrestling with the thought.
You're trying to change it. Again, it's
like having a captain at the ship of
your vessel that's moving in a certain
direction and you try and change a
negative captain. The captain's not
going to change. But if you choose a new
captain that goes in place that just is
going in that direction, well then
suddenly you'll be off to the races
moving where you want to go. So you
always want to choose differently and
redirect your focus. And so I would keep
in mind all of these and the ways they
try to hook you and then remembering all
of these to defeat it. You notice it's
not that complicated to defeat one. Why
is it not complicated? Why is it not
hard when you get this? Because you are
infinitely more powerful than a
pendulum. You are infinitely more
powerful than an agregore or thought
form. But this doesn't mean to then, you
know, go off and not be aware of them.
be aware so you know if they're trying
to hook you. And then bring yourself
back into your power, your ability to be
the observer and creator again. This is
observation. This is creation.
Excuse my terrible writing here. This is
observation. This is creation. And these
two help you to move back into what you
truly are, which is the observer and
creator. Right? So this allows you to
observe because you're being the
observer. And then this allows you to
create based on your observation. You've
observed, you've seen the actual lay of
the land. Now with that information and
data, you step into your power as a
creator and choose the direction you
want to go. Okay. So now we need to talk
briefly about the conditions where you
can ride a pendulum and actually
benefit. Now, this could be for almost
any pendulum, although we want ones that
more of a positive frequency, but
depending on how you interact with it
and what it gives you, um, you can
safely ride a pendulum. We'll go over
what that is and also some pitfalls to
watch out for. Basically, the pitfalls
are from that last screen. If any of
that's happening, like it's trying to
hook you, it's trying to get you into
drama. If any of that's happening and
you're succumbing to it, then you want
to stop riding this pendulum. But in a
lot of cases, it can be hugely
beneficial. For example, um let's say
you know a certain meditation technique
is a pendulum, right? And let's say you
are joyfully riding that pendulum. It's
providing you energy and everything
else. Then that's a beneficial thing.
But let's say then you get incredibly
serious and rigid and almost in your
head about it. Then you're suddenly
feeding just the pendulum without
gaining anything in return. Right?
You've raised the importance. You've
created drama around it. And so even
though the idea is seen as a really good
one in a vacuum, you've now succumbed to
a frequency uh with that pendulum where
it's actually just extracting energy
from you and it ceases to become
beneficial. So understand there might be
things you go oh this is good in a
nutshell but there are people for
example who align with certain spiritual
say modalities that can be really good
but become for example very prideful
about it. They become very right versus
wrong about it. And that's when it can
take a dangerous toll. So don't just
look at it at face value or appearances.
Look at how it's making you feel and
everything else. So one thing is if it
aligns to you is something that you can
ride and go with. So for example, the
pendulum of meditation, the pendulum of
certain spiritual ideas, right? Those
still exist. And if they align to you,
which means they're going to energize
and uplift you, that's a perfectly good
pendulum to follow and allow to ride
along because you're going to gain
energy from it. Essentially, any that's
going to give you good energy is a good
one to align with. The next thing is it
doesn't drain you. If you ever notice a
pendulum is draining you, you either
need to reconstruct your relationship
with it because you might be raising
importance or doing all this other stuff
or it's time to completely just release
that relationship to this pendulum
because it's getting to a point where
it's not benefiting you. Right? So, if
it's draining you, that's something you
need to also be aware of. And the next
thing is don't be attached to its
outcomes. Maybe certain things within
the pendulum have certain outcomes
they're going for and you need to make
sure you are not attached to these
raising importance through these or
again now being susceptible to having
your energy drained in order to support
its outcome. Remember this is about your
journey and what you came here to
create. If you get sucked into a
movement that has a particular outcome,
unless it is completely aligned and
therefore gives you joy, you're going to
be in for a rough ride. And a lot of
people get seduced into that thinking,
"Oh, that's the outcome I want, but it's
really just being the influence of the
pendulum." Again, if it feels draining,
if it puts you in low consciousness, if
it does not uplift and align, then it
isn't your true dharma or journey or
whatever we're calling it. But again, if
this is fulfilled, then you can ride the
pendulum and gain energy via or through
it. Just recognize that no pendulum is
looking to necessarily support you
without benefit to itself. Don't look at
it from a moral standpoint. These are
just thought forms that have one mission
essentially, and that is to survive and
thrive energetically by having more
adherence um and gaining more energy
through them. So, they don't care how
they do it. They don't care if also you
benefit or you don't. But they, you
know, for example, if if this if you
died, they wouldn't care. Let's just say
it that way, right? So make sure this
criteria is fit if you're going to
follow one. Now again, this could be you
joining a movement joyfully without
identification, right? So you actually
gain a lot by being in whatever movement
or whatever the thing is. You get joy
out of it. It aligns, it uplifts, it
doesn't drain you. But the moment you
start becoming emotional, serious,
rigid, um understand that you're now
feeding the pendulum and moving away
from your purpose with whatever that is,
it is no longer benefiting you and now
it's extracting your energy instead of
uplifting you. Essentially, the easiest
litmus test is when you are with a
pendulum, is it uplifting you and
causing your energy to raise? Does it
seem like you have more energy to work
with? And again, things at higher levels
of consciousness will typically have
this effect more. or does it feel like
it's draining you? Does it feel like
it's just using your energy? Do you feel
that it's just leaving you depleted?
Then that is one you most likely want to
just distance yourself from. And again,
using the steps we had in the last
screen to get out of its resonance
frequency. Now, this is some great
stuff. And if you want to really learn
how to do this at a high level, you can
check out mold your reality down below.
It's going to show you how to do this
quickly and so much more. We're getting
amazing results coming through that
program which will be on screen right
now as I'm talking. I've made it very
affordable. You get two coaching calls a
week and so much more. You can learn
more through the link below. Or if you
want to work with me on an even closer,
more kind of one-on-one small groupoup
basis, I have that down below as well.
Now, this next video over here is also
going to help you to wire this in even
more and benefit even more what you've
learned today. So you are creating now
with the awareness of pendulums, making
sure you don't get sucked into their
frequency and also being able to use
them to your benefit.