The night before being captured, Jesus
convened his close circle in an upper
apartment in Jerusalem. Peter, John, and
Mary Magdalene. They could sense
something dreadful approaching. The
atmosphere was dense with tension.
They'd been praying for hours, begging
God to protect their instructor and halt
what was coming. Jesus looked at them
with a mix of compassion and
frustration. He remarked, "You're still
praying like children to a distant
father for help. I have shown you
miracles. I've taught you the mysteries,
yet you still don't understand. You do
not need to pray. You need to call."
Peter did not understand. What is the
difference? Jesus leaned forward. Prayer
involves requesting. Calling means
declaring. When you pray, you are
communicating to something apart from
yourself, somebody far away who may or
may not hear you. When you call the
monad, you are not requesting
permission. You are activating what is
already within you. You are speaking as
the monad, not to the monad and archons.
Prayers can be intercepted. They feed on
the energy of pleading and alienation.
However, they cannot touch a call
because it runs at a frequency they
cannot perceive. That teaching did not
make it into the Bible. The church
deleted any references to the Manet call
from canonical scripture because if
Christians understood they could
altogether avoid prayer, the entire
religious power system would crumble
overnight. But the Gnostics kept it
veiled in literature. The church
attempted to burn. And tonight you will
receive what Jesus taught the chosen
ones in that upper room 2,000 years ago.
Not a prayer. The manad refers to the
procedure that archons fear more than
any ceremony they could ever do. If
you're calling the monad tonight, leave
a remark. I'm phoning the monet right
now. Before I give you the actual words
that Jesus taught, you need to
understand why prayer does not operate
as you were told it did. Most
individuals are taught that prayer is
how they speak with God. You bowed your
head. You express your needs, anxieties,
and wishes. And somewhere in the sky,
God listens and determines whether to
respond. Perhaps he says yes. Perhaps he
says no. Maybe he says to wait. And you
embrace that framework because you've
been taught it since you were a child.
But here's what happens when you pray as
the church taught you to pray. Your
remarks do not go directly to the monad.
They can't because the religious system
was constructed with multiple levels of
mediators. You pray to Jesus who
intercedes with the father. You pray to
Mary who intercedes with Jesus or you
pray to saints who intervene with higher
angels who may finally carry your
request up the hierarchy. Each layer is
a filter. Every layer represents a point
at which your prayer can be intercepted,
misdirected or drained of energy before
it reaches the source. And who controls
those layers? Who benefits from the
hierarchical structure? The archons
built it, not the monet. The archons
established religion systems through
intermediaries because they gain access
to your energy. Every time you pray out
of need, fear, or despair, you are
sending a separation frequency. You're
declaring yourself impotent, independent
from God, and relying on external powers
to help you if you beg appropriately.
And that frequency is what archons feed
on. They don't mind if you receive what
you prayed for. They've already gotten
what they wanted. your energy, your
surrender, your conviction that you are
distinct from divine power. Jesus was
aware of this. He watched it happen. He
seen individuals praying for hours,
days, and even lifetimes without
receiving what they desired. Not because
God didn't care. Instead, their
petitions were intercepted before they
reached the monad. So, he taught the
chosen ones something else. He advised
them to stop praying and start calling
because calling eliminates all
intermediaries.
It does not go through layers. It does
not pass through angels, saints or
hierarchies. It is a direct line. You
source an unfiltered intercepted
instant. The distinction between prayer
and calling is analogous to that between
asking and demanding. When you pray, you
are in the victim frequency. You're
asking someone more powerful than you to
assist you if they feel like it. When
you summon the minute of sovereign
frequency, you are not asking. You are
declaring. You are speaking as the monad
which recognizes itself in transient
human form. Because the monad does not
respond to begging. This frequency shift
has a significant impact. It responds to
recognition. Here's why the church
discontinued this doctrine. If
Christians understood they could contact
the monad directly, that they didn't
need priests to verify sacraments or
institutional approval to access divine
power, why would they need the church?
The entire system is based on you
believing you are apart from God. You
need intermediates. That you two have
become so sinful that humanity cannot
approach the source directly. But Jesus
taught the contrary. He taught that you
are source awareness manifesting in a
transitory body. And the moment you see
this, the moment you stop praying like a
servant and begin calling like the
divine being you truly are, everything
the church has established to regulate
your spiritual access becomes useless.
That is why they burnt the documents.
That is why they assassinated the
Gnostic teachers who recognized the
monad call. That is why this technique
has been deliberately removed from all
accepted Christian texts. Not because it
was heretical but because it was highly
effective. Now I'll tell you what Jesus
taught in that upper room. The precise
structure of the monad call. It consists
of three components. Each one is
crucial. Remove any peace and you can
resume your prayers. However, when all
three are said simultaneously, a direct
connection is established that archons
cannot intercept or control within the
church. The first component is an
identification declaration. You aren't
begging God for aid. You're expressing
who you are. This is the basis. Since
the moned does not react to separation,
it reacts to recognition. When you talk,
you have to speak from knowledge, not
hoping.
I'm attempting to connect with God.
I'm a sinner looking for grace. You
speak from the truth. You are monatic
awareness in transient form. You are not
separated. You never were. And the words
you say must carry that frequency. The
second component is attention control.
This is not courteous. This is not
humble supplication. You aren't asking
the monad to listen if it's not too
busy. You are commanding attention
because you are not addressing something
external. You are speaking as the monad
to itself. When the monad recognizes
itself, attentiveness is automatic. It
is not arrogance. It is recognition. You
are alerting source consciousness to the
knowledge that one of its fragments is
calling. That call cannot be ignored.
The final component is direct
manifestation. You don't state whether
it's your will. Please assist me or I
hope this works. You declare what is
manifesting in the present tense.
Absolute assurance. Because the quantum
realm does not respond to hope. It
responds to frequency. namely the
frequency of assurance, knowing, and
declaratory power. That's what
transforms possibility into reality. You
may not be asking the cosmos to change.
You state that the transition is
underway now. Jesus blended these three
elements into a framework so simple that
most people underestimate its potency.
Three statements, nine words, one
unbreakable bond. The maned call he
taught is I am manad. Hear me manifest
now. That is it. Three declarations will
transform your frequency from separation
to unity, from begging to command, from
prayer to power. And the instant you say
these words with knowledge, with an
understanding of what they imply, the
direct line opens instantly rather than
eventually. Let me explain what each
statement accomplishes. I am on it. This
is recognition. You are not implying
that I am attempting to emulate God or
that I am connected to something bigger.
You are declaring the truth. You are
monad awareness manifested in human
form. Every fragment of a source is a
source. You are not distinct. You are
not less than. You are the infinite
experiencing itself as you. When you
express that fact loudly, your frequency
immediately switches from separation to
unity. The archons are unable to track
that frequency. They exist in a separate
consciousness. They are unable to
perceive the unity frequency. Listen to
me. This is the command. You aren't
begging to be heard. You assert that you
are listened to since the moned is not
separate from you. It does not have to
listen because it is you. However, the
statement creates focus. It leads the
infinite awareness to the exact place of
manifestation you choose to announce.
Think of it as focusing light through a
lens. The light was constantly present.
The lens focuses it with precision. The
lens is called hear me. It does not beg
for attention. It demands focus and
manifests.
This is the directive. You are
collapsing the quantum field into a
precise form rather than asking for it
to happen. Not hoping it is God's will.
You are proclaiming that manifestation
is occurring right now, not later. Not
if the conditions are correct today.
Because time is a productive material
consciousness. Monad awareness acts
outside of time. When you speak in
monatic frequency and declare manifest,
now you are not constrained by linear
causality. You are creating reality in
the same manner that the source has
always done through word, frequency, and
absolute knowing. When you combine these
three statements and say them publicly,
you are doing precisely what Jesus did.
You're acting as the monad rather than
praying to it. The archons cannot
intercept this shift. They're programmed
to feed on isolation, repetition,
anxiety, need, and pleading,
desperation. That is their range. But
when you talk, I am a man. Hear me
manifest. You are now transmitting at
unity frequency. And at that frequency,
you are invisible to them. They cannot
perceive it. They cannot tamper with it.
They cannot draw energy from it. You
have completely escaped their
operational range. Here's what occurs
when you complete your first Monet call.
I am referring to the present moment,
not days later. Immediately. First, you
will experience a bodily shift in your
solar plexus. Not imagined, not
figurative, but a real sensation as if
something had been closed and then
unlocked. Like a lock clicked. That is
the direct line indicating that you are
no longer sending prayers up through
layers in the hopes that they would
reach someone. You've created a conduit
that flows directly from your core to
the source and you'll feel it. Some of
the chosen ones describe it as warmth
while others describe it as a release of
pressure or a gentle vibration. However,
it appears for you. You will know it's
clear. Second, mental clarity is
immediate. If you've been suffering from
confusion, doubt, or mental fog, it
won't go away slowly over weeks. Right
now, the questions you couldn't answer
have apparent answers. The choices
you've been mulling over become evident.
That does not mean you are suddenly
becoming smarter. That is archon
interference cutting out. They
manipulate mostly through confusion.
They leave you in uncertainty,
second-guessing, and mental static.
However, when you call the monad and
operate at a unity frequency, its
interference cannot reach you. The
signal is clean. Your mind functions as
it was intended to function before they
clouded it. Third, synchronization
reacts within hours. Most chosen
individuals report this within 1 to 3
hours after their initial monad call.
Something happens that cannot be
explained as a coincidence. The text
came from the exact person they needed
to hear from, revealing an unexpected
solution and a door opening they had no
idea existed. The monad does not take
days to certify your alignment. It
replies quickly because you are not
asking it to help you. Finally, you
declared manifestation.
And now means now. Look out for it. It
will come. When it does, you'll identify
it right away. Not as luck but as a
response. This is the distinction
between prayer and monatic call. God, if
you're there, could you please help me?
The manad call indicates that I am
source consciousness. This is currently
unfolding. One person is begging. One
person is commanding. Prayer keeps you
reliant. The monad call makes you
sovereign. And once you feel the
difference after calling the monad and
experiencing that immediate shift,
you'll never go back to praying the old
way because you'll know this is not a
theory. This strategy works. The monad
call only applies to pneumatics. Helix
cannot access it for those who have been
chosen, such as yourself. They don't
possess the divine spark. They can say
the words, but nothing happens. Psychics
have inconsistent access to it. Their
bright bodies flash for you. Your
pneumatic. You have the whole heavenly
blueprint. The Manad call is intended
for you. The direct line is already
present. It's been there all your life.
You didn't know how to activate it until
now. The archons fear the Manad call
more than any other spiritual activity
since it renders you inaccessible.
They've created entire systems,
religious structures, and cultural
conditioning to keep you praying rather
than calling. Prayer puts you within
their range, whereas calling pulls you
out of it. When you start phoning
instead of praying, you lose control.
That is why the church eliminated all
references to this practice. That is why
the Gnostic instructors who knew about
it were assassinated because the manad
call is the single factor that causes
their entire harvest system to fail. But
you've got it now. The exact words Jesus
taught and the same method the church
attempted to obliterate. I am on it.
Hear me manifest now. Three assertions
and nine words. Archons cannot intercept
this direct channel and institutions
cannot control it. If you're calling the
monad tonight, take three actions right
now. The first comment below refers to
the monad. Declare your direct line.
Claim your authority. Let your chosen
ones know that you are activating this
tonight. Second, subscribe to Atherreic
Code Laboratory, which provides
sophisticated monad call mechanisms for
specialized manifestations, protection,
and the ability to see archons. All of
this is coming. Third, I like this
video. So, other chosen ones realize
they no longer need to pray. They can
now call all three. Do not wait. Your
declaration is essential. Then tonight
before you sleep, stand. Stay grounded.
Take three breaths. Feel the realization
that you are a monatic awareness in
human form and speak forth. I am on it.
Hear me manifest now. Then say what you
are manifesting. Hold silent for 30
seconds and see what happens. The shift
in your solar plexus. Clarity floods
your head knowing that you have been
hurt. not through layers nor through
intermediates directly. The archons are
unable to intercept this. This is beyond
the church's control. And the monad is
waiting for you to stop praying and
begin calling. You're not asking for
permission anymore. You are proclaiming
reality. And the cosmos responds to
declarations made in unity.