Hunter Hunter chapter 1 is a big deal.
Not just because it's different from the
anime episode one. We all know that
Togashi had a different beginning of
Hunter Hunter that Madhouse Studio
changed. And I'm not hating on Madhouse
Studio. They did a great job for Hunter
Hunter 2011. But I want to say this,
Hunter Hunter Chapter 1 also fleshes out
what Togashi had in mind all along when
it comes to the Dark Continent, when it
comes to who's the main character and
Jing Freaks, and when it comes to Gone
Freaks also being a main character and
how they go back and forth, which I've
been talking about for years. So, I know
you guys are really excited, but let's
talk about it. The first ever chapter in
Hunter Hunter history. Make sure you
guys don't forget to like the video and
subscribe to the channel. Now, many
people believe the Dark Continent was a
redcon after found Jing at the end of
the Hunter Hunter anime, but I beg to
differ. I actually believe Toashi was
planning this since chapter 1. The first
two pages says it all. Strange beast and
monsters, secret treasure hordes,
undiscovered wealth, mystical places and
unexplored frontiers, the mysterious
unknown. There's magic in such words for
those captivated by its spell. aka
Jing and Gon have been destined for the
dark continent since the beginning. This
is not really explaining our hunter to
hunter experience in the anime. It's
more so explaining our hunter to hunter
experience that's going to be coming to
us in the future in the dark continent.
Yes. So I don't think what we saw with
the on the world tree was a redcon. I
actually think it was planned since day
one. And I think said once found Jing
which was which was initially Kite's
goal. I do believe he already had this
set in motion and that's why I believe
Jinx will be the main character and then
Goan will come back to take over as the
main character. Yes. And I truly believe
this first page of chapter 1 is
describing everything I'm talking about.
The second page goes on to say they are
called hunters with Gon and Kite. Like
2011 Madhouse anime of Hunter Hunter is
some of the greatest adaptation of anime
of manga I've ever seen. Honestly, I
think it actually makes Hunter Hunter a
better series. Yes, cuz um Toashi has
some very interesting word vomit and
interesting uh artwork. But I will say
this, when it comes to storytelling,
Toashi's mind does surpass the studio.
And he wanted Kite to be a main figure
in the beginning of Hunt to Hunter where
2011 is like, "Yeah, we'll just make him
a main figure when the Chimera Anarch
starts." Which I get what they're trying
to say. They're not trying to confuse
readers, but I think it would have been
so cool seeing Kite again. It's like
walking dead when you saw Morgan again.
So, I feel like they really dropped the
ball there, but they have done an
amazing job, so I can't say much. So,
the beginning of the Hunter Hunter
chapter is gone. He catches the master
of the old swamp. It says, "Five grown
men together couldn't do what this kid
just did." And his aunt Meto, knowing
this, said this is the only way she was
going to let him take the Hunter exam.
Yeah, she thought it was impossible as a
kid, but of course, he achieved it. And
of course, he she should have known he's
the son of Jing Freaks. Of course, he's
gonna achieve this. Yes, it's even
stated that Goon has the same gleam in
his eye as Jing. And Mito is shocked
that Goon wants to be a hunter when she
kept his father a secret. Like honestly,
a big reason on why I believe Jing will
be a main character in the Dark
Continent is because of how big Jing is
in the first ever chapter. Like the lore
that Jing has in the first ever chapter
gives him the only right to become the
main character after Gone. in my
opinion. We also get a flashback 3 years
before Gon goes to take the Hunter exam.
He's saved by Kite. This was shown in
the beginning of the Kam anarch in the
anime of 2011. And I think it did a
shame to Kite's character. Yes, Kite was
still an emotional moment for Goan and
everything, but I think that his his
importance definitely was undervalued. I
think it should have been in episode one
to make us as fans really gravitate
towards Kite. So to talk about this
moment, [music] Kite kills a fox bear
with a cub because of course it tried to
kill Gone as a kid. And he says if you
try to kill a human like a true hunter,
he has to take down the animal. I think
this is really cool to show also how
savage the world is in a sense and how
people underestimate animals like
because we live in kind of cities and
areas where there's not that many
animals, wild animals, but wild animals
will [ __ ] you up, guys. And I love how
Kite punches Gorn for wandering around
Snake Beach forest this time of year. It
could and saying that you could have
been killed. And he's kind of pissed off
that he had to kill a fox bear. You
could feel Kite's anger and his passion
when it comes to hunting. He doesn't
hunt for fun. He hunts because it has to
be done. It's a profession and he
doesn't want to kill aimlessly. We even
see Kite highlighting the territorial
mark of a fox bear when she's with her
cub and mentions the lies clearing out
till welping season is passed. Yes, Kite
is showing the details of what Gohan
ignored because Kite believes he didn't
have a father in his life. He's like,
"Didn't your father bother teaching you
anything?" Remember, Goan had no father
as Jing was a deadbeat. And Kite
mentions the squirrel giving him a
warning and that's the only reason he
knew that something was going on. And
now he got a pointless kill to his
credit. And Gohan tells Kite he has no
dad or mom and lives with his aunt. And
Kite kind of feels guilty for being too
hard on Goan and gives him some
antiseptic for his injured arm, which I
found pretty interesting. Kite then
tells Goon he's going to put down the
cub as it's better a scenario than
letting it starve to death. And might
have some hate towards humans for seeing
his mother killed by one. But Goon wants
to take care of the cub, showing great
uh love Goon has for the baby. And
honestly, I think this is really good
emotional intelligence. Like he does not
want this young animal to be killed.
Then we see Goan saying he will take
care of it as it's scratching at his
arm. Like honestly, he's a great kid
with compassion and sympathy for animals
and I loved it. And then Kite sees Jing
in Gon's eye. Remember I talked about
how Gon has the same gleam in his eye
like Jing? Yes, Kite sees it. Kite then
explains he's looking for Jen and pretty
much this is a big lead as he just found
one in Goon and tells Goon that Jing is
his teacher. He drilled the basics of
hunting and final challenge for Kite is
to find Jing. Kite also says Jing is the
best hunter and there's no one like him.
Remember Nero said Jing was a top five
Nen user and his ability to copy Nen as
a talent, not his Nen makes me believe,
yeah, Nzur wasn't lying. The hype is
real when it comes to Jing. Kite then
lets Goan know that Jing is alive even
though his aunt Mito wants to protect
Gohan and says all good hunters are good
with animals and pretty much says the
blood is telling when it comes to Goan
and it speaks volume when it comes to
potential that Goan has which is pretty
insane as we saw during the Pito versus
adult Goan fight how much potential he
truly had to avenge Kite. Also Kite
leaving Jing's hunter license was
amazing. Why didn't the anime show this
in the episode one? Like I still don't
understand. Like what a fail from a
great 2011 anime series which is pretty
much perfect. Like why not just do this
to make it even more perfect. Go then
tells Co, the cub of the fox bear, he's
going to be a hunter. And it's kind of
like a feel-good moment. And pretty much
he's I honestly would love to see Coin
the dog cartoonet after years during
Go's return with Nen. I think that'd be
super cool to see in a super adult
version of Coin the Fox bear. Then we
see Gohan tell the fox bear cub K hunter
do things animals hate and K as a king
of the forest can't be friends with the
hunter aka don't follow me. I love the
emotional intelligence by Goon trying to
tell him to stay away because he knows
he does he wants to do this journey by
himself like Goan is very mature for his
age. Goan also says family comes second
when it comes to being a hunter as Mito
finally admits that Jing is Goon's
father. That's something only Jing would
say. And Gorn recalls Kite who motivated
him to find his father Jing and follow
in his footsteps. The hardest challenge
that Kite said he had was to find Jing.
And after being a hunter, that was his
final test. And I think pretty much
growing got motivation for that goal to
find Jing as his main purpose. And he
found Jing at the end of the Anti Hunter
anime. But there's definitely a manga,
guys. And Dark Continent is on its way.
I also love how Aunt Meto admits Jing
never abandoned Go, but was forced to
give Go away. I I love that theory that
Goon might be a calamity like Alaka or
has to do with something that happened
in Jing's hunter alive maybe in her
content. I'm not too sure. As Goon says
he already knew because Mito never looks
in his eye when lying. Great emotional
intelligence by Gon Goon states he will
come back a great hunter to Meito which
angers the other applicants who were
like these guys are pretty much scrubs
but they're like yo why is this guy
talking so confident like does he not
know what he's getting himself into?
That's the energy I got. Then they also
try to give Goan a reality check saying
he should be happy if he even survives
the exam as Goan's journey begins to be
a hunter. Find Jing and of course we see
the captain of the ship muttering it's
going to be rough as he is one of the
examiners actually and the exams already
started. I think this chapter of Hunter
Hunter was a great start to this
chapter. So what are my final thoughts?
My final thoughts is this chapter is
going to be legendary till the end of
Hunter Hunter if we even get an ending
of Hunter Hunter. But they did promise
us 50 chapters. The reason why I say
it's going to be legendary is because we
do know some major things. Jing Freaks
is about to go crazy right now on this
trip to the dark continent and he's
about to be the main character.
Secondly, if Go comes back with his end
back, definitely is going to be really
cool to see of course him leaving again
the island that he was born and raised
and of course leaving the King of
Forests and going back to of course this
go to the dark continent. Maybe he
brings Killer there as well. I'm not too
sure. Then of course Kite. Kite is still
alive guys. Kite got reborn and we know
Kite was a major factor in the chapter
1. So I tr truly believe seeing a moment
of Jing Kite and going to the dark
continent would be my favorite moment in
Hunt onto history. And I think chapter 1
would definitely make me hype because of
all the foundation it laid out. Now I do
want to say this. Seeing Jing's
flashback is going to be think make me
think of chapter one too. So Jing's
flashback is something that I really
want Toashi to give us. Please, Toashi,
give us the secrets of Hunt. At least
just spoil me, yo. Like, just spoil me.
I know we have 50 chapters, promise, but
just spoil me cuz I want to know. And
guys, if you like videos like this where
I highlight and analyze chapters of
Huntter, I might do every single chapter
in Hunter Hunter, but it I'll only do
that if it gets 1,000 likes. If this
video gets 1,000 likes, it shows that
you Hunt Hunter fans still want me to
analyze the entire series up until the
50 chapters come out. But if it doesn't
get 1,000 likes, I will not do that
because that was a lot of work to reread
Hunter Hunter. I've reread it and
rewatched it so many times, guys.