Hi you guys. Thank you for being here.
Thank you for pressing play and showing
up. [laughter]
I appreciate your guys's time. Um, thank
you for being here. And thank you guys.
[screaming]
Ruby says, "Hi." Um, thank you guys for
sending love to me, you know. Um, I'm
going through something personally and I
just appreciate you guys sending, you
know, healing vibes my way. Um, I'm
going something going through something
with my mouth right now.
Um, I'm going to go get this looked at
and have it taken care of. Um, I just
appreciate all the the healing vibes. I
really do. I saw it in the comments and
I really appreciate it. Thank you guys.
Um,
if you guys want to check out um, Otter
Spirit. There's two links in the
description for a discount. They sell
triple gradea gemstones um, ethically
sourced. Um, they give back to Mother
Gaia. They're a beautiful company,
beautiful intentions, a family-owned
business. Um, yeah, and they give a
portion of the proceeds. It goes back to
Otter Otter Sanctuary. So, I mean, if
you're looking to invest your money into
crystals, that's where to go. And if you
want a discount, there's two links in
the des in the description. Um, check
out 144 from the Stars Tarot. Um, that
is Soul Family to me. Um, he's amazing.
His whole family is amazing and they're
ve all very talented. Everybody, even
Odin, he's a guide. He's got Ian has
this little dog with him. His name is
Odin. And um just like Riri. It's He's a
guide. He's there. Hey. Hey. No, no, no,
no, no, no. Okay. I have an um a cat
here with me. His name is Charlie. He's
new to the family. Hi, Birdie. And um he
I don't know what happened with him, but
I found him and he was skinny and um
just it wasn't looking good. He was, you
know, this wasn't looking good. So, I'm
taking care of him as much as I can. Um,
I want to take him to the vet, but I'm
having a hard time getting to the vet
already. Like, I don't have a car, but I
did find out that there's something
called like you can you use Uber for
your pets. So, that's the um that's
where I'm going is I'm trying to go in
that lane. I'm going to use Uber to go
take them to the vet as soon as I can.
Um because it's not just him that needs
to go to the vet. I have other cats that
need to see a doctor ASAP. Um and
Twitter, you know, her leg. Uh, anyways,
I don't want to go there right now. It's
just All right, let's um get into the
message, you guys. Thank you for being
here. I appreciate you guys a lot. It's
okay, mama. All right, so
this message,
you could be from Sirius cuz we have
both star I mean both cards coming out
that are from the star system named
Sirius. Okay, so what we have at the
bottom of the deck is good intentions.
And then what flipped out was saving
humanity. And you know what behind that
I have to say graduation. And this is
perfect because
so Sirius was um is a star system that
back in the day they had the best
intentions, you know, to save humanity,
to help humanity in some way. But what
happened is they got very obsessed with
it. Um
and now you know they're realizing that
um the way to save humanity is to become
that example. You can't save anybody but
you can become the example that people
can look up to or become that lighthouse
for people is what I'm saying. And I'm
this is the vibe I'm getting from you.
This is the message coming through for
you today. There's something here about
you having the best intentions in the
world to save humanity or I'm getting
here someone wanting to save a family
member. Okay, in specific or wanting to
save your family in general.
So um
right now you are graduating okay and
this is what's happening. You are
realizing that I cannot save anybody. I
can only become that example and this is
what you've done. I'm talking to someone
who you have put the world of sorry the
weight of the world on your shoulders
wanting to save everyone okay you have
the best intentions to do so but the
there was a problem here it was like God
had to show you like you can't save
anyone but you can become that example
that people can look to okay and that's
what you're doing I'm talking to someone
who's doing this okay um you're going
through an activation right
Wow. And behind that we have activated
earth too.
Mother Gia has been helping to activate
you. Okay. I'm talking to someone who
gets activated through mother Gia.
Whether you watch things online about
animals or you watch things about um the
earth or something um or whether you do
this out in the physical, you know. Um
either way, you get activated through
mother Gia. Okay. Whether I don't know
if you're listening to frequencies or
whatnot. I don't know. But you have been
activated.
Your light body has been activated.
Okay? And this is what you're doing. You
you have been devoted
to saving people, but now you're devoted
to saving yourself and becoming that
example, making your life a moving
prayer. That's what's happening here.
This is how you're saving humanity. um
is realizing that you're not able to
save humanity. Um but you can be that
example and by being that example you
are saving humanity. Do you see what I'm
saying? Um okay.
So make your life a moving prayer and we
have prayer coming out here. Um but what
I want to talk about first is this.
Okay. You are in perfect harmony right
now for something to come in or to move
forward in some way. there is something
that you've been wishing on or wishing
for. Um,
and I do feel that it's like you pray
for people. You you want the best for
people. You really want to help others.
You have the best intentions. Mary
motive.
You have the best intentions with
everything you do. I'm talking to
someone. You have beautiful intentions.
Um,
okay.
prayer.
I spread peace. This is how you are
saving humanity. You're becoming a
moving prayer. You're making your life a
moving prayer.
And this is what is healing your
connections.
You guys, for someone in specific, I
just have to say really quick, okay?
This could be your family or a family
member that you have been wanting to
help
and it's been hard for you to move
forward because you see yourself
transforming and you you're just you
just want to help them as well. And I'm
talking to someone who has let go.
You've let go of the res here and you
just became the example and by doing
this you are saving your family.
Okay, that's for someone in specific.
For others of you, this is humanity in
general. Okay, we do have family tree
though. Okay, we have family tree coming
out. This is expansion. This is legacy.
[clears throat]
And then we have emotional desert coming
out here for you.
And I'm getting that you could have had
to pull back your emotions from your
family in specific or whoever you're
wanting to save here. It's like you had
to cut your emotions out of it and leave
your emotions out of it and just become
that and just become that example. And
by doing this, like I said, you're
moving forward here. The old has
crumbled. We have the tower. It's over.
You're moving forward now with the eight
of wands. Okay. And again with the this
making a wish. There you are. There's
something coming in here that you wished
for as a child that you're seeing come
to fruition now.
Wow. And again, look at this. It's
because you let something go.
someone here. It's like you've released
the outcome of a prayer or of wish um of
how something you it's like something
you wanted to see something come to
fruition and you've released the outcome
of this of how it's going to happen.
You're like, I don't know how it's going
to happen, but I don't I just know it's
going to happen. And you've released it.
This is why. Okay, so you've released
it. This is why prosperity is about to
begin for you. Okay. Um look at that. I
mean, as a child, you were wishing for
something, and now you're going to see
it come true.
Very cool. Spirit wants you to know that
you have safe paths. Oh my god.
It's because you shed something here.
There's a wish coming true. Okay, we
have wish again. Wish, wish, wish,
prayer. You have safe passage here.
Okay. And then we have the word yes.
So
[snorts] yes, you have safe passage.
Thanks, Ruby.
Yes, you have safe passage.
Yes, you have magical hands for someone.
That's interesting. Okay. Yes, you have
magical hands. There's something in your
hands. Have you been wondering that?
Yes, you're right. There's some kind of
energy coming out of your hands. That's
for someone specific.
But if you've been wondering, is it okay
to move on? It's is it okay to move
forward? The answer is yes. And it's
time to move forward.
Yes, there's some kind of wish coming in
here. Yes.
Yes. There's an answer to your prayer.
I want to get one of these.
So it's after a time of having to
be alone for a while and figure this out
and realize I can't save anybody but I
can save myself and become that example
for everyone around me. And by doing
that you are saving everyone.
And again not one person can save
humanity but you if you become that
example you invite others to join the
fight with you and then together you
will save humanity. It you this is how
it happens. I mean and this is how it is
happening. This is beautiful. So you're
making your life a moving prayer here.
>> [screaming]
>> Okay, Riri.
[laughter]
Okay, can you get one of these spirit?
That's way too many. You know what came
out was patience. It's almost like
spirit's like, "Be patient." [laughter]
So, do you see what I'm saying real
quick before I look at this card? I was
wanting a card when I wanted it, right?
It's not on my time, it's on spirit's
time. And then the card that came out
real quick was way too many cards. I
wasn't going to take it. But on the top,
it said patience. Okay, that's a message
in itself. We can't receive things when
we want it. Spirit knows, God knows, the
universe knows when we're ready for it.
And you're ready for something because
you have released the outcome. You have
released how it's going to come to you,
when it's going to come to you, what
it's going to look like. You released
all of that. So, it's coming.
change. Ooh, the dragonfly spirit. You
could be seeing dragonflies.
Beautiful. And then we have air spirit
knowledge. This is your mind that we're
talking about. This is what you've had
to change is the way you think.
And that, you know, we've been getting
the bear spirit a lot lately. Okay. Bear
is coming out again. That has been um
around you lately.
Um, and that this bear spirit, I just
want to say really quick, has been
helping you regain your personal power.
So, the dragonfly spirit is here to say
there is some change coming. There is a
change that is here. Not coming. It's
here.
It's here.
There's something about your reflection.
Uh, sorry, the cat's cleaning himself
right here.
H, yeah, it's your thinking. Okay. Air
spirit knowledge. There's some kind of
like um
the way you think is different. This is
what's happening. Okay. It's the way you
think.
It's your mental body. You are thinking
totally different. Like I said, you're
letting go of the outcome here. Okay?
You're releasing it. You don't care. You
know, that's God's job. It's not your
job to figure out the how, the where,
the when, the why, all that. You just
know um to become it. You are it. You
are the blessing. You are the prayer.
There's some kind of fairies around you
right now. There's a fairy in the
corner. Look at that. It's like you can
barely see her, but she's there.
There's a fairy around you that you
don't know about. You don't see them.
You don't know about this fairy, but
they're around you. And they're helping
you with this change.
They're helping you with this change.
They're helping you shift your mindset
here. You guys, you do have a fairy
around you.
Very cool. I love that.
So, what I want to do now is we're just
going to get
Let's get some um tarot. Yeah,
I want to get an angel real quick
though. I Yeah, I do. I want to get an
angel real quick and just see what
angel. Okay. Uh Charlie, no babe.
Sorry, guys.
Lay down, baby. Okay, Riri,
be nice to her, right?
Okay.
What angels around them? Spirit,
you have two. Three, really? Okay. the
two that came out. Wow,
you guys. You have a um
um
someone here. You have a relationship or
a tie, a connection to Egypt. We have
Rah Rada coming out with soul flame. We
have Isis coming out magic manifesting.
Bottom of the deck we have Krishna with
devotion and we have Jesus.
I mean I've heard people say the the
relation the Krishna and Jesus are very
similar.
It says trust your spiritual guidance.
Your commitment has been recognized.
Devotion you guys. Devotion. [screaming]
Back up, Rever. You're too close. Sorry,
guys. Um, devotion. Your devotion has
been recognized. Um, you guys have
devotion. You have good intentions.
Saving your devotion has been
recognized. Spirit sees and Jesus sees,
Krishna sees how you love humanity and
how you want to help people so much.
Your devotion, you've been devoted to
this. Um, this is why. Okay. But here we
go. It says, "Experience relationship
harmony and healing.
Sacred connections." It says, "I nourish
my relationships with respect."
You guys, I'm so sorry. And I am not
starting this video over again.
No way. Sorry, guys, but you should have
seen what just happened. So, Riri got
too close to Charlie, and I've been
telling him that to back up, and he
won't listen. Finally, Charlie reached
out and went like that to Riri and Riri
jumped back and knocked over the camera.
That's what happened. Um, sorry guys,
but I'm leaving this in. I'm not going
to start this video over. Uh,
there's a reason why it happened. Um,
I feel like, um,
give me a second.
Someone could be um interfering with
something
that you're trying to do and it's almost
like you've been telling them to back
up. Leave me alone.
And I feel like someone just um
it's like you had to assert
assert your power
or show your strength in some way and
tell someone to back the up.
That's for someone specific that
happened for a reason. It'll resonate
with someone. It's almost like you've
been telling someone like, "Back up.
Back up. I don't want to hurt you. I
don't want to go there." But then
someone pushed you so hard to where
you're like, "Okay,
I guess I have to I guess I have to
stand up for myself." And spirit's been
waiting for that as well, for you to
stand up for yourself.
That was so crazy. Where was I? I don't
even um
your devotion has been recognized. Okay.
You have good intentions of saving
everyone. You had to save yourself first
and you had to realize to just become
the example that how do they say be
become the change you want to see in the
world. This is what you're doing. Okay.
Um so you have Isis and Rada coming out
here.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. This is what I was
saying. It says redis rediscover a lost
part of yourself. And then is then it
says experience relationship harmony and
healing. And this is what's happening.
Okay. You are healing your
relationships. And this is happening
because you've healed yourself.
All right. So there is some kind of
magic manifesting with Isis. It says
your dreams, visions, and goals are
becoming a reality. Stay focused.
Your devotion is being recognized and
it's being rewarded here you guys with
this some kind of magic coming in.
You're manifesting something with we
have wish over here. Um we have prayer
over here and then we have wish over
here. Okay. And then over here it looks
like she's wishing on a star. There's
some kind of wish coming in that you are
manifesting.
And we have devotion a couple a couple
times too. Okay. It's your devotion to
this.
Okay. So we know we have Isis Rada
um and Krishna. And then Jesus popped
out from the back of that the back of
Krishna. Jesus was right behind Krishna.
[laughter]
Why do I feel this is like significant?
But I can't tap into the message. I
don't know what that is. But I feel like
this there's a message from Jesus and
Krishna and I don't know what that is.
Like Jesus says though on that card it
says it talks about forgiveness and it's
like you've had to either forgive
yourself or forgive someone else.
And this is how you're saving them.
It's by letting it go. Someone here
really wanted to save their family from
something. I feel like and you've
learned that just by letting it go
and becoming
becoming that energy that you would like
to see in them.
This is what's doing it.
All right. [laughter]
So, let's get a message here. Someone
just pulled up in my driveway. I have no
idea who this is. All
right.
[cough]
I swear if I could just stay in my
Hermit cave forever, I would. Trust me.
[laughter]
Okay. What do we got? Oh, shut the You
have the star coming out, you guys.
There's a wish coming true. There's no
doubt in my freaking mind with Ace of
Wands at the bottom. Sorry, you can
hardly see that, huh? Um, Ace of Wands
at the bottom with the Star. You take
You're taking action on some kind of
wish here. You're wishing upon a star.
This is so crazy. There's a wish coming
true here.
And you guys, I just have to show you.
There's like the star. There's the earth
right here in the middle with with like
the star all around it. It's like you
wanted to save humanity or you wanted to
save people and you're going to be able
to do this and it's because you're
becoming that that example yourself.
This is like a wish come true of you
wanting to heal people or something.
H.
[laughter]
So interesting.
So so interesting. Okay, [laughter]
focus.
>> [laughter]
>> Okay. So, you're taking action on some
kind of
you've taken action on some kind of wish
fulfillment
by either praying about something.
You've been praying about something or
just having that intention.
And whatever this is, it's coming true.
It's going to be different for
everybody, whatever this wish is. Um,
but it's coming true. It's something
that you've been wanting.
and you've been devoted to changing your
life, changing who you are, changing
everything about yourself. And I don't
mean the stuff that you know, I'm
saying. You know what I'm saying?
Alchemizing, not changing. Alchemizing.
Hi, baby. Hey, what are you guys doing?
Sorry, guys. The cars just went
everywhere. Um, Charlie, what is wrong
with you? You just got up and freaked
out.
What's wrong? [laughter]
That's Shiva. Shiva's nice.
Okay, spirit. Any more cards here? I
mean, this is interesting. The Star and
Ace of Wands. It's like nothing else
wants to come out, [laughter]
you guys. Come on.
Why am I not getting another card?
[laughter]
Hm.
This is very interesting.
I don't think we need another card.
[laughter]
This has never happened before and I
have to go with it. I don't think we
need another card. The star is the only
card that's coming out right now.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm not going to press it, but one came
out. 10 of swords.
Like I said, it was your mental body.
It's your mental body that you have just
released some kind of something, some
kind of um mental conflict that you were
having about saving humanity or saving
someone in your family. And you've
released it with the T of swords. You
put it to bed.
Queen of Wands at the bottom. You
are becoming in touch. You're
manifesting.
This is I feel like um this goes with
the Isis card. Really? It's like you're
manifesting something. Someone here you
could be working with Isis um to
manifest something.
What's up with that?
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. You have
been stabbed in the back a lot. You have
been um so much so much you've been your
mental body has been attacked. Um and it
really affected your confidence here,
okay, with the Queen of Wands. But
because you have put this to bed, I'm
feeling someone you're going through a
glow up, you guys. There's something
here about um your confidence coming
back, your inspiration coming back, your
creativity coming back, um some kind of
manifestation, power coming back to you,
your confidence. It's like you're ready.
You're I could be talking. What is going
on today? I mean, for real,
I'm having a little um trouble.
[laughter]
Let's try that again.
Here we go. Yeah.
Wow. You had to decide. Two of swords.
Okay. To go through this death and
rebirth.
It was vital is what I'm hearing. You
had to let this go. This two of swords
with the 10 of swords. You had to let
this go because this was seriously
breaking your heart.
This was making you
stuck. It's like it was too much. You
were putting too much weight on your
shoulders is what I'm hearing you guys.
Wanting to save everyone
and you don't have to do that. Okay. So,
you've learned to make a decision to go
through this death and rebirth here.
[laughter] And now with the star,
there's some kind of wish coming true.
Okay.
Anything else, spirit?
Yeah.
>> Yeah. Wow, you guys.
>> Jesus. Okay, so you have let something
go with the three of wands at the
bottom. Okay. The seven of what you let
go of was the seven of swords. Something
that was just mentally entrapping you
like it was making you feel these were
this was false information making you
feel like you had to save the world. You
were, like I said, you put too much
weight on your shoulders, too much
pressure. Two of wands. There you are
choosing a different energy to be in.
Not the seven of swords anymore. You're
I'm not going to use these because you
can't see them. Huh. Um you're choosing
a different path here. Um uh than the
seven of swords.
Three of wands right on the bottom. So
you've let this go and you're waiting
for the new to come in.
And what's coming in is some kind of
wish fulfillment. Um we'll get one more.
[laughter]
It's okay, Charlie. [cough]
That's so interesting though. The star
right off the bat.
Boom. Here we go. Page of cups. Okay. At
the bottom, dreaming, wishing.
There's something you've been dreaming
about.
It's coming true. 10 of cups.
Whatever is coming in here, whatever
wish is coming in here, it's going to
make you feel extremely fulfilled.
And I will leave it there.
You're manifesting some kind of magic
here. Okay?
You've learned to let something go. And
this was
feeling like you had to save people.
Okay? And you have become some kind of
beautiful example here. And you are
making your life a moving prayer. Now
this is the message. And because of
that, you are saving people by being
that example for people. You're this is
how you're saving everyone. And it's not
that you're saving everyone. You're
learning how to save yourself and become
that example. But by doing that, it's
like you're inviting others to join this
fight with you. And together you will
save humanity. That's what I'm getting.
Okay. What I want to do really quick
before you go, you guys. Um Oh my god.
Twitter.
Oh god.
How did that happen, you guys? I turned
my back for what, 20 minutes?
>> Yeah, you did that, didn't you? That's
all right. It's okay. I will clean it
up.
Oh, you guys. Twitter
Twitter's having a dust bath, but she's
doing it
[laughter]
right next to everything that I have
here. And it's just it's got
It got dirt in there.
It's okay, Ri.
We're just going to get one.
I always say that, huh?
This is what it is. You put some worry
to bed. You put it this back into
balance. Okay. The twin flame is
balanced to me. Okay. And there's some
kind of worry that you've been worried I
I swear about the collective, about
saving people. This could be specific
family members or friends of yours that
you have been worried about saving and
you finally put it to bed and you put
things back into balance.
That's what it is. You were almost
obsessed with saving people. Okay? And
you're not anymore. You're learning that
I just can save myself and then become
that example for others. And in turn,
this is what you're doing is you are
saving people by doing this because like
I said, you're in you're inviting others
to join this fight with you. Um, and
together, boom. Okay. We can't do
anything by ourselves.
And people have to make a choice to live
for themselves as well. So, I think
you're learning that. My hair is crazy.
I don't care right now. Um, thank you
guys for accepting me exactly how I am
and not judging me. I really appreciate
that the most, you guys, because I have
a low self-esteem and it helps me to
know that I have people like you guys
that don't give a about that stuff.
They just want to hear the message and I
appreciate that a lot because it makes
me feel so much better. It really does
cuz then I don't have to come on here
and worry about physical stuff so much.
You know what I mean? which I'm learning
to yes to take care of myself but not to
overdo it, not to be so worried about
how I look and um stuff like this, you
know.
All right, that's just a side note.
Okay, so for um yeah, for some of you
guys, this is family members that you've
been trying to save and you're learning
that I can just be the example for them,
but by doing that, you are saving your
family by doing that. For others of you,
this is humanity on a bigger scale
wanting to save the world and putting
way too much pressure on yourself. And
you're learning that, hey, I can just be
the example and send an invitation to
others. That's all I can do. And by
doing this, you are saving people. Okay,
this is the message. Um, I'll see you in
the next one. Please let me know how
this resonated if you feel like. You
don't have to. Um, I'll see you in the
next one. No worries. Okay, love you.