Hello. Hello.
All right. Welcome.
So, what we wanted to share right now is
actually
maybe more personal. I wanted to share
something with you
and and that is that we
when I say we I don't mean to sound
weird
but
it is how we've come to understand this
human body
because we have come to to comprehend
this human body much different than what
most people think.
And
this whole system
is
is very different than what most people
think too. And so
they haven't fully learned how it is to
truly truly operate their human being
correctly.
And when we say correctly, what we mean
is not some egoic uh snobbery or
something like that,
but it's more to do with
being an energetically
being in an an energet energetic correct
frequency within your own system.
And that's not something that many
beings are operating in. We are
operating like that more and more now.
We are sort of messing up less and less
and
we are starting to function quite well
in that way too and not just think that
we're crazy type of thing.
But the to have multiple sensory
experiences where you you know that you
have access to different consciousness.
That is actually a quite a big thing to
realize
and we believe that most beings are and
have capability of that and that can be
trained. In fact, that is what we are we
are training people to get there. There
is a link in the bio if you're
interested in that. And so that training
is taking you and changing your
consciousness in order to think more
like an ascended master is what we we're
saying. But it is to think in close
vicinity to energetic truth.
That is the main
uh part of this message is this
energetic truth because that is how you
are connecting to the and and what what
is energetic truth?
It is the truth of energy and it's the
truth of the body. Most beings are going
around pretending fantasy realities
between maybe even large groups of
people so it seems real, right? That's
what you get in cities. You get people
behaving in a certain way and in certain
sort of communities you get people
behaving in a certain way or countries,
right?
And so
when you are operating and these
teachings go against uh not against um
these go by the way what we're doing
here we are channeling we are channeling
higher intelligence but we're also
making sense of it with you and for you
so that you can comprehend your own
energy
because your own energy is the most
precious that you have.
It is your commodity really
is your energy in essence.
And that's something to realize and to
really get on a subtomic
particle level so that you're truly
ingraining that into your body. And we
have a lot of hair remedies for that.
And that's also linked in the bio in the
description. And those are more
vibratory. They are working on the
vibratory field. Some of these
corrections are working on the mind
aspect to correct certain things that
then become in alignment with energetic
truth and certain things. The HYA
sessions they the HYA remedies sorry
they they were called sessions before
but now they're called HA remedies. They
are
remedies, frequency remedies, ch
channelneled frequency remedies for the
body, for the human electromag magnetic
field for certain situations and certain
energy corrections and those can be
frequency
attuned as well. And that is something
that you can get from these HYA
remedies. And you once you if your
intuition is in tuned, you can go on the
store and you can sort of feel for what
is actually calling you and you will
notice certain ones will light up for
you. That is Gaia. Gaia speaks to you
like that in order to figure out what
you actually need and what your body
need to calibrate right now to this
holistic perspective.
And so the energetic truth once you are
connecting
the once you are seeing the world
correctly with the energetic truth and
that you're correcting your perspective
to be in sync with your own body. By the
way, it's not something that we say but
with your own body. Once you are in sync
with your own body, then
your body, you will start to have a
really deep connection with your body, a
much deeper connection that you might
realize because what many beings are
doing is that they're usually projecting
onto other beings. But once you get
really good at this consciousness
shifting game, you will start to retract
a lot of these projections that you have
given other things and other beings so
that you start to become self-contained
energy and so that your energy is for
you to birth creations. If that's what
you want, that is something that you can
do now.
And so once you if you want let's say
your intuitive abilities it is a
requirement you need to change these
energies so that you are self-contained.
You have to do that because unless you
do that you are not connecting the right
energies for that alignment
of frequency calibration and your
inunement to flow properly. You see? So
it needs that correction in order for
the energy to flow properly through the
body. That's really all there is to it.
The mind may seem like it is complex. It
is not complex. But the mind needs to
sort of some minds needs to be sort of
retrained. We have had to go a complete
retraining in order to think in the
correct way sort of. And we're saying
correct because we're saying it needs to
be in sync with your body. It's not
something that we say. It's not
something that you need to adhere to.
It's for your own benefit. Because once
you align with your own body and you
properly sync up and you manage to get
all of these energies right, you light
up like a battery. And when you get to
heal past all of these projections that
you have comingled yourself with other
beings and you fully
take everything back,
you are like a self-containing
organism
and you get to have your energy at your
disposal.
And only then can you truly start your
life
because then you will have your energy
for you.
And then you get to do your life which
is when your life gets exciting because
you are making your life
a reality. Your dream life. That's what
it's about.
That's when everything start to happen.
When you start to feel joy again. When
your life starts to blossom again. When
all of these energies just light up your
whole human energy field
and you are fully self-containing
organism, fully connected to the cosmos
and fully rooted to Gaia in full harmony
between the two.
That is what we're inviting you for
here. We love you so much and we want to
say thank you so much for being here.
Let us know in the comments how are you
in frequency. Where are you? Where are
you getting stuck? Where is your I can't
seem to get past this thing. Let us know
and we can help you. We love you so much
and we'll talk to you again in the next
one. Ciao. Ciao for now.