Jujutsu Kaizen sequel has dropped banger
after banger as chapter 17 reveals Ra's
return and Surigi looking more insane
than ever. But that's not all. More
Yujiadori hype has been dropped. We see
him speaking to UT's son and we
literally outright are told he's on
another level of strength. But Gay
doesn't stop cooking because the law we
learn about jiujitsu society, it's
totally messed up. FP. Everyone in this
world carries a curse on their shoulders
and dies with regrets. Chapter 17 opens
up with laying that all down about UT's
own family. Uta and Mari smashed with
their son Iori being born in 2031. He is
a spitting image of Uta and ended up
marrying a woman named Muyu. Muyu is the
same woman that appears in chapter 1,
who told Yuka at age 10 that she can't
have Ra's ring despite Yuta wishing for
her to have it. Instead, giving it to
Surrii, telling him what he wants is
irrelevant. Muyu married into the Gojo
and Zenin family, following their
decisions on who is best suited to
inherit Ra's power. This set the seed
for Sudigi's motivation to become strong
to prove the clans's wrong that he
doesn't need it. Now, a lot of us were
angry that she's an idiot. But with
chapter 17, we understand a lot more
because Muyu was left alone with Sudigi
and Yuka as their father left them as
soon as she was born. As a result, this
explains why our MC's cling so hard to
their grandparents and want to be like
them. As they admit in chapter 2, Margi
and Uta had to step in to give them a
real childhood and train them, filling
the void their father left behind. But
why exactly did Iori leave? Well,
chapter 17 reveals that Sudigi was
curious to know as well. He wanted to
know what kind of person his father was.
Uta and Mari avoided the subject, but he
secretly went around asking members of
the Gojo clan. Iori was a serious and
diligent person, but that backfired. He
was chasing a standard he could never
reach. Bro was basically a power scaler
and he dived so deep into it, he said,
"Oh [ __ ] wait a second. We're weak as
hell and our generation is cooked. None
of us are special grades." So compared
to the generation before him, he felt
weak. How could they live up to legends
like his parents, Yugji, or even Saturo?
And then his power scaling didn't stop.
When compared to the sorcerers beneath
him and under his wing, he felt
responsible. Sorcerers are only getting
weaker, which is widening the problem
against stronger curses. What if another
sukuna appears and they can't deal with
it? And that pressure turned him into a
man who started breaking down mentally.
But before he became a deadbe and left
the sorcerer world behind, he met Yuji
Itodori. Iori was lashing out at Yugji
about his problem, but our goat said it
doesn't matter. This leads to
speculation from Surigi that his father
leaving after Yuka's birth must have
something to do with power as Surigi was
heavily restricted. But Yuka was somehow
born with the 10 shadows. However, he
ponders this huge question. Why didn't
he just leave after his birth? It must
have something to do with the presence
or absence of techniques within them.
Surigi believed that his father must
have felt his role as a sorcerer was
complete. But the argument with Yuji,
well, it goes a lot deeper. For
instance, what if Iori tampered with
Yuka and is actually the cause of her
brain cancer? We know in the sequel,
Mahito still exists and appeared in
chapter 7. He's waiting on the other
side for Yugji, or from what we can
tell, someone in particular. Mahito
prays on human insecurities to
accommodate his goals to the point where
his victims go against any common sense.
But you may be wondering how can Mahito
even be contacted. Well, there is an
area where he resides. Even Kenjaku
showcased this before the culling game a
rift between reality and dreams where he
contacted players. Similarly, Mahito did
the same thing in chapter 271. Mahito
meets Sukuna after his passing and tells
him due to his innate ability, he
resides himself within the samsara
cycle. He's in the pathway where souls
walk. And this means everyone who dies
or comes to life can interact with him.
I mean, even Yuka mentioned the cycle of
rebirth before facing Darra, connecting
the plot even more. Now, Mahito's
technique, it could have unlocked the 10
shadows in Yuka. After all, Sukuna
revealed that cursed techniques reside
in the preffrontal cortex in the brain
against Gojo. So, if I truly believe
that the next generation needed to be
stronger at any cost, it's not hard to
imagine him searching for a solution for
his children's defect that would be in
his eyes. Yuka's brain damage could be
the result of her father doing a binding
vow by making a deal with the devil
himself to get what he wanted.
Especially when you look at chapter 6,
there is no solution for Yuka's cancer.
No understanding of what's going on, and
they haven't even heard of this illness
before. And that could be because Mahito
affected the soul, which makes sense of
everything. Remember that Kenjaku used
idol transfiguration on a massive scale
to start the culling game. He targeted
people who already had dormant curse
techniques, but lacked the brain
structure to use jiu-jitsu. He literally
rewired their brains so their techniques
could awaken, such as Higuruma. And in
the end, I's argument with Yugji and him
saying it doesn't matter. It could be
our boy telling him what he thinks is
wrong. And his children being the way
they are shouldn't matter to him.
Because Yuji once said to Sukuna, after
all, we were born with the burden of a
curse. Even if no one else accepts it,
he's willing to go on living with him.
So I's role should be to nurture his
kids with what was given rather than
pushing an ideal onto them by force. And
guess what people, this makes perfect
sense. And the writing is amazing
because this generational trauma
connects to Maru. Well, let's not forget
that he's an inverse of Surigi's
situation. And that's Gay's way of
showing how curses come in all forms.
Maru's curse is having a present father
who left him religious ideals that haunt
him with an obsession while Sudigis is
having an absent father who left him
with scars and curiosity. So people are
missing the point with Maru's ideal to
be a warrior. It makes way more sense
when you see what the culture drilled
into him because on their planet
Lumerian women can't wield cursed energy
so their men have to be warriors by
default. Their jiujutsu is literally
framed as a gift from the gods. And real
men protect women and children because
they can't bear the burden. So Maru is
trying to be worthy of a holy title his
whole society worships. That's why he
can't back down on Sugiri's challenge
and he's not going to give up on the
50,000 refugees on the ship. But let's
not forget Yugji is slowly becoming the
only answer to all the problems. Yuka is
already in a state of suspended death.
The ritual would not end unless Darra is
killed or Maharaga is destroyed. If
either of those things happened, Yuka's
death is guaranteed. This parallels what
happened to Megumi in chapter 117. But
Sukuna used RCT to save him. However,
that's not the only time we have seen
someone be saved from death. It happened
to Yugji twice. First, when Sukuna
ripped his heart out and then revived
him, and later when UT killed him and
used RCT to bring him back. All of this
links to a huge plot point fans believe
will happen. Yugji is going to save the
day by helping Yuka live and taking on
Darura or Mahuraga, depending on the
outcome. This would parallel Sukuna's
fuga moment perfectly, as Yuji would
form a height moment and aura by
displaying his new powers immediately
upon arrival. I still believe that
Maru's harmony technique can also come
into play to locate Yugji because
Sukuna's finger is still holding up a
barrier and that can be used to resonate
with his essence to find Yugji anywhere
in the world to help humanity. That
would fit the writing of his character
development to believe in coexistence
and peace again. putting aside his
obsession and curse to be a warrior.
Like, bro, I'm going to crash out if
Yuji got hyped this much and doesn't
appear once in this sequel. Gay
literally drew how prime Yuji looks
like. And it's it's depressing. Look at
his eyes. He's looking around 20 years
old and more like his uncle Sukuna. Give
him a break. Give him a hypora moment.
You know what I'm saying? And at this
point, Yuji understands something most
sorcerers never will. The world is in a
balance. When Gojo was born, the world
responded by creating stronger special
grade curses, right? And when Sukuna
rose, humanity was forced to produce
monsters of its own just to survive
where they all became special grade. So
when Yuji says it doesn't matter how
strong sorcerers are, he's implying that
chasing strength is meaningless because
the jiu-jitsu system will always find a
way to correct itself. The wheel will
never stop turning. And that's why in
the sequel, I think Yuji wants to break
it. He's searching for a plan to
eliminate curse energy altogether. Just
like Yuki was researching in the
original manga, she believed the only
way to end curses was by eliminating its
source. She identified that curse energy
is produced by humans through negative
emotions, right? Which means killing
curses is only a temporary fix because
new ones will always be born. And Yuji
has been witnessing this for six bloody
decades. This also ties directly into
Yuji's own problem of being immortal.
Yugji wants to die and he wants a good
death surrounded by friends without
regrets. And to do that, he needs to
break the wheel with the others just
like Yuka and Cross promised to each
other and bloody mention. Chapter 17
then picks up the fight between friends
immediately. Maru's technique of chaos
and order disrupting physics has Surigi
on the back burner. He doesn't
understand the technique yet and almost
falls off a building. He can't even get
close. Maru then immediately jumps in to
stab and is launching him all over the
building like a play toy. But eventually
he figures out a counter and makes both
of them lose their swords. But as they
race to pick them up, they clash once
again. However, Sugiri's sword is caught
between Maru's blade, trapping him
inside using his physical strength
against him. With that, he busts him
outside and they have a chat midair
before the final blow. Sugiri thinks to
himself that he might have won. And even
if there was a 1% chance that Yuka can
be saved, then he would always bet on
that just like Maru would for his own
cause. Now this beautifully connects to
another plot point from the original
manga that you cannot forget. Remember
that Kjaku stated life is a gamble and
people who do not take a step in action
whilst looking at death in front of
their eyes they are absolutely
detestable. Even Hakari believe that
everyone in life gamles on something.
This is their fever of trying to change
things in some way. But the true manner
of dealing with this fever is by
gambling. He thinks that society
tramples on people who can't bet big
enough, meaning people who can't take
chances to progress their goal. This is
something even Gojo mentioned to Uta
whilst they were training, mentioning
the fever once again. So this is
something that we find Cross, Yuka, and
Sugiri doing, right? And it will tie
into how they will make Maru have a
change of heart to gamble on coexistence
once again since his ass is about to get
beaten into a pole. Because although
Sugiri gets completely destroyed,
multiple cars thrown at him, explosions,
a whole ass building collapsing and
dashed into the ground. If this dude was
any other human without heavenly
restriction, then he would have been
finished. Now, the look of despair on
Maru's face tells it all. Obviously, my
guy doesn't want his friend to suffer by
his hands, and he doesn't want to kill
him. But Maru's love for his brother and
his duty as a warrior supersedes
everything. However, Sugiri is not done.
He thinks about his father's ideology of
valuing strength and power. He accepts
that being born great and having a great
death is something to be proud of. But
he can't accept that way of thinking.
Like Yuji who told Sukuna how every life
and memory is precious. He thinks that
even if a person's life is ordinary and
vague. As long as their everyday
existence was out there, then that was
enough. This testament is a reference to
his father who saw himself as trash
became depressed and then disappeared.
Now at this moment, Uda's ring on his
neck starts glowing. Cursed energy
floods out. Sugiri thinks his grandpa is
here, but no, it's the queen of curses,
Ra. She disappointedly tells him how
takes after Maki, calling her that
woman, reminding us how Ra was obsessed
with UT and was jealous of Mari that she
ended up with him marrying, smashing,
all that good [ __ ] Now, I do want to
mention that this panel right here, oh
my god, hypeora moment. Absolutely fire.
[screaming]
Now eventually they form a contract and
because of Uther's requests and their
undying love, Ria was told to help the
progeny of his bloodline. So she does
just that and tells Sugiri to accept the
deal. And with one word, he becomes a
special grave. Just like we had
predicted, he has become one of the
strongest sorcerers to exist. Though he
doesn't have a full restriction like Oji
and Mari, his body is insanely strong.
And now with RA's immense curse energy
reserve, he has become completely
broken. Ra merges with his body, showing
us a new transformation we haven't seen.
And before Maru can blink twice and say
anything, questioning who this new
challenger is, Ra gives him a quick
write, sending the Samrian flying busted
all open. Now remember, one of R's
ability is curse technique storage. So
whatever UT probably copied is probably
still in there. So he has access to all
of that now too. And there's also the
cursed tool storage which has all these
special grade weapons sitting inside of
her. So he is completely busted and we
cannot even fathom what the hell is
going to happen next. Now everything is
adding up. Sugiri will defeat Mu now and
convince him that with RA now back they
can use RCT on cross and save it.
Remember, Ra was able to use positive
energy to heal UT. And in chapter 269,
it was absolutely an insane feat because
he explained how Ra was able to heal and
even sustain his dead ass body whilst
his brain wasn't in it. Now, currently,
the level of RCT the Jutsu sorcerers
have is weak. In the sequel, in chapter
13, the healer literally called herself
trash while she was trying to heal Usami
and Cross. But with Ra, things have now
changed. Not only can she heal Cross,
but even Yuka. Remember that this fight
is happening before Mahur Raga and
Darra, which means once this is over,
they will still have time to save her.
We can't forget that there's another
option for these people. The Samrians
can manage the Kalan in Tokyo and will
be allowed to reside there, which was an
option that they had. And with the
condition that no curse can leave the
vicinity, it's a win-win for both
parties. Ra is also a Kalano member.
according to them since she's a cursed
spirit. Imagine she kills another cursed
spirit in front of them. They're going
to be thinking, "Wait a second. Why is
Kalan killing Kalan?" And then they're
going to question their beliefs and
realize, "Wait a second, the humans were
telling the truth. This is something
else." Another point to make is that
Sugiri directly parallels Megumi, who
failed to save his own sister. These two
characters mirror each other, but their
outcomes diverge. Now, to enjoy more
Peak Fiction, watch this video about
Erin doing over eight time loops in
Attack on Titan.