Hello chosen ones. Welcome to the
channel. Today I have a message for some
of us that is pretty specific. So just
ask God about it. But the message is you
are the coldest chosen one. So it's
definitely specific because not all the
people who are in a relationship with
the Lord Jesus Christ who have like sold
their soul out to God to where they're
being used in the kingdom of God in big
ways. They're major players out here in
the spiritual warfare that's happening.
Not all of you guys are meant to be
cold. Not all of us are meant to have
this um specific part of our
personality. You know, it's it's it's
it's only for a specific group of the
chosen ones out here. And so, but the
message is that you are the coldest.
Okay? So, you have some kind of part of
your personality that is ice cold. it
is. Um, you might have been called cold
before. People might have told you like,
"Damn, you're cold." Or you might have
just had moments where you realized
like, "Damn, I'm cold." Or something
something is like kind of dead inside
with me or something's very cold, you
know. And um, you know, the ironic thing
is that for some of us, for most of us
who this is for, you were actually born
as like the most empathic. You were born
as like the most loving, most
compassionate, the most sensitive, the
most emotionally just um driven and and
open with your love and just very
compassionate and sensitive and
empathic. And you especially are very
compassionate toward animals and
children. And you were able to sense
very, you know, compassionate uh
empathic souls that were also out there
that you would feel all of this uh
strong sense of love for. But
something happened to where it was just
either ingrained in your personality for
you to just become colder and colder as
you grew up because of just the way that
your brain was built. And then for some
God had to let you go through
experiences that totally sh changed your
personality that completely transformed
you into somebody who is extremely cold.
And so there are a lot of reasons for
this, but one of them is that for some
you're supposed to go very very far in
this reality and to to deal with people
from a very high place. And you just
have to be extremely cold to be able to
make it in a high place like that. You
have to be able to deal with
sharks and like the worst of the worst
kind of people, the most brutal types of
coldest types of cold-blooded people
ever. So, you have to be able to um be
at the same level with these people. And
so God is saying that you have actually
come through a completion where you are
the coldest. You are colder than any
coldblooded
Mcavelian dark triad personality type
out here that uh you can be more
coldblooded than that person um than a
full than a full-blown like uh you know
Satanist or somebody who is um you know
even trying to be dead inside or trying
to be the coldest. You are naturally
colder than they are because of your
calling and because you have followed
God through whatever experiences that
you were meant to go through to become
this person and to have this gift. So
you have been given this gift of of
being able to be ice cold. It's almost
inhuman how cold you're able to be. You
can go through situations that other
that would terrify other people that
would make other people extremely
uncomfortable that they wouldn't be able
to handle it because you just have to be
so cold-blooded to get through that kind
of a situation. And because you are who
you are now that that God has changed
you, you are able to go into these
situations that other people wouldn't be
able to to get into. Okay. So, but God
is saying that, you know, um this is
part of what is going to bring you into
your destiny and it's a major part of
what you had to become in order to get
there. But that it doesn't make you any
less of a person who loves God. It
doesn't make you any less of God's child
because you are still that loving,
empathic, sensitive, compassionate
person on the inside and you still have
this heart that is so soft for certain
people. But um you you know are only
going to show that to innocent beings,
you know, to beings that are not evil
that deserve it and that this is a part
of God's calling for your life and that
you're meant to be this way. And some
people might try to demonize you for
being such a cold-blooded person
sometimes. And God is saying that when
that happens, you have to remember that
no, actually, this is God's gift to me
because he wanted me to be able to go
very far and to deal with the coldest of
the cold-blooded per people out here.
And this is my gift that God's given me
for survival. Okay. And I am just also
getting that, you know, some of some of
us might think that we're too cold to
ever be able to find a person who like
is a partner or to find that, you know,
spouse or whatever because we're just
too cold blooded. I got to say that he
has already set you up with somebody who
is just very similar as you to where you
guys are going to understand the
coldness of each other. It's uh going to
be something very very familiar
between the two of you, okay? Where
you're just going to have a very deep
understanding of why you are the way you
are and who you actually are on the
inside behind this mask of coldness.
So, but I'm going to go ahead and pull
some cards, but I'm just getting that,
you know, for some of us, you have come
through a major completion. I'm just
seeing the world that you have gone
through a major healing process. um
where years and years and years of you
experiencing the worst of the worst
kinds of situations with the worst of
the worst types of people has all come
together into this uh season of healing
where you have just um absorbed
everything and you've uh allowed God to
just filter everything through uh in in
in a way to where this coldness has been
purified and and and you just um you are
experienced on a whole another level.
Okay. So, I'm just getting that you are
now ready to be in any room with um any
type of person and you could be
surrounded by a whole bunch of sharks.
You could be surrounded by the most uh
terrifying like you know attorneys or
just I don't know the types of
personalities that are so intimidating.
Whereas before you might have just come
into a room like this and and you might
have felt like they get to call all the
shots like they get to make all the
decisions. they're higher than me,
they're better than me, you know,
they're just the these people are
cutthroat or whatever. But because you
are who you are now, you can go into
these types of rooms and know that no,
actually, I'm the coldest [ __ ] here.
Um, and it don't make me any less of a
chosen one that I am the most
cold-blooded [ __ ] here. And it don't
make me any less of a cold-blooded [ __ ]
because I have this facade or I have
this uh, you know, natural personality
of kindness and compassion and empathy.
And I might show that to you once in a
while, but that don't mean that um that
I ain't more cutthroat than you are or
that that uh that I'm scared of you in
any way because I am the coldest person
here. So, this is a gift that God has
given you that could only have been
received through your faithfulness in
following the Lord Jesus Christ beyond
church and beyond religious fear. Okay?
because you have stepped out into the
darkness where God really called you to
and you uh you did not listen to these
religious people who tried to stop you
and now you are the coldest [ __ ] out
here and you are going to uh to step
into rooms where your uh your gift of
coldness is going to save you. You will
be able to survive because of this.
Yeah, you are the coldest [ __ ] out
here. Okay, listen. They they don't they
don't see they don't see what's going on
behind your facade because some of you
just have the cutest facade. Okay. But
uh you've actually you've come up
against the devil himself. The devil
himself has uh tried to to murder you.
Okay. The devil himself has been after
you trying to unalive you for so long
that you are uh you are
you are a beast. Okay. You are worse
than any kind of a dark triad
personality out here. You have dealt
with the worst kinds of personalities
out here. Some of you have dealt with
murderers and stalkers and psychopaths
and sociopaths and demonpossessed people
who were trying to unal alive you who
were doing meth all the time and
becoming possessed in regards to you.
You have dealt with the the like worst
of the worst out here. This is the worst
of the worst out here. See
this is uh this is trying to unalive
someone relentlessly because you are
demonpossessed. All right. And it turned
you into this cold uh into this ice cold
ice queen or king who uh with the king
of swords, okay? Who is just you are uh
I don't know how to say it, but but
ain't nobody getting nothing past you.
All right? And if they do, it's an
accident and and uh it's not going to
happen twice. I don't know how to
explain this, but uh yeah, you were
unimpressed. All right? You don't care
if somebody uh tries to intimidate you
or comes at you acting like they're cold
and that they can uh you know have that
that that they can do something to you.
You're like, "No, no, [ __ ] I I am not
interested. I've seen it all. I know
that um I'm colder than you. All right.
I know what's up. I can see beyond this
situation because I am really ice cold
and I am not phased by your coldness. I
am not phased at all." Okay? So, God has
made you unfazed by these types of uh of
of dark and evil personalities because
some of you are going to be dealing with
big bosses out here. These are big big
big bosses, big big corporations that
are filled with sharks.
All right? And you're going to be coming
in there with looking like new money.
All right? You're you're coming into
very highlevel positions. Some of us are
stepping into this right now and you are
going to be the new money. You're going
to be looking like you've got a whole
fruit basket on your head energetically
and you're going to be surrounded by
sharks who want to steal it. Um and and
these will be very strong people, all
right? With very big contracts and you
will be um you will be able to
absolutely know what it is. You're going
to know damn well who you are. You're
going to know that can't nobody take
anything from you. You're going to be
the coldest person and totally
unimpressed by any kinds of uh
intimidation
and uh you're not afraid to slow things
down and you're not afraid to uh to wait
and be patient. And God is just saying
that you have come to a completion of
your training. All right? And you're
ready and you're you're you're taking
off into these places. All right? And
you're going to be the coldest [ __ ]
there.
Even though you might also be the nicest
person there. Yeah. because you you uh
you kept getting up. You allowed God to
take you through experiences that tore
you open, that tore you apart, that
completely broke your heart into
billions of pieces, and you continued to
uh to follow God and to do what he said.
All right? And you got colder and colder
and colder,
okay? And and and smarter and smarter
and smarter and uh more block happy. You
uh you learned how to block people like
instantly. like you don't give a damn
about nobody's feelings. All right? If
if you catch the first sign of somebody
being an op, you don't give a damn about
their feelings anymore from that point
and you block them. All right? And um
yeah.
Oh my god. So this has just brought you
into the place of um
of major destiny of being able to
receive everything that is coming in
without uh without losing your head,
without losing your energy. um you are
just ready because it's about to go down
in a huge way and actually another thing
is that you know you're suddenly going
to be connected with with a spouse and
this is going to be someone who again
God has created for you. It's somebody
who is similar to you. They know your
coldness and they they understand
that that that isn't actually who you
are in your heart that that's who your
flesh is because you have to be this
person. But in your heart, they they're
going to know um they're going to know
who you are and you guys are going to
have like the most epic relationship
because of this. All right? It's going
to be a very deep intimate relationship
that only you guys understand each
other. All right? It's going to be very
much filled with joy and happiness and
brightness. All right? And this is going
to be a wish, a major wish come true.
But that, you know, this is also having
to do with your career because these
people are going to respect you because
of who you are, because of what you've
been through. because they're uh you
know they're going to see that,
you know, within the first within the
first few minutes of getting to know you
that you are this person that God has
has created you to be a very cold, a
very intelligent and uh a very unafraid
person. All right? And that's just going
to that that's going to suddenly get you
uh a massive amount of success. All
right?
Yeah.
So,
let me just pull a couple more cards and
see. I did uh have the sign of Leo and
Aries.
Yeah, but this is going to bring you so
much success. All of these betrayals and
everything that you've been through has
turned you into somebody who is able to
handle literally anything, the worst of
the worst kinds of pains or situations
or anything. And you are taking off now.
Uh you you you're about to find massive
success because of this.
Okay.
So yeah, this is why God has allowed you
to go through all these pains. Okay. So
I'm going to leave it there. I'm also
seeing Virgo and Gemini.
But um I hope this message helps. Chosen
ones. I love you guys so much. All
right. And uh
And God just wants you to know that you
you you know, you will shine. Your real
heart and your real soul is so beautiful
and so lit and it's just so intuitive
and compassionate and empathic. And God
is not going to have you live in this
coldness forever. He's going to give you
that person or that situation or that
private life or that place, that safe
place where you're with the the the
people or the the animals and the
children or a place where you can really
share your real light and that God is
saying your real light, your real heart
is so beautiful.
All right? and he gave you this
incredibly cold ego to survive, to be
able to harbor this beautiful energy
while while also surviving. Okay, so I'm
going to leave it there and uh I'll see
you guys in the next video. All right,
and thank you so much to anyone who's
donated and thank you for your comments.
And you guys can follow me on Instagram
if you want to, but I'll see you later
and God bless.