Angels, ancestors, wayshores, guides,
ascended masters, archangels, galactic
federation, council of light,
elementals, fay, Mary Magdalene, beings
assigned to our team for highest,
holies, heavenliest, most divine, godly
good, celestial guardians, protectors,
divine messengers, and all benevolent
beings of light. What do we need to know
about this wheel of fortune finish line?
What awaits you is phenomenal. Got your
enemies working overtime. Empress
peeking out right here with the two of
pentacles and the 10 of pentacles. Big
monetary means coming in. I feel I feel
like y'all are locked in. Y'all are
officially locked in to 2026.
Wheel of Fortune with wish fulfillment
and everything that comes with it. What
is up, Galactic Golden? How y'all doing?
How y'all feeling? What's the vibe?
Welcome in. Welcome in. Welcome in. I
missed y'all. I took a little mini
vacation, but it's so good to be back.
Hello, family. And listen, whatever's
coming in for you, which again, Wheel of
Fortune energy, nine of cups, wish
fulfillment with the T of Pentacles,
it's big. It's phenomenal. It's
supernatural. And it's got your enemies
working overtime.
While you're over here locked in on what
is unfolding before you, you got your
enemies locked in uh to directing you
the chaos that they're experiencing. I
also feel like if you are in a union, if
you are in a relationship, whether this
is new or this is long-standing, just
know that your enemies are directing a
lot of chaos towards you. So, whatever
is occurring in your physical reality
pertaining to you individually or your
partnership, uh ground ground balance.
You may even want to do some like
protection work uh or say your psalms
over you yourself, your babies, your fur
babies, your home or your counterpart.
fast movement forward with the T of
pentacles coming out here cuz you do
have a ace of pentacles behind that
because you do have individuals
directing chaos towards you and your
partnerships. Uh you could even be
experiencing some aggravation or
irritation in friendships. Now there are
some cut offs that are being made before
2026. The divine will reveal to you who
can go with you and who must be left
behind. Hello hello hello.
Welcome in galactic golden family. What
is going on here?
Lock in as well. I I mean it. Lock in
because you've got major things coming
in and it requires you to focus and
remain focused on your highest
vibrational future, your highest
vibrational fate. Cuz you got
individuals, looks like we do have
hermit energy out here that were making
offerings in order to cause upheavalss
in your reality that could only align if
you allowed them to. So again, anything
that is meant to cause disturbance or
disruption,
uh, take it as like a grain of salt. Do
not
Yep. Look, you got a harvest ahead of
you. A har They said not ahead of you.
You got a harvest, uh, here. A harvest
is here. You got a lot of pentacles
coming out, too. 10 of pentacles, seven
of pentacles, ace of pentacles. Now, one
of you incredible Galactic Golden Ohana
members was like, uh, instead of saying
as within, so without, because we are
never without, we are with all. Say, as
within, as is my external, as within, as
my external. And I love that. Thank you.
I really do appreciate you putting that
in the comments. And yes, I do read the
comments. Y'all are amazing. Uh, I'm
going to start saying that from now on.
as within, as is my external, as is my
reality.
Because we are never without. So yes, as
within, as my external, make sure you
are proclaiming that over your
experience and your relationships. You
are attracting in magnetically in this
time. All that of which that you are and
all that you have integrated which for
many of you if not all of you is years
upon years upon years or lifetimes upon
lifetimes upon lifetimes of currents
ofqi uh lower vibrational corrupted
darker energy that you have alchemized
into light prosperity unconditional
love. They said faded and highly
fortunate events. Oo spirit coming
through early.
And yes, we are here early. What is up,
galactic golden Ohana? We may be early
for the next few days. I feel like they
said and you have ascended ear. What? I
just heard you have ascended earlier
than anticipated. Get ready for the ball
that is now rolling. What is this ball
that is now rolling? Spirit, we got
three of swords. Your enem is left
heartbroken. Two of cups because you're
in a dynamic or you're about to be.
Emperor and death.
So, some of you are not in a union yet.
Some of you are about to be leaving
those that were working against your
connections heartbroken because this is
just the beginning for you. This lets me
know some of you are in a union right
now and there was work being done
against your union. This is only
deepening the bond. Some of you do have
a third party. You're not in a third
party. You have a third party. There's a
ex that just won't leave you the [ __ ]
alone. This ex could be a Scorpio, could
be an Aries, could be a Gemini, Libra,
Aquarius, or a Pisces, Cancer. Does not
have to be. Take what resonates, leave
what doesn't. But some of you, you do
have an ex out here. Uh, a counterfeit
counterpart. Could be a part of some
occult or organization that is
heartbroken because you never came back.
Whoever this is, their seat or I won't
say their seat has been taken, but this
contract void, they feel as though their
seat has been taken, but they forfeited
their seat when they came after you.
This is somebody because their life is
falling apart. They now want to come
reconnect with you because of how well
it's going for you.
So, some of you have an ex out here that
knows you have
either aligned with somebody new
energetically and this person's coming
through physically or you aligned with
somebody new energetically. A con a new
divine contract has been stated and this
individual is now in your life.
So, with the ball, the divine saying get
ready. The ball is rolling. Some of you
are about to have a very sweet
serendipitous meeting with a person that
is meant to be a part of your
experience, a part of the fate that is
unfolding. It's a joint mission, a
double mission. Some of you also have
friendships coming in. I heard fame.
Some of you, this may not be a romantic
partnership at all. This is you Aries
energy. You could be an Aries emperor
energy. you standing firm and remaining
focused on continually elevating into
your highest potential and knowing that
everything will inevitably unfold in
your highest favor. And for some of you,
what is a part of this high highest
favor, your highest potential? Uh the
biggest mission your soul could have
taken on here is fame.
So take what resonates, leave what
doesn't. Cuz y'all know I'm not here to
conform, nor am I here to convince you.
I'm just here to confirm what you
already know. So, this very well could
be individuals from your past attempting
to stop you from being highly positively
praised and recognized uh for your
creative soul expression. And I heard
rising from the ranks. They're also
showing me a phoenix rising above or uh
cult organized ranks. a cult organized
rank, brotherhood, sisterhood, cult,
coven,
individuals that were supposed to be
higher ranking than you. The empress
just came back out. This could be your
[ __ ] mama. Your mama could be some
type of eastern star or something, but
that's irrelevant. Whatever occult
workings were being used against you in
order for you to forfeit your fate and
your destiny and keep you from rising
through the ranks and stepping into your
highest potential have completely
shattered. These individuals were under
the illusion that they would be able to
compromise uh your power, compromise
your light in order for it to be used
for nef judgement immediately for
nefarious intentions.
It's almost like these individuals
intended on continually getting away
with causing heart harm and injury to
others by masking themselves in your
energy. And some of you, this could have
been a mother figure. You could even
have a father or stepfather that
perceives themselves or proclaims
themselves a 33 degree Freemason.
Whoever this is, they're not doing well.
Like your ex could be in some type of
organization. They could have worked
with a karmic family. [ __ ] You could
have a secret society on your ass.
Whoever this is or whatever group this
is, they are not doing well at all like
mentally and healthwise, especially
directing you death. I also heard if you
resonated with my last reading, you
unbound an angel of death that was being
manipulated.
Tell me a little bit more about this
angel of death that has been unbound.
Because they just they just said that
you have unbound an angel of death. We
got a prince of hearts and a missed
opportunity. What does this have to do
with this angel of death? The illusions,
the illusions and the endings from the
bidding this angel had done have been
undone.
So it seems like there was some type of
conjure, there was some type of entity
that orchestrated endings not only in
your lives but others. Uh and it seems
like individuals have awoken from this.
So we do have a prince of hearts. Some
of you may actually have individuals
that want to apologize to you, that know
they missed the opportunity to apologize
to you, that don't even know why they
betrayed you, don't even know why they
walked away from you, why they hurt you,
uh why they were seeing you in a certain
way, but this was a binding done
like
is this a ex? Who who was under this
binding? They said all those in your
life that were seen in your energy as
elevation.
So, some of you had friendships, I won't
say some, the majority of you in here
had friendships and relationships that
when they popped in your energy, uh,
others that were doing divination on you
are looking into your aosic records or
astrological chart. We're seeing that
these relationships had potential to
elevate you,
that there were good things that would
come from these connections if you chose
to ascend with each other. And it looks
like one of you or those that had come
up against you uh in certain forms and
fashions had been intentionally
manipulated because of the way they were
picked up in your energy. But again, all
is divinely orchestrated.
These were tests to the hearts and
spirits of those that were around you
because like the butterfly effect there
are many many choices we could make that
would lead to different outcomes. So the
highest vibrational outcome uh of these
connections would be if these
individuals ascended if they had not
been corrupted if they had not made the
decision they did in order to betray
you. Now, it's left these individuals
not only in depletion physically, but
energetically
in anguish and having a lot of anxiety.
We got protection out here. You have you
were protected from these people that
weren't
as strong as you. And I don't mean to
say that in an egotistical fashion. What
I'm saying is these individuals with the
test that you were faced with and the
test that these individuals were faced
with, you could have chosen to be
corrupted. You could have chosen to move
like those that came up against you, but
you chose the path of the straight and
narrow. You chose to be a good person
when everything was giving you a reason
to be a shitty person, a evil just
[ __ ] You could have been out
here just treating people the way that
people have been treating you, but you
didn't. You also weren't compromised
when it came to money. I feel like some
of you have received blessings in the
past or maybe the recent or uh yeah the
recent recent past or maybe
a few years ago where instead of just
being grubby with it, you gave like you
give somebody the shirt off your back.
You're a very very sweet soul, very
kind, very unconditionally loving heart.
Like you go out of your way to do things
for others where others have not done
these things for you. And it's not that
you ever felt obligated or like you had
to. You just did it out of the kindness
of your spirit where these individuals
were eight of swords. These individuals,
these sneaky deceptive individuals that
are now out in the cold. Look at them.
Five of pentacles are in their heads
about what they should have and they're
watching you. What they could have,
should have,
and would have done.
I heard they didn't have the strength to
walk in your shoes. You walked through
fire and still had divinity in your
heart. You should be proud of yourself
with this finish line. This is the
completion of all of these previous
karmic contracts that were placed within
your soul's reincarnation
uh cycles as assignments to get you to
elevate. And this has been completed.
But like I said, you do have these
individuals in the background working
relentlessly and tirelessly to shift you
out of alignment to what is unfolding as
we speak. It's like they can sense,
excuse me, I was corrected. Not it's
like they know. They know and they can
sense that you have walked into destiny
that they're that you're at this finish
line or you've crossed this finish line
and they want you so desperately to
backtrack. This is why spirit's saying
remain focused and continue to lock in
on what you know is occurring in your
reality and what you desire to
experience within the coming months. I
also heard February is going to be a
very big month for you.
January, I feel like it's going to be
you organizing, sorting things out
pertaining to your new life and starting
to get accustomed and adjusted to your
new life. And February is going to be
the month where the divine, again, take
what resonates, leave what doesn't. For
those of you, this is for where the
divine accelerates what you've become
adjusted to, which means more abundance,
more love, more recognition for you.
It's like you're ready now, but you are
also It's like I need to It's like I
keep saying that this is a life that
you're really going to like. And they
also want me to stop saying it's like
because it's not it's like it is. So,
excuse me. Divinely corrected. You are
ready for this. But again with the way
things are moving physically, January is
going to be the month that you get
accustom and you adapt and you adjust to
the changes that have been integrated to
the changes that are unfolding and to
the ways that your routine uh has
completely shifted. Some of you may even
be guided to get back in the gym uh in
order to raise your frequency and
vibration. Some of you have been guided
to shift your eating habits. Some of you
could even be purging like my skin is
purging right now. Uh, and I know with
every skin purge that I have, especially
with how bad it is, um, it indicates
like the release of things that are not
following me into this new year and a
massive ascension I have completed. So,
some of you, if not all of you, could be
experiencing things pertaining to your
skin. Your scalp could be itchy.
Your skin is purging, too. Don't even
stress about it. Let it happen. Let your
skin purge. Let your body get acclimated
to this new timeline with the way that
it is caught up to your spirit. You
could also be experiencing body aches,
uh, weird dreams. These dreams could
also signify what you are releasing or
the cycles that have been closed out.
With the moon here and the king of
swords, this is a complete severing of
ties to those that needed your energy in
order to elevate. And this is why your
enemies are so obsessed with finding a
way to not only attach to you, but
misalign you to cause chaos and
disruptions in your reality. So you're
more focused on the negative and
manifesting more of the negative than
you are what you should be focused on,
which is your brand new start, your
brand new life, your brand new beautiful
relationships, and this big ass bag of
abundance that's coming through. I heard
God's going to do it for you. I don't
know what you prayed for recently in the
last 3 days, but your prayers have been
heard and they have been answered. I'm
hearing specifically if you asked for a
uh for a monetary blessing.
This is coming through for you. But just
know that there are going to be things
within the matrix thrown your way, an
unexpected [ __ ] bill, uh an
unexpected expenditure that's going to
try and shift your vibration from the
abundant alignment that you have been
in. perceiving yourself as being a
magnet to monetary means to doubting,
dismay, distortion,
uh
disempowerment
and
poverty, lack mentality. So just be
aware do in a sense the matrix is going
to test the matrix the simulation
organizations network societies
corrupted groups are going to attempt to
test how strong your frequency and your
vibration is. So do not allow what is
meant to mentally entrap you in a
certain timeline or in a certain
frequency. Uh I also hearing high
frequency weaponry. Do not allow what is
meant to entrap you in a certain
timeline or frequency to adhere. Now,
with the moon and the king of swords, we
do have Pisces heavily on the board. We
have Gemini, Libra, Aquarius heavily on
the board. You could be a Gemini, Libra,
Aquarius. You could be a Pisces, but
individuals understand what they don't
see. And what I mean by that is with the
moon, intuitively these individuals are
picking up that these ties have been
severed.
Not only are they intuitively picking
up, but because they cannot restore, I'm
hearing restoration. restore what is
falling apart. They know that there has
been a permanent reclamation of your
power. There's been a permanent severing
of ties. This is also causing a lot of
arguments and conflict within this group
where they had at one time bonded
against you. They had recruited and they
had grouped up in order to continually
defame and smear your name to keep you
from experiencing certain opportunities
they knew uh were meant to unfold if you
had reached a certain alignment. Now
with the king of swords energy, this is
also getting Archangel Michael in the
dream state with the moon being out
here. Your angels are alerting you to
what may be directed towards you so you
can prepare to intake it necess intake
it and apply it as necessary. And I'm
also getting you may have recently
called on Archangel Michael. You are
being protected not only in your dream
state but from what you cannot see. And
this is individuals. Give me one on this
King of Pentacles cuz I was going to say
these are individuals that feel like
they can find a vulnerable moment or put
you in a vulnerable position to where
you're easily emotionally manipulated
into a lower vibration so that you don't
walk into 2026 as the highest vibratory
aligned angelic energy
as your highest. Oh, yep. There it is.
Thank you, Archangel Michael. I can't
make this [ __ ] up. The angel said uh
reverse on this tower. What's behind
this tower? Six of pentacles.
So you are being protected with the king
of pentacles out here. If you are with a
counterpart, this counterpart is going
through ascension just as you are. Or
they may have just completed out their
ascension. You could be with an
individual right now or you have this
individual in your energy who was being
relentlessly targeted but subconsciously
angelically guided to alchemize this
energy. A tower has reversed that was
meant to stop not only you from
receiving what is unfolding before you
but to keep you from receiving an offer
or to keep your counterpart in a
financial burden to where that was
supposed to stress y'all out. So if you
are with uh a counterpart or when you
get with a counterpart your relationship
will be tested
or your again your frequency and your
vibration will be tested because these
individuals they argue over money. They
think money is the end all be all. I
feel like you if you are with somebody
uh as you are alchemizing this energy
you may have some some bumps along the
road. You may have um a little bit of
financial like upheavalss, like I said,
an unexpected expenditure, a bill that
pops out of nowhere, but y'all will
handle it with grace. This will not
cause upheavalss in your relationship or
this will not cause upheavalss in your
life uh pertaining to
or yeah, pertaining to how you handle
this. So, if you're not with somebody or
if you're not open to a relationship,
this could very well be these
individuals that paid to cause financial
upheavalss to you in order to again
shift you out of this very positive,
high vibrationally abundant alignment
because they don't. It's like they want
you to take these old cycles with you
into your new year. And the divine is
like, "No, leave that here. That's not
going with you. You can't take that with
you. You better not take that with you."
So, Archangel Michael and angelic
energies working relentlessly here
against those that are trying to
orchestrate a tower. Having this tower
reverse onto those your enemies who are
just oppressed, depressed, and stressed
and pressed. Looks like they been out of
shape. Look, they been out of shape out
here because you do have this fool's
energy which is about a new beginning.
It's also about a leap of faith. A leap
of faith into the new. The fool card is
zero being at zero point master
manifestation energy. I also power play.
I also just got a notification that said
power play. So this lets me know you are
a very powerful player and it's giving
checkmate [ __ ] This is how you're
leaving 2025 isanara
good riddens. everything that was a part
of I'm hearing from 2018 for some of you
uh to to now 2025
where all of these cycles, all of these
assignments, all of these karmic
energies just got moed. They just got
checkmated and they're out here
relentlessly. I'm getting for some of
you a maternal figure as well as an ex
or a paternal figure as well as an ex
working tirelessly and relentlessly in
order to attach to you before you walk
into 2026 cuz I'm getting this portal.
I'm getting you are walking through this
portal and as soon as you do this this
2026 portal it is something about 2026
this new year as soon as you walk
through something as soon as a test
comes through and you passed it that
cycle closes that portal closes behind
you that's what I'm getting you got
individuals attempting to attach to your
look at this your justice your dharma
your celebration
people from six of cups your past who
were living their best lives off of
distorting your energy, affecting your
progress, and again, keeping you from
elevating by instigating and uh
provoking certain emotional upheaval,
certain emotional reactions that you're
no longer having because you're not the
you that they knew. Ooh, bars. You're
not the you that they knew. They don't
know how to trigger you. Two of
Pentacles
and we got Ace of Cups. Your cup
overflowth.
highly favored, extremely fortunate,
favor fa uh uh fortune favors the bold
type of energy.
I don't know. I'm getting this very
weird in the background, insidious,
spiteful, envious vibe.
And I feel like from those that again,
they they made bad deals,
but it you were like used as bait. They
made very bad deals. There was
collateral if this deal over your life
fell through and it did because it was
never going to be you. They were unable
this karmic family that's under
judgment. Told you I was feeling this
insidious [ __ ] judgment with this 10 of
cups. You were the one that brought all
of this judgment down upon these
individuals that can no longer cloak
themselves or protect themselves in your
energy. Or this is your ex's karmic
family. Somebody's whole household is up
in in flames.
fire.
This is why your enemies are so
stressed.
Again, they're watching you experience
this beginning that they had
continuously siphoned and sacrificed
pertaining to you in order to have this
come up, in order to be seen as
abundant, in order to heal.
And now, while your dream life has
become your reality, their worst
nightmare has been made real.
What do we need to know about this
energy? Because it again, your wheel of
fortune is here. You're at the finish
line of something massive and it is
leading to so many phenomenal,
miraculous, supernatural events in your
experience. But the when it comes to
your enemies, it looks like everything,
every [ __ ] thing is going
wrong. Everything that could go wrong is
going wrong. And they're trying to
direct that wrong and project that wrong
over you. So again, if there's a little
bit like it's giving lemony snick series
of unfortunate events, if you have like
little small [ __ ] trying to piss you
off, don't let it. This is these are
projections. This isn't even your
energy. I feel like the divine may be
letting this through uh slightly just to
test you.
We got eight of wands, communication
coming out sideways, block
communication, a decision, two of
swords,
Give me one on this block communication
and this decision source God what do we
need to know about this queen of swords
keep these cuts made that's what the
divine wants you to know there is a
lover that may try to uh appro you
already know this you could have been
having dreams of this person or if this
is not a lover these were individuals
that should have loved you where things
are going [ __ ] wrong and they can't
attach to you and they can't project
this ending over you you need to know
with those that are faced with defeat
and that are being forced to surrender,
they're going to try and make themselves
known to you. They are going to try and
reach out. They are going to try and
communicate. Spirit's saying, "Keep
these cuts made. There's a reason why
you have been guided to block
communication with certain people. Could
even be a Leo out here.
Somebody's being exposed for the things
they said about you, too, and why they
made the decision to go up against you.
I told you with this angel of death that
has been unbound. Uh there were
necessary endings that occurred in your
life where others had again mistaken not
mistaken were misguided and misled about
you. These may be the individuals that
now want to apologize
because they're like I don't know why I
did what I did to you and I'm so sorry.
You are not obligated in any way, shape,
and form to accept that apology or to
hear these people out. Honestly, with
the way communication is coming through
uh in this deck, spirit's saying keep
communication blocked
with the decisions you made to cut
communication off from certain
individuals. Keep it that way
because they're not allowed to be a part
of what's unfolding for you. And they
were out here collaborating. I can't
make this [ __ ] up. Look at this three of
pentacles. That's a collaboration. We
got the prince of wands out here. They
moved quickly to collaborate against you
with the magician. So if you were
wondering if certain individuals that
are now left in remorse and regret were
doing some type of huby jubilee over you
or if they knew some type of huby
jubilee was being done over you, some
type of [ __ ] hocus pocus voodoo
magic. Oh, I would say voodoo madness.
That was not a coincidence. Yes. Yes,
they were. They were out here
manifesting against you. Some of you,
you have exes that are [ __ ] Satanist,
bro.
some type of a cult. They was playing in
something dark. They thought it was
funny, too. Somebody out here, maybe
this was a sibling,
but somebody out here felt like the
darker occult was amusing, like it was
some type of aesthetic
and they were playing in some dark [ __ ]
they didn't fully understand
and bound themselves to. And this is why
they've been permanently released from
you because they was playing in some
weird [ __ ] And now because their life
is falling apart and whatever they were
playing with is destroying their life,
they want to come over to you.
Don't don't unblock them. Let your wheel
of fortune unfold as it should. Oh
Jesus. Yeah, I know. They was playing in
some dark [ __ ] Look at this. Your
ancestors said we fighting the devil
right now. These do not let these
individuals back into your life,
especially with how beautiful it is, how
beautiful it's about to be. Cuz your
ancestors said these know that they are
the devil. This is who they was playing
with. This is what they was involved in.
Ebuke.
Give me one on the seven of wands with
the devil spirit.
Eight of you walk the [ __ ] away.
Yes. Spirit's saying keep your distance
from these individuals. Whether it's
family, ex-lovers, old friends, anybody
from your past is meant to remain in the
past. It's not meant to be a part of
your future. And they're really adamant
about this. So, you may very well have
some people that like need you right now
that have the audacity to reach out
after everything they've done to you and
everything they said about you. It is
giving. Yes, John. It is giving house a
sellouts.
What else do we need to know about this
wheel of fortune and the phenomenal
beautiful expansive experiences that are
spirit says that's the truth. You
already know this.
These beautiful expansive experiences we
can
expect to unfold with the Ace of Swords
and the High Priestess. You're also
about to find out the truth. Hold on.
I'll get into this Wheel of Fortune uh
and the 2026 energy in a minute.
But they're so serious about this. Like
they're not playing. The divine is
stating these individuals made
intentional deals. We're intentionally
playing in the graveyard. We're
intentionally conjuring and doing like
little They're showing me somebody prick
their thumb and like
put it in something like intentionally
doing things in order to
work with something darker
in order to get a certain outcome. like
they really expected like the devil to
bring them
fame, fortune, luck, favor,
but it's something about your name was
written in blood or some [ __ ] Like you
were meant to be the the biggest
sacrifice and you got away, which
compromised all of their previous
contracts.
All of their previous contracts were
void because they couldn't get you.
So you these individuals were like
intentionally diabolical, nefarious, and
evil. What the hell? What was they
playing in? Oh yeah, they was evil.
Queen of cups in the reverse.
Oh, they didn't feel sorry about this.
They wanted these. They wanted a good
life.
And this was off you being sacrificed.
That's crazy. These are some evil
energies with the Queen of Cups in the
reverse. They didn't feel any type of
way about you not being here or
something bad happening to you
continuously or your babies, your
households, like
they really held no feelings towards
what they were doing. They just needed
it to work.
And now it's a new year. It's a new day.
It's a new life for you. And you're
about to be feeling real good. You could
like Michael Boué
because your hard work has paid off. And
there's the Wheel of Fortune.
You're at the top of the wheel and again
at an all-time high energetically.
Everything is being magnetized to you in
this moment. You are literally walking
into this new year as this new version
of you with this new experience that is
unfolding. And again, January is about
you getting accustomed and adapted and
acclimated to all of the new that has
aligned for you and that is physically
unfolding for you.
And again, this may be slightly
uncomfortable. The first month of
January or the first month the first
month of the new year may be slightly
uncomfortable with how you are having to
get adjusted and the things that you are
going to be guided to change or
relinquish
in the next few days into January. And
this could be even bad habits like this
could be you,
you know, slowing down your sugar intake
or you cutting back on caffeine or you
changing from eating fried greasy foods
to something healthier and more uh
high frequency and high vibrational for
your system.
So, this is going to take some getting
used to this. the way that you walk now,
the way that you talk, the way that you
are. And it's going to take time for
others to get used to this new version
of you as well, because you're going
into this new year as a new you, a you
that nobody has had access to except
those that are meant to be around you.
So, yes, make sure that you're taking
your salt baths, you're doing your
cleansing. Uh, you may even want to do a
return to sender of intent and entities
just to clear out any residual
unnecessary energy and intentions before
2026.
What else do we need to know? Spirit,
you want me to get the Ganesha deck for
show? You have a Leo that's holding on
to you or these individuals. You do have
enemies out here that are holding on to
the thought that they would be able to
disrupt, distort, or take from you if it
Yeah. Ace of Pentacles. If it's not a
Leo, it's somebody that like they can't
believe that it's over. Like they can't
believe that you really escaped, that
you're really this protected with the
Princess of Swords. They're watching,
waiting, praying,
doing practitionary work or paying for
practitionary work. Whose crusty ass is
this? Hold on. Let me find out. Let's be
a little nosy real quick cuz I need to
know who is still [ __ ] attacking the
collective.
I I just heard those that will not
listen no matter how bad it gets for
them continue to move forward leaving
them in the past while you skyrocket
into the future.
Let me see a little bit cuz we got time.
Somebody that wants to win by any means
necessary and they watching you.
Who is this? How many? Can you give us a
number?
Four.
balance
for oh
four balance four of cups balance missed
opportunity to balance things out with
you. This is also individuals are
fighting you and relentlessly targeting
you and attempting to do whatever they
can in order to obtain off your energy
because they need balance in their
lives. I told you everything is going
all right with the four of cups. They're
missing opportunities back to back to
back. Their life is going through
upheavalss as yours is balancing out.
So why are they attacking you? Why are
they targeting you? For balance.
Ooh, this came out sideways. They're
blocked from your people from your past
are blocked from your destiny. Six of
cups. This beginning and your ancestors.
Your ancestors are blocking these
individuals from your destined and faded
beginning. With the star out here, this
is not just about healing. This is about
destiny with the new or with the
beginnings card which is the fool card
card zero out here and your ancestors
fighting these individuals. They are
foolish to continually attempt to combat
you for what had been faded to unfold
for you at this point in time. Any
adversity that you have is being handled
immediately.
So, you're not feeling the brunt of what
they had intended you to go through. And
that's because angels and ancestors are
all around you. They are not allowing
any of this to have effect on you
because of where you're at vibratorily
and what they need you to focus on.
What do you need us to f
Well, I was just about to ask what you
need us to focus on what they're telling
us.
We got 88 out here.
walking away from everything that does
not serve you and is not meant to be a
part of your experience as well as what
you're walking into. This is what spirit
wants you focused on is this fortune,
this abundance. I'm getting a big
monetary blessing. You prayed for life
to change for the better. You did the
work in order to align with this
positively abundant timeline. And now
your spirit team and the most high are
communicating to you. Be ready for the
changes that you prayed for because they
are happening now. And again, 88, you
could be seeing 888, 808 or 88. You got
abundance, bro. They said inheritance
unlocked.
Inheritance unlocked. We got a king of
staves out here. Give me one on this
king of staves. We got a temptation.
This is why. This is why you also have
an ex working against you. We got
temptation with the King of Wands. Bad
deals were made. This you got
individuals that feel like they
shouldn't have blocked away from you or
a union. This is also somebody that
wants to lure you back in because you
have your inheritance, your ancestral
divine inheritance unlocked, which is
leading to a massive monetary windfall
in your life. Whoever this is that you
were associated with uh at one point in
time, they know with the way that their
life is falling apart and the ways that
yours is getting better that it's only a
matter of time before you have some type
of very successful breakthrough, very
successful. I'm getting like blow up and
glow up. So, some of you could be
online. This could be pertaining to
something uh social med pertaining to
something that you do on social media or
that you post online or that you're like
a business and somebody knows that
you're about to be very very very
successful.
I don't know why they just they just
showed me Tony Stark
and I believe as Iron Man he was uh not
only a genius but a billionaire.
This is your justice. So, you got
individuals that know we got another
eight on the board. They're mentally
entrapped because their ships are being
laid to rest because of the sacrifice
they tried to do over you. This could be
a Pisces, Cancer, Scorpio, Leo, Aries,
Sagittarius. Doesn't have to be. While
you're getting everything that's due to
you. So, I don't know what type of
comeup your ex had or what type of
comeup your family had or whoever was
working against you, but that was very
short-lived. Very short-lived.
And now they're realizing that
everything that they thought they were
going to be able to maintain, everything
that they thought they were going to be
able to permanently stabilize in their
life, as it's falling apart, they've
realized that you've reclaimed all that
is yours, and that every deal they made
before you, that your energy protected
them from reaping the consequences of
have now fallen upon their own heads,
and collateral is being taken. I'm
hearing the devil has come to collect
because the devil couldn't collect you.
Ain't that better? Yep. Look at this.
They stressed about this little hooly
jubily. They did the moon. They're
stressed about their secrets, too. This
could be a Pisces. You also as a psychic
intuitive, a seer and oracle. You have
these individuals stressed because you
always know what the [ __ ] they're doing
and you know what they're going through.
Spirit is giving you a bird's eye of
your enemies, letting you know every
move they intend to make and every move
they have made and every move that they
may be currently making in order to
prepare yourself from what you are going
to integrate, what you are going to take
in and what you are going to be
redirecting. We got magic out here and
fortune. They really thought this was
going to lead them to fortune. Now they
got to watch you get it. Look at this.
You got ships coming in of wish
fulfillment and fortune. Then we got
nine. Look, two nines on the board. You
could be seeing 999 909 or 999. Look at
that. They get to watch you movement
right here. They get to with the sun of
the ace and the ace of pentacles and the
two of cups. Look at this spread.
Galactic golden. They literally have to
watch you be unconditionally loved. Get
this ace of pentacles that they wanted
to hold on to, that they wanted to be
the one out here living with and watch
you right off into what is seen as the
sunset and the sunrise. It's just the
best days of your life. 2026 going about
to be lit. You are protected. Spirit's
saying, "I'm making sure to coveret all
of it."
And you get wish fulfillment. You get to
experience these ships that so many
others were partaking in that are
rightfully yours. I don't know who got a
job, who got a relationship, who got a
house, uh who got like a windfall, who
got cars off of compromising you, but
that is over.
whatever they the life they were living,
the celebration they were having, the
party's over now. The party is over for
your enemies. They have to sit back and
watch while it's just beginning for you.
I think this is a beautiful reading
because this is basically spirit saying
you're going to have some irritants
throughout the week. Okay, the new year
starts, I believe, on Thursday. You're
going to have some irritants throughout
the [ __ ] week. All right. These
individuals gonna be trying to to get
under your get under your skin and call
up your ass, okay? With the little brown
noses helps. So just I won't say ignore
the irritants, but acknowledge the
irritants is what they are. Everything
in this [ __ ] mama trying it and
trying you before you walk into 2026 and
everything that's been faded for you.
You could have a mama out here that's
trying to betray you or a Leo, Aries,
Sagittarius. You got somebody upset out
here that everything they did to betray
you didn't stop your future and it show
as [ __ ] didn't stop you. Whoever this is
may even be with love out here working
against your love life. You and your
partner leveling up wanting to cause
endings to your relationships and it's
backfired on this
malevolent little demon.
Whoever this is that thought that they
could stop the I'm hearing the first
part of fortune, they are watching it
unfold or they've seen it unfold
already. Something has either come into
your life or is about to that indicates
to this weird crispy demonic derelic
duck that it is the first part of your
fortune. It's the first part of you
buying the whole building.
That's what I'm getting. I'm getting
Yep. to what is rightfully yours. Seems
like individuals thought they had
slammed uh the door to what was yours in
your face and locked it. And now you
coming back to buy everything in that
[ __ ] You're like, "That's mine. That's
mine. That's mine." You're coming uh for
the throne. Your throne. And you sitting
on that beautifully. I'm also hearing
you should see me in a crown. And
they're about to. You have been crowned
royalty. This is somebody that decided
or individuals that decided
to come up against you for your harvest,
your fertility. Again, even your
vitality is what I heard. And now they
over here. I feel like some of your
enemies are looking real they they look
real ragged like Crips Keeper Gollum.
Like I I'm not one to judge anybody's
physical appearance, but I feel like
this is the energy being stripped from
them. the divine energy that they were
like glamorizing themselves with all of
the as well as bad karma probably
beating that ass.
You have some enemies out here.
They not only down bad monetarily and
their foundations and relationships have
crumbled, but it's also like physically
these individuals are Yeah. They looking
like what they are. Heartbroken, bro.
Heartbroken over your power.
Heartbroken. You've reclaimed your
power. That's why power card coming out
here. What else do we need to know about
most high
expect to be get? Look at this.
Anticipate being given what is
rightfully yours. You've reclaimed your
power and everything that your power was
meant to align you to. You have gone up
in the ranks. You have leveled up. Your
divine ranking has elevated yet again
with the 10 of pentacles. Spirit's
saying, "I'm about to give this to you.
I'm about to do my big one. God saying
I'm about to do my big one. Watch how I
move. Sneaky and deceptive individuals
left out in the cold. People have been
lied to. They pay to leave you out in
the cold of what's being given to you.
They they paid and prayed to leave you
out of the cold of
it's like health, wealth, unconditional
love, the things that they desire to
maintain or acquire. And now they're
like, "This practitioner [ __ ]
lied to me.
These individuals feel bamboozled and
hoodwinkedked because they paid a pretty
penny for this and they worked
tirelessly against you. You got your
enemies tired, bro. They tried and now
they tired.
I told you. Look at them. Tried and now
they're tired. We got five of Look at
it. Five of saves out here. That's
chaos, conflict, competition with the
Ace of Cups. They were fighting for your
favor and now they're worn out.
Yep. I was about to say what you should
expect for your 2026 is you will receive
word of your enemies being in chaos. You
will receive word of your enemies being
oppressed, limited. It's like
spiritually jumped like they're being
jumped by your ancestors. They're being
jumped by angels. They getting their ass
whooped. You will hear word of the
judgment and the karma that your enemies
are going through. those that attempted
to oppress uh the divine and the most
high's plan for you. And what else you
should expect? Receiving a victory
monetarily.
This is what your 2026 looks like. Queen
of Pentacles, Princess of Pentacles.
You're like evolving monetarily. Going
from a princess or a prince. I'm not
saying that you are, of course, you're
the empress. You're the emperor. But
monetarily there is something coming
through empowering you. You're going
from one way of life, from experiencing
life uh monetarily in a specific type of
way in a way that did not align with
your spirit to being empowered to having
a massive windfall come through in the
way that you've been locked in on this
new alignment for you that leads to a
massive I told you like business
victory, life victory. This could be a
victory in court. What is coming through
has been ordained by the most high for
you. But it is transformation,
life-changing. You're going from
overwork or working harder than I won't
say the divine feels like you should,
but it's like going from
showing the divine that you can be,
how do I put this? Because this wasn't
just going to be like given to you
because then you'd sabotage it. You
wouldn't know how to handle it. Um, this
is you showing the divine your work
ethic, being yes, obedient, showing the
divine that no matter what is thrown at
you, you can still remain in alignment
and continue to put in the work on your
mission. This is showing the divine and
showing the most high that you
acknowledge and hold gratitude for
everything that you've acquired because
of the work that you put in. And you're
about to be given so much more with
wisdom here. You already knew this
though. The divine wanted to test your
spirit. Thank you, Patrice. Thank you,
Patrice. Thank you, Breezy Baby. Thank
you, each and every one of you beautiful
galactic golden souls that have swn into
me and not just into me, but into
humanity as well. and know that you are
receiving it back infinitely, amplified
and endlessly in all the ways that God
ordains and deems as necessary to your
expansive, highly impactful, highly and
positively impactful,
incredible, phenomenal, supernatural
experience here. And all those faded
connections that are meant to unfold in
the position that you are meant to be
placed in and that have been divinely
advocated to receive in this moment and
experience in this moment. And may it
all unfold for you expeditiously.
Seriously, thank you. Thank you for your
likes. Thank you for your comments.
Thank you for making this Galactic
Golden Family what it is,
unconditionally loving and
non-judgmental and welcoming to all
those that felt lost previously.
Because this family would not be a
family without you. So, thank you
because so many new Galactic Golden
family members have located us and feel
at home in this family. And it's all
because of you. I see y'all talking to
each other in the chat and in the
comments just, you know, it's almost
like giving these other souls a sense of
of well-being with the understanding
because I know so many of us at many
points in our journey felt [ __ ]
crazy. And it's so comforting to know
there's so many of us that have had
similar experiences. That we truly are a
galactic golden angelic collective that
were meant to experience this so that
we'd be able to not only evolve, ascend,
and elevate humanity, but help. It's
like help the world understand what was
meant to be cloaked, what was meant to
be hidden, and illuminate it completely
while also shining a guiding light to
others who felt lost in the darkness.
So, thank you for not only the beautiful
energy you've directed my way, but all
those that you have saved along your
journey and all those that you're about
to with what's going to happen for you
with what's about to happen for you.
Thank you. And just know this beginning
is big. It puts you in a position to be
You see how big this staff is and how
the sun energy is behind it. God is
revealing you. This is you. A big
energy, but you have a bigger God.
Whatever is about to be done in your
life, it's going to be seen by all. And
they're going to know who backs you. If
they don't believe it, they're about to
with what's about to be done for you.
Let me get my Ganesha cards and see what
it's your harvest.
I heard go big or go home. Bit go big or
go home. Galactic Golden Ohana wish
fulfillment.
Something really is. It's big. Hold on.
Let me It's big. Can you give us a
little bit of energy on this big
phenomenal
like beginning this 2026? What's coming
through? You're about to be generously
given to. The divine's like, "What I'm
about to give you? What did I just say?"
So, it's what God's about to do in your
life.
I heard your ancestors and your angels
prepared for this moment.
You've been prepared for this moment,
but they've been waiting for this.
Again, divine timing. So, this is your
ancestors and your angels going by any
means necessary. Keep this soul in
alignment and make sure that everything
unfolds when it is supposed to because
time is here.
This is another reason why your spirit
team is so adamant on on keeping people
blocked, not communicating with them,
releasing what is not of your highest
vibrational good and staying focused on
the future.
They said you never know how fast the
future can happen for you, but know that
the future is now and everything is
happening very quickly. Stay focused,
Galactic Golden. Ohana, we got be
candid. So, this is my sit down a little
bit. What's being given to you is going
to humble a lot of people. This is sit
down little [ __ ] Be humble. And this
is also move in silence. Now, with this
spread, I'm not getting that you you may
be trying to move in silence with what's
unfolding, but what's about to be given
to you is going to be so big that it is
meant to be seen by your enemies. It is
meant to be revealed by the most high to
all those that have attempted to oppress
and oppose you because this is going to
be humbling them. Your enemy is about to
be massively humbled. I just heard they
already are.
But what's about to be given to you is
going to shut the mouths of many. All
right. Bet. What do we need to know? Oh,
what do we need to know? Inner knowing.
You already know this. I'mma shut I'mma
put this back in the deck. I almost said
shut this back in the deck. They're shut
out. We got guidance with generosity,
but guidance in the reverse.
Your spirit team's saying they are not
guiding you in any way, shape, or form
to give to any [ __ ] money over here
that's being humbled.
So, right off the bat, just like we
talked about earlier, uh your spirit
team is saying they're going to come to
you.
Your enemies will tell you what's going
on. They will need you. So, you could
have somebody reach out of the blue and
be I just went through this and I just
went through that. And they're expecting
you to be, "Oh my god, do you need
help?" Like, do you need me to send you
a few dollars or something?
No. This is the divine's way of showing
you who had been uh opposing you, who
had been up against you, and who's going
through uh judgment. See, your spirit
team with guidance in the reverse is
not, look at this, with prosperity on
the bottom. Do not give to these people.
Do not give to these people.
You are not being guided to give them
anything. Which means this is coming in
now. Whatever is unfolding monetarily
for you, you're going to have well well
more.
Well, a well, a well, a wish. Well, more
far more is what I meant to say. Far
more than you anticipated. They said
well more. Like a well. It's it's
it's never ending. It's a a a well of of
fortune. A well of wealth. A wealth
well. Maybe some of you have a well
outside or you recently saw some type of
well, but a well of wealth like you
could give to these people and it
wouldn't affect you. It wouldn't it it
wouldn't be a dent in your prosperity.
You're not being guided to. So you are
going to have people that reach out that
try and pull on your heartstrings
because of what they're going through.
Just know that your enemies, they
getting wrecked, son. They getting
riggedy wrecked, son, because this is
what they manifested. cultivation just
landed on be humble. They have to accept
this is what they cultivated by being
determined to direct energetic movement
your way. This is for their soul to gain
understanding while your life changes
while you experience more joy
and your harmony is unaffected.
So you have individuals in a lot of
disharmony, a lot of chaos, sickness,
health, poverty. Well, your life is
stabilized. Your beautiful, abundant,
harmonious, unconditionally loving,
extremely prosperous and highly favored
and extremely fortunate life has
stabilized. This is your new beginning.
You're being taken care of would nurture
by the divine.
And your fulfillments are being met. And
not only met like wish fulfillments are
being they said promises being
fulfilled, wish fulfillment coming to
fruition. It's protected as well
by any means necessary. I told you your
spirit team is not playing about what
they work so hard for you to experience.
This is giving. You made it. You really
made it with drive here. I'm getting the
chariot with this energy and the promise
of the future. Chariot energy. Uh horse
energy again. 2026 fast fiery movement
forward into what has been promised for
you. I told you a promise has been
fulfilled with blessings at the bottom
of the deck. Blessings and love.
This is others. Stay open to this. This
is others showing you unconditional
love. This is you loving your life and
yourself. This is you loving everything
that unfolds for you and every
relationship that you've been faded to
make and every way that you skyrocket
and are uh uh positively praised and
recognized.
I don't know if somebody's eating like a
strawberry strudel
or like a strawberry cheesecake or
something. Strawberries could be very
relevant. I just smelled it. I just
smelled like a strawberry strudel or a
strawberry cheesecake.
Strawberries. Harvest. Harvest energy.
You could have just recently eaten
strawberries as well. You could have
seen a strawberry. Just take what
resonates, leave what doesn't, cuz y'all
know they be channeling me very
interesting things. Claire's sentience
has been amplified.
So, your spiritual sense could be
upgrading. You just made a strawberry
cheesecake. That's confir. That's
confirmation. You're making red velvet
cookies and strawberry cheesecake in the
middle. What? Everybody make a
strawberry cheesecake and stuff. If you
ate strawberries this morning,
confirmation right there. Harvest,
harvest, harvest. Exactly. Cause
if you've been seeing strawberries, just
know that this is for you. You could
have even Yes. had a a strawberry
smoothie.
They said strawberries hold a massive
spiritual significance. Look into it.
Hold on. They're making me look this up.
Pause.
Because I know that strawberries
symbolize abundance, but they want me.
Strawberries.
A strawberry spiritual meaning is love,
purity and abundance, love and passion,
purity and righteousness, abundance and
fertility, perfection and humility,
healing and balance, and magic and
nature.
Wow.
Is that what you can expect your 2026 to
be looking like? Cuz you better claim
it. You could have been craving
strawberries as well. So that is the
spiritual meaning of strawberries that
Yep. Insight.
The divine is giving us insight right
now into 2026.
Abundance, fertility, love,
righteousness,
purity, peace, comfort. I know peace and
comfort wasn't a part of the
strawberries, but when you eat them, if
you like strawberries, when you eat
them, you just feel a sense of peace and
comfort.
And that's what I'm getting. The divine
is assuring that everything unfolds as
it should pertaining to your purpose,
your future, and your partnerships as
well as the position.
Oh, and he thank you. They also reminded
me strawberries indicate healing as
well. Thank you, spirit. I almost forgot
that you are also healing. You will be
at your utmost healed state walking into
2026. Healing uh h they said having
fully been repaired from the trauma you
experienced within previous cycles. What
is coming through is healing for you but
this is also about soul level healing.
It's not it's not just about uh
restorative healing to the things that
had been perceivably lost along this
journey, but it's also about what your
spirit may have
allowed itself to carry through the
trauma that you experienced through the
assignments
and the contracts that you closed out.
So it's a deep soul level healing
priority.
It is a priority that sustenance. It is
a priority that you anchor in and ground
for what's coming in quickly because it
comes into stay. Not just this healing,
but everything that was due to be res I
almost said responded to
the way the universe, the way the most
high, the way your angels are responding
to you and the way that this restoration
and this rejuvenation is occurring for
you.
It's like the divine is saying, I need
you prepared for how quickly this is all
happening, for how quickly things are
moving. [ __ ] Some of you could be in a
relationship and be like, "This is
moving hella fast." Like the divine is
saying, "Embrace how quickly this moves.
Embrace how quickly the things that are
meant to come in uh how quickly it comes
in and how it is meant to stay.
I heard it. I heard it again. It's a new
dawn. It's a new day. And I'm feeling
good."
So, be prepared to experience the best
that life has to offer because you've
experienced the worst.
Relax. Some of you also need some more
rest. You need to meditate. I'm also
hearing relax as it all happens. Relax
as it all unfolds.
Oh, okay. Thank you.
The best up to
The best up to now.
What does that mean? The best up to
the best. It's up from here. I just got
an ad that said the best up to and then
it said 40% off now. So, four
union something you can hold on to with
the four of pentacles, four of swords.
Things being laid to rest.
Those being humbled have to sit down.
And what else am I missing? Four of
cups. They missed an opportunity with
you. They missed an opportunity to be
connected to what's being given to you.
Amplified by the zero. 40%.
So four zero. Four amplified by the
zero. Take what resonates, leave what
doesn't. But what you need to relax and
let all unfold that is happening very
quickly is this beginning. We've got
cleared out your energy. Those that you
cleared out your energy are watching
this. Just so you know, the divine is
going to make sure to flex on each and
every one of your enemies. For real,
they are going to have to sit down and
be humble.
I heard and keep your name out of their
mouth.
Who? Damn.
I was about to I was ABOUT TO SAY, WHO
SAID THAT? Those that love you. We got
capacity to love and prosperity.
The divine really is about to show up
and show out in your life.
and you're about to massively move
forward. This is even some of you are
going to be getting a new card.
A lot of people are going to have to
shut up when it comes to you and what
they've even this could be a
practitioner speaking over you. They're
going to have to shut up.
You get to it. Yeah. A practitioner and
what they're speaking over you spiritual
practice. They're going to have to shut
up. they going that somebody's gifts are
being stripped and they are being
silenced in the spirit for because
you're being protected from spiritual
practice and they were told to sit down.
So whatever is happening to them, it's
because the divine is saying you're
done. And what's happening to you is I
heard angelic assurance as well as what
is what is necessary to be
supernaturally provided at this time
pertaining to your purpose and the plan
over your life. Those that keep
attempting to speak endings or project
endings will be and have been silenced.
Again, I'm getting they're done. So,
some of you do have a practitioner that
could be actually getting silenced.
Like, they could be snatched to the
outer realms. They could be kicked out
of their whole [ __ ] vessel for
messing with you. Cuz somebody is not
going to be able to heal or have their
gifts restored in the ways that the
divine is going to be uh making sure
they can never cause hurt, harm, and
injury again to you or anybody else.
What else do we need to know?
Achievement.
Some of you are getting this gift, too.
with achievement. This is your ranking
going up or this being added because you
I'm almost getting like Mortal Kombat.
Get over here. This could have been a
Scorpio that was targeting you. Uh some
of you are having this practitioner or
these practitioners gifts being given to
you
because you outranked them. You came up
against them and you won and they ended
up forfeiting their gifts to you. Wow.
So, just expect even more scary,
accurate, intuitive hits to come
through.
They said you're going to know
immediately what's been given to you
with what you're able to do or what's
been amplified for you. We got Splendor
in the reverse wanted to land over here.
So, this has nothing to do with you.
This is somebody at the bottom of the
wheel of fortune. This is somebody that
the work they were doing over your wheel
of fortune has reversed.
So, you are having additives to your
experience.
Yep. Look at this. Blessings. I can't
make this [ __ ] up. You are having
additives to your experience. You did
have some perceivably powerful
practitioners attempting to do work over
you. They were told to leave you the
[ __ ] alone. They didn't do that. They
were egotistical and had to prove
themselves. And now they have nothing
left. There is a practitioner here that
won't be able to work on or work for
anybody else. Insight. I told look at
did you see how it landed over here? The
divine has so many messages except
the amplified insight that has been
given to you by this individual that was
attempting to work over your wheel of
fortune. It now belonging it now belongs
to you.
So something about insight here. You
your seer abilities your oracle
abilities being amplified.
Oo they should love you. You could be
having some crazy dreams right now. You
could be like, "What the [ __ ] these
dreams mean?" You're looking into uh the
energetic information that's been given
to you. And it's crazy cuz the dream I
had last night was about demonic deals
that had gone bad for individuals that
had set up collateral was people they
loved. And I was seeing this play out
from like an outside view. Like I was
looking over the entirety of these
situations going, "Who the [ __ ] was out
here making these deals?" Like it was it
got so ugly. Some of them uh it was like
one of the individuals in my dreams it
was their daughter and it was a couple
and the other individual like their
daughter was negatively affected and
their souls ended up being compromised
by the deal they made and their daughter
was collateral and then another
individual that had made this deal. It
was his wife and I was like who the [ __ ]
was making these [ __ ] deals over the
people they love thinking they was going
to get something. And the craziest part
is in this dream, the couple that had
placed their daughter up as collateral
made the deal for their daughter to have
a good life. And then the husband that
had placed his wife up for collateral.
And with the deal going bad, his wife in
my dream ended up taking her life. And
he was like, "This shit's not even worth
it. Like, I don't even want to be here
without my wife." The reason that he put
his wife up for collateral uh was
because they were unable to have
children and he wanted to have a child
with her. And the deal was for them to
be able to not only be financially uh
stable, but to have a child because she
wasn't supposed to. And when the wife in
my dream took her life, she was
pregnant. And I was like, I don't know
what type of deals these people are
making, but they're bad. So, you could
be having I say all this to say you
could be having dreams about what's
going on with these individuals that uh
were working with a practitioner where
this practitioner may have bamboozled
them or the deal they made backfired
when this practitioner came after you.
Take what sleep doesn't. You could even
have be having dreams about what's
happening to a karmic familial unit,
what's happening to old friends, or
what's happening to people that you
don't even know. You could have people
in your dreams where you're like, "Who
the [ __ ] are these people?
You have taken on the sight of those
that had been targeting you, that at one
point had been gifted until they had
forfeited their gifts to you by
attempting to abuse the gifts that had
been given to them. They have been
permanently restricted while you have
gained the sight of those opposing you.
And you may be seeing into the workings
of these individuals that have had their
gifts given to you. And you may be
confused cuz you may not know who the
[ __ ] these people are and what's going
on. Why you dreaming random individuals?
It's because of what's been given to
you.
What you can now see
with this
amplified insight, delight. Yep. With
look
enlightenment.
So this is about to spirit's saying
we're delighted to elevate you in this
way, but please use these gifts
accordingly to the divine guidance
given.
You will see some things that don't make
sense, but they will help break it down
for you. What else do we need to know?
Spirit,
the revelation and surrender.
Look at this. The revelation is the
prophecy over your life. Surrender is
how many individuals have to let this
go, have to let you go. This is or have
to stop looking into your life with
surrender and revelation. I feel like
some of you are about to with the way
your gifts have been enhanced and with
what you've received from who was
targeting you, you're going to see the
fall of your enemies uh spiritually like
with your gifts before you see it
physically. And you thought your gifts
were intense. Now, this is like
you knowing every feeling, every
sentence, every
intention of these individuals that are
about to go through severe judgment or
that are already experiencing severe
karma.
They said, "Be aware that the gifts that
you have been given, they had been
testing for in the gifts that you've
been given that have been amplified,
they had been testing for in your youth,
seeking out special gifted children.
There is a reason why you were not fully
activated in your younger years, but why
you are being fully activated and
enhanced now. Know that they will look
for you. These are individuals that have
been very concerned about those in these
revolutionary light leader positions.
Yes. The gate program. Exactly. Exactly.
Sleep with light. The gate program.
These are individuals that are either
have located you like CIA energy or will
soon locate you. But again, you should
not be afraid. These are individuals
that seek to study to seek to understand
but will not be given any type of access
to the divine information that has been
relayed to you. All they can do is
observe you. So some of you need to know
this is a spart a spart this is a part
of your spiritual quest.
They said the world will see through the
eyes of divinity and this is what they
feared. The world will see through the
feared. You are making massive
uh imperative pivotal changes upon this
planet. You have already been documented
as a extra what extraterrestrial they're
saying an extraterrestrial external
threat to those that had been
capitalizing off of the corruption. But
again, there is nothing to fear, only so
much fortune to look forward to. This is
what 2026 holds for you and holds for
the planet too. Be prepared to really
take on this and embody this leadership
position, this leadership,
light leader, anointed powerful
position. What else do we need to know?
Cuz I know that's not for everybody. I
know this life is a little bit and
maintain a positive outlook no matter
what the matrix or what may be thrown
your way in order to
misalign you. We got divine support. The
divine is working everything out in your
favor. So make sure not to let the
little series of inconveniences that may
occur this week completely aggravate and
agitate you. All right? Remain positive
and stay focused. And the divine is
saying I am supporting you in everything
they said in every way that these
blessings are coming through to you.
Stay open
to guidance
on this fast forward moving energy. So
spirit is saying stay open to the ways
that we are going to be guiding you with
what's coming in quickly and how you are
meant to move forward
from these individuals that are being
humbled and again how you are meant to
move forward steadfast with the way that
your life is changing quickly.
They're saying what you're going to do
with what's being given to you again.
Lock in Galactic Golden ohana cuz this
is happening quick. This is happening
fast as [ __ ]
These blessings
are happening. Yeah. Steadfast. Look at
that. I told you. I told you. You
manifested this.
You cocreated and cultivated this
alongside the most high.
Anything else we need to know?
They said beauty. Behold beauty before
you. What? Behold beauty before you and
allow
the allow the
dis distortion and death of the past to
be laid to rest. You no longer reside
there. You are free. But I'm going to
leave it right there. Galactic, did you
have a message?
Bring it here.
Bring Bring me to Saturn.
Bring me to Saturn.
No, don't drop it. Oh, no. It's not
Saturn. It's the asteroid. Abundance
Kitty has the asteroid.
Bro, you I I keep I tell you this every
time she talks. Y'all have not like
heard Abundance Kitty be loud like that.
Anytime she's loud like that, she has a
message. This time it was abundance
kitty and she brought over the asteroid
which means somebody's financial
foundation is being completely uprooted.
Those that have been targeting you,
they're going to remain in poverty where
for you the asteroid can also symbolize
the tower divine intervention. There is
and that was abundance kitty bringing
this asteroid. There is what else do you
have?
Now she got the rocket. I know you heard
the little jingle in the background. Now
she has the rocket.
You better prepare for this [ __ ] to be
uh happening quickly. This monetary
means, this divine intervention, this
windfall of wealth is happening faster
than you may expect.
Fast as [ __ ] boy. I know you just heard
her little skidly pips.
She never plays like this. She really
feeling something in the energy. So,
yes, blast off. 2026 is going to be the
year that you really take off not only
within your relationships uh and your
co-creations but also your monetary
manifestations.
Whatever you're receiving is more than
you think that it is. That's what I will
say. But I love you. I appreciate you. I
honor you. Again,
yeah, my face is purging a little bit.
So, y'all are just going to have to bear
with me uh as we are all, you know,
acclimating to this this timeline,
acclimating to this energetic elevated
state. So, again, be gentle with
yourselves, you guys. Make sure that you
are, you know, speaking affirmations
over yourself in your life. Uh making
sure that you're praying over your
relationships, over your uh environment
and your babies and your fur babies. and
make sure that you are just remaining
locked in and focused uh on what is
unfolding now for you. And it's all that
is highly favorable to your empowerment
and expansion. But I love you. I
appreciate you. I miss y'all so much.
It's so good to be back. It's so good to
be back. I love you. I appreciate you. I
honor you. I am so proud of each and
every one of you. And I'm so excited for
everything that's coming through in
2026, knowing damn good and well that it
is due to you. And if I won't see you
over on uh Tik Tok in about 15 minutes,
maybe 30, probably 15, uh then I will
see you again tomorrow. So until the
next time I see you, remain peaceful,
unconditionally loving, stand united,
and remain respectful unless
disrespected. Then check with the Most
High and check your [ __ ] self
before you check a [ __ ] with
grace. And like Sha would say, XXXion
88. If anybody tells you to lay down,
run them the [ __ ] over, but not with
your car. Vroom vroom with your energy
because we have nothing to prove. Our
energy obviously does it for us. And
last, but most definitely not least,
drink your [ __ ] water. It is a
conduit of energy. It will assist you at
this time, especially if you are still
alchemizing or if you are acclimating to
what you have alchemized in the
alignment that you're currently in.
Remain grounded, stay balanced, and
remember who the you are. A co-creative
Godanointed, appointed, divinely
designed child of the cosmos. A
beautiful, extremely powerful soul that
came through and reincarnated in order
to bring massive wave making change to
this world. And you have, but also is
set up and aligned to experience it
simultaneously because as within, so is
your external. So don't be surprised
when everything in your physical reality
shifts rapidly.
You prayed for this. You wished for
this. And now it's here. You deserve
every blessing that comes through. But
know that there's more responsibility
that may be placed on you. Do not move
frivolously with this fortune and these
finances that are being given to you. I
love you and until the next time I see
you. Blessings to you. I love you.