[sighs and gasps] Okay, all my batteries
have failed. Everything has failed. I
have a 26% remaining on that one.
All right, so I'm going to show you guys
something. Show you guys something. If
you ever have to start a generator, a
small generator specifically, at least
the one with the low oil lights or with
an oil shut off. Uh, keep in mind I have
zero W30 in my generator and I am still
going to uh suffer the problem that
you're about to witness. Um, so before I
get into everything, uh, thank you
everybody for supporting my GoFundMe. I
really need it. Um,
things are not awesome. So, let me try
to give you some useful content in
return.
And um
so the GoFundMe is to get a battery so I
don't have to keep doing this.
I'm going to show you what'll happen is
your oil is going to be thick.
I'm at such a temperature right now that
I can't run this machine without a
heater. You'll see here. So there's my
generator and there's a heater stuck to
it. That heater is going right into the
air intake. You see?
[sighs]
So,
I'm having to even heat the oil as it's
running just to keep it running. Okay.
So, here's what we're going to do. Uh
I'll set up the uh
set the camera right over here. You guys
can you guys can kind of see what I'm
doing here. So, I might be able to pull
it without the choke. Nope.
So, we can set the choke.
Pull it.
Going to take the choke off. Okay.
Now, see, it's running right now. Watch
what it'll do.
Watch, watch, watch.
There you go. It just shut off. That's
the low oil light.
The wrong answer is to put more oil in
it because it has the correct amount of
oil in it. What's happening is your oil
pump.
Your oil pump's not picking it up.
It's too solid. It's It's not viscous
enough.
So, you your oil pump's going to keep
shutting you down. And uh you may be
very frustrated wondering
why
won't this thing start? It says there's
low oil. I have oil. I know. Shut down
again. Yep. And what you have to do
Wait till the Wait till the light shuts
off. There you go.
And so what I'm doing is I'm just keep
on turning it on. Keep on turning it on.
Letting that
the engine
eventually get warm enough
to where
it can warm up that oil. The other
answer is to take this,
unplug everything, take it inside, let
the oil loosen up, set it by the wood
stove
about 30 minutes or so,
or you just keep on doing this. Um,
so I'm let I'm doing this to prove a
point to show you
it will keep shutting down.
Just keep restarting it
and it will eventually work. So you can
watch me just kind of do it again and
again.
The worst thing you could ever do in
this situation is add more oil. Uh
what'll happen is now your now your
machine will be it'll work. It'll
instantly start sucking that other oil
up
start sucking through the uh you know
pumping through the oil properly.
Jesus. But
then it's going to be over full.
Uh it's going to develop pressure. It's
going to be overpressurized. It's going
to push oil up uh into your cylinders
and that you don't want.
It's going to push up into your
cylinders and what doesn't burn is going
to go out your exhaust
and then you can
you risk all sorts of issues doing that.
I mean,
you risk all sorts of issues doing that,
so I don't recommend.
It's ridiculous, isn't it? So, this is
why I need that battery. Um, this is one
of the reasons here
just to not have to constantly do this
to beg my machine to work
when I need it to work. You know,
sucks.
Every time I want electricity, this is
how it has to happen.
Just ridiculous.
Oh, come on.
So, thanks to people who supported the
GoFundMe right now. Uh, I'm up tound and
um
I'm still at $134.
Still at $134. Um,
Jesus damn Christ, dude. Start. I need
you to start.
This sucks. Try doing this at like 3:30
in the morning.
Woke up out of bed cold, naked,
trying to get dressed in your [ __ ]
cold ass dark house
to get out here and do this.
This sucks.
But like I said, you know,
worst thing you could do is just add
more oil right now. Just keep on
reefing.
The other answer, like I said, is to
take it inside. But you see how long
it's taking.
This sucks. My life sucks.
For now, it'll get better.
Dude,
stop [ __ ] slamming.
The wind is causing that door to open
and close and slam.
This thing will get there eventually.
All right.
Are we about there? You think? You think
it's going to keep going?
Good.
I think it might. It still might shut
off. So
[sighs]
It's just what it is, dude. You got to
accept your lot in life.
Wait for the damn
It be so nice and I get a battery for
real. Cuz I might get a battery and then
I'll just charge it up
and then I don't have to [ __ ] do
this.
I could,
you know,
the one battery gives me three days
worth of power. Three days
instead of having to do this.
And then there's the waste of fuel. Like
it cost me $75 a day.
Like $87 to $8 a day.
just for electricity
unsustainable.
I think it might actually stay going
this time.
Yeah, that's why I get that heater stuck
right on that intake to heat up that oil
on the oil pump. So,
yeah, I have that little heater, little
500 watt
stuck right on the uh
stuck right on the air intake there to
warm up the heat pump or oil pump, you
know? You know what I'm saying?
Oh,
[snorts] freaking cold.
It's still pretty warm in here. You know
what is it in here? 78°. Yeah, cuz I
just get this when I'm at home. Be nice
if I could start working from home again
cuz I I'm missing out on money. This is
ridiculous. But um
yeah, when I'm here, I can get that
thing I can get the wood stove roaring.
78 degrees. That's what I want. I want
it more like 84.
[sighs] But yeah, that's what I have to
do. Just fight it like that. And that
that's merely to um to charge the
laptop.
Yeah.
And to have a light.
Real great use of resources, right?
Yeah.
Yeah. So, look in the description.
GoFundMe. I know I'm harping on it, but
I'm I'm [ __ ] desperate.
You see kind of why a little bit, you
know?