What's going on Gemini? How are you
doing? Hope you're doing very well. This
is the Autistic Mystic and this is going
to be your weekly reading for December
31st through January 4th, 2026. So, in
this reading, Gemini, we're going to
take a look at your overall general
energy. Some things you do not see
coming and also get some advice from
your angels and spirit guides for you
and so much more regarding the 31st to
the 4th, the first week of the new year
essentially. So, thank you so much for
being here. As always, you are very
welcome here in this space with me as we
go through this reading. I really do
appreciate you in advance for taking the
time to check this reading out. And if
it does resonate with you, definitely
smash that like button, subscribe down
below if you have not already for future
updates. That would also be greatly
appreciated over here. So, without
further ado, I'm going to pull the
energy for you and see what's cracking
and see what's coming through. So, let's
go. As always, I would like to thank the
angels,
the interdimensional beings and the
spirit guides who are overseeing this
the divination for the sign of Gemini.
Okay.
So the first thing that is coming
through Gemini is that the self-doubt
that you are currently experiencing is
not a match, not a vibrational match to
what needs to be said or done for the
31st of December to the 4th of January.
The self-doubt that you are experiencing
is not a match to what needs to be said
and done. You need to become more like
Neo in the Matrix. You need to think
outside of the box right now because
there's a lot of advice for you. The
energy that you need to embody more of
is all about confidence, immunity,
healing, and integration. So, first
things first, having confidence in
yourself. Also, you are not as
vulnerable right now to certain energies
that may be trying to adhere to you at
this time. The more you think that you
are vulnerable, the more that you will
become vulnerable in some sort of way.
So, you're not as vulnerable as you
think to something, but there needs to
be some sort of putting together,
putting the pieces back together because
um it's showing me that in some way,
shape, or form, you're essentially
fragmented right now within your own
psyche or within your own soul. There's
definitely fragments that need to be put
back together, put back in place, but
it's not going to be an easy road for
you to do that. But the way that you do
that for a lot of you is basically just
finding a way to get your confidence
back, doing something that you're
already good at or starting something
new. For a lot of you, this is all about
um the idea of a fresh new start
relative to something in your life that
will allow you to spiritually integrate.
It's been a really interesting journey
for me as I ride this Saturn return
journey. And a lot of what's happening
is that um it seems like there's like
walk in soul like from a spiritual
perspective I'm having like all these
aspects of my own consciousness that I
knew I would eventually get to basically
like take on a whole persona take on a
whole being a whole separate being
that's basically like a walk-in soul.
It's like my own consciousness. I have a
different conscience about things
because of where I'm going and what I'm
doing and what I need to do compared to
my old integrated state of consciousness
that was good for that period of time.
So for you the advice that's what's
happening is that if many of you have
like um a lot of anxiety about life at
this time for a lot of you it's about
the idea that you could be having a you
are having a spiritual integration that
allows you to experience the opposite of
some sort of trauma that you've been
going through.
Okay. So and that may not look how you
think it looks. It may not look as
exciting. I definitely think that's one
of the things here with this reading
Gemini for you from the 31st to um the
uh 4th is that it's kind of like back to
square one. You may not
know what to do because of different
fragments. You know, the energy that you
need more of, the energy that you need
more of to embody for your own highest
good. One of these cards is the oracle
card of integration.
And integration is all about bringing
two seemingly opposite things that are
highly fragmented and polarized back
into one single working unit or at least
a cooperative unit, but basically
becoming whole and complete within parts
of yourself that are going in two
different directions. And you may have a
lot of these. This is especially what
Gemini is known for. So, a lot of your
confidence is going to occur actually
through the idea that you think your
life is effed up. You think you're the
only one going through what you're going
through. You're not. Pain likes to
convince you that you're the only one
going through. No one has it as bad as
me. I'm the only one going through this,
etc. We are all going through basically
a collective nightmare at this moment
from a certain perspective. And one
thing pain likes to do is to make you
think that you're going through it
alone. But you may not be as alone as
you think. Especially in terms of
how you navigate this. This is a big
choice point for you. I want to
emphasize this that on a practical
level. It seems like you have the whole
world in the palm of your hands in some
sort of risky
new life decision going forward or you
have a safe option that you can
basically basically cash in on and be
relatively good. But there's some advice
here that your safe option may be taken
away from you.
Uh
there's a quote coming into my mind
about like it's it's like I don't want
to scare any of you but it's like
literally it's like do you have a
backup? And I don't believe in
retirement, but do you have a backup
retirement plan? And it's cool if you
do, but do you have a backup retirement
plan when your retirement plan doesn't
work anymore?
Because there's some sort of risky new
right of passage that's amazing that's
standing in front of you. Or you have
the the safe bet that you have basically
been cashing in on a certain plan of
your life, a certain way that you
thought things were going to go. Your
challenge is that that set plan is not
as set anymore at all.
Something that you've been building up
towards planting the seeds hoping that
they would sprout. The honest assessment
of this reading is that there is a
possibility that they can still sprout.
But there's also a big possibility that
they just completely get taken away from
you, something that you've been
building. So there needs to be a plan B
for there needs to be a backup plan for
every backup plan. And I don't want to
confuse you to make you more fragmented.
Maybe there's just needs to be one new
risky option that you consider in your
reality in some sort of way. I'll
explain why this is happening in a
moment. But let's go to your
opportunity. This reading came out with
two cards in the opportunity, two cards
in the challenge. So your opportunity is
the justice card and the ace of wands.
And the justice card is also the
opportunity for Aquarius. So there may
be a connection there. The Ace of Wands
is all about a fresh new start relative
to inspiration, healing the spirit as
well. It's funny that I talked about
walk-in souls in this reading. There are
certain aspects of your consciousness
that are that are ready to to come on
board in order to help you heal. So it
may feel like you have taken on a
completely new persona. A completely new
side of you is ready to start taking
control of the show. The question is,
are you ready to let that side take
control of the show or not? Um, this is
all about bringing balance to the realm
of thought relative to your own
confidence in life, your ability to take
risks, your ability to act on
inspiration. This is all of your
opportunity because there's something
that you need to do in order to remove
the self-doubt that is not currently a
match to the situation. But even if you
remove the self-doubt, you're still
stuck in a risky scenario. And that's
just how it's going right now according
to an accurate reader. So in your
challenge you have the six of swords and
the knight of cups.
So I do feel that there's some sort of
idealistic vision that you've had that
is now becoming less and less
idealistic, less and less romantic, less
and less realistic for you.
And now it's time to move on to a new
vision, to a new idealism, to a new
thing that you set your sights out on.
Now, for some of you, quite frankly, you
could just be going through a breakup
within your relationships. And this is
the challenge when it comes to your
romance. There could be a shift from one
partner to another or something like
that or the want, the desire for that.
It doesn't have to be like that, but
that could be what's going on with this.
The six of swords and the knight of cups
could be something about you idealizing
your reality that has to come to an end
and you need to set a new goal and start
idealizing something else. But it's
really up to you because you have a
major choice point and remember that
you're not as vulnerable as you think
you are at this time. You do have a lot
of um opportunities to regain your
confidence at this time, but the safer
option is super risky for you at this
time. And so is the new option. There is
no safe option for you at this time. But
guess what? You did not come here to
arrive at death safely in this reality.
All that you do when you play it safe is
you get to your bed with uh your your
deathbed with regrets.
um
sometimes.
But let me show you the so so romantic
issues, not knowing whether you should
move on from a romantic situation or not
because a lot of you have a cold partner
that you're not connecting with
emotionally.
For the mas for the Gemini um men out
there, there can be a real cold [ __ ] in
your life that just makes you feel
emotionally horrible.
They might they just make you feel
emotionally horrible. They make you feel
horrible. They make your heart closed
basically.
For the Gemini women out there, there's
probably a man in your life that is very
cold as well that gives you a lot of
emotional problems. So for a lot of you,
you are stuck in the situation. I will
say this song, should I stay or should I
go? And that of course is a featured
song in Stranger Things which I have
been on the real life set of
gaslight set non- gaslight set you know
it's all there.
Um,
let's go to your overall general energy.
And this is the choice point that I was
pointing out to you.
You
have the two of wands, which is a choice
point, a safer option behind you,
including that seven of pentacles. You
have the four of wands ahead of you, a
right of passage, which requires
enthusiasm, a risk of danger, but you
are in the right frequency. So, you're
not in a bad space. You do have options
at this time.
Um, you do have options at this time,
but you need to follow the one that will
increase your confidence basically at
this time and and induce a state of
healing and
integrating yourself in some sort of
way. cuz you may have a really split
personality that someone in your life is
basically just like causing you to
become to have to become more split. And
I don't think it's your fault. I feel
like there's a there's a situation in
your life or you have two different
sides to yourself. You keep getting
pushed into one side of yourself because
you're like you need to do that in this
reality or something like that. Um
so be aware of that
in
your uh
what you don't see coming. You have the
king of swords, the lovers card, and the
five of cups.
So yeah, a lot of coldness, not being on
the same page on an emotional level. For
some of you, this is definitely going to
have to do with a soulmate experience.
Lovers, you know, reality feels harsh,
reality feels bleak. I want to go out on
a limb and say that a lot of you are
for some of you, you're not with the
right person and you already know that,
but you have to be with them for some
sort of reason right now. For a lot of
you, and I don't want to make this sound
like a romantic novel because you don't
need a soulmate to be whole and
complete. You don't need it, but a lot
of your life force energy is somehow
being drained by like not being with
someone that you're meant to be with.
And for some of you, you feel like
you're caught in a lose-lose situation
relative to this choice that you need to
make on a romantic level
or just regaining your confidence to go
out on a quest because some of you you
need to re completely
um you need to completely revamp your
requ your your quest in life. Start a
new quest in life with this justice card
and the ace of wands. Do something bold.
Fortune favors the bold. But
in your advice, you have the five of
pentacles, the nine of cups, and the
seven of swords.
So, here's the cautionary tale part of
this reading. There may be something
that you need to do to outsmart
someone. For a lot of you, you're being
schemed. You're being tricked into a
situation that you didn't even realize
you were being schemed or tricked into.
A lot of this is saying, "Watch out."
out. For some of you, you need to like
realize that something that you've been
investing in, that you thought was going
to go good, that you thought could you
could work through, that you could
overcome now is drying up,
but you still have a chance to make it
work with that, but it seems like it's
drying up.
And then you have this seven of swords
with your nine of pentac, your nine of
um nine of cups. So this does talk about
the idea of trickery relative to
synchronicity. The idea of being on the
lookout for negative synchronicity.
Sometimes following signs and
synchronicities lead you straight to the
thing that you want that will increase
your expansion. Sometimes it will lead
you straight to hell. Because the idea
is that if you are always at the effect
of what you are receiving and following
the signs like a blind or like a dog,
then it may lead you to something that
will lead to your expansion. But if you
can kind of cultivate this is what I
want. I know what I want. I know who I
want. I know what I want, etc. It will
just streamline you there. And I'm not
saying it's your fault for that because
right now there's a big, as we know,
there's a big AI arms race going on
and that filters down into citizen life.
So unfortunately, there's a lot of signs
and synchronicities that are being put
in your path by people or groups of
being or by AI beings or whatever that
do not have your best interest in hand
to basically make you think you are
doing the right thing by following the
signs and synchronicities when may or
may you're leading straight to the path
of hell. So this is about the advice is
that is that there's people trying to
scheme your synchronicities.
There's there's beings there's people
trying to scheme your synchronicities,
trying to put something there, trying to
gaslight you in some sort of way. For
others of you, it's letting you know
that you need to come up with a new plan
before your old plan gets completely
dried up in some sort of way.
That's really what I feel about this
reading. So, now let's go ahead and get
into um some more of it.
Let's go ahead and clarify why this two
of wands, this choice point, you do have
the tower and the
uh wheel of fortune coming in.
Why is the two of wands here for you
in your overall general energy?
Knight of wands. This is definitely
about the contemplation of a new
adventure with that justice card and the
ace of wands. A new beginning. A lot of
fiery energy relative to this choice
point. Having confidence in yourself,
but there could be travel involved with
this. There could be a new journey that
you have to give you an old journey
you're giving up a new journey you're
you're going on. Why is the two of wo of
wands here for you?
There's something about this investment
or something leading to betrayal or
something like that. The seven of
pentacles is clarified by the page of
wands, the devil, the seven of cups, and
the nine of swords.
So, it seems like this is your new
point. Like when I shuffled this, they
jumped right on the direction. This ace,
this knight of wands jumped right into
the future, right into the more risky
option that leads you to
the four of wands and having to navigate
a scheming synchronicity timeline. It
does seem like some like the danger of
this is this. Whatever your backup plan
is or whatever set plan you have is or
something like that, Gemini. Um it seems
to be leading you to a nightmarish
situation with this devil card, nine of
swords
and the and the seven of cups. It seems
to be leading to emotional heartbreak,
confusion,
a and things like that. and a lot of
immaturity or something like that.
For some of you, this is about the idea
of like completing something or going
back in time.
But at the same time, this is about
something that you've been investing in.
The safer option is no longer going to
work because of some sort of reason.
So you have a risky option in front of
you, but that's honestly what's looking
like the really only option for you.
So you have a choice for a lot of you.
You also have a choice to be with
someone who's a little bit emotionally
cold
versus uh emotional wreck.
Um,
but
don't judge a book by its cover.
Let's go ahead now and uh keep going.
Let's clarify that justice and ace of
wands in your opportunity here.
Yeah, you have that five of cups popping
right out on that five of pentacles. You
also have the five of cups and what you
don't see coming. So, this is now a
duplicate. So, there is some sort of
justice ace of wands with the star card
and the five of cups. So this is all
about healing, integrating your sadness,
integrating your sadness here, Gemini,
in some sort of way. A new beginning
that helps you move on from the past
because a lot of times this is a change
to your emotions. The number five has to
do with change, traveling. The cups have
to do with emotions. There's something
that you're you're trying to drink these
cups. They already they're done. And
there's a fresh spring of water right
here that's just flowing constantly. and
it's going to lead to you to a new
beginning. But a lot of you are like
like and I don't mean to be fish
I don't mean to be fish I
I don't mean to be rude
but some of you are trying to pick up
cups that are completely empty and drink
from them.
So you need to become confident enough
so that you don't end up in that
situation. I don't I just don't
understand you.
Judgement on a scheme
there. There's definitely judgement on a
seven of swords energy going on right
now for you.
Also,
this is about your social mask falling
off.
You see, it all just hit me.
This is your life with your safer
option. This is your social mask that
you put on and act like everything is
just fine. Everything's fine.
Everything's good. Everything's good.
And then this
is the advice
is to exit this cycle of social mask
which doesn't lead to confidence or
healing. I just call judgment on your
seven of swords. A lot of you, yes, this
is seven of swords, judgment on a
scheme, particularly a synchronistic
scheme
more. So, this is about it's judgment
day to stop wearing a mask
and to just freaking
six of swords, knight of cups this
situation. At least this is in your
challenge. Why it's in your challenge?
Well,
page of swords.
You've been thinking about it.
Let's go ahead and clarify this six of
swords. Actually, you know what? Let's
leave that alone. I think we said enough
about that. Um,
let's clarify that nine of cups, that
social mask or that negative
synchronicity or that thing that you
need to jump on the wave of.
Yes, you need to defend your future
right now from something really bad
here.
Seven of swords immediately blocking out
this five of pentacles and you kind of
getting away with all the goods. We have
a lot of really positive cards coming
out right here. So I think it's judgment
day that there needs to be a boundary
put up to whatever this five of
pentacles frequency is. Whenever I show
it to you, what is this frequency when
you when I put it up? What is this to
you? That's the energy that you need to
put up a boundary with in your reality.
Any closing remarks?
Yeah, it's time to admit to the pain
that you're actually in and channel that
potential aggression in order to make
those changes into your life. Channel
your confidence in order to make that
change in your life. So, with that being
said, I'm going to conclude this
reading. Thank you so much. Peace.