There's like this deafening silence
right now.
If this message found you or if you
clicked on this message because
the title of it called you in,
then this message is 100% for you. And
this is a message for people who are not
in divine partnership yet. Okay? Like
this is a pretty obvious message. You're
not in a relationship right now or yet,
right?
And this is one of those messages where
the angels are coming through really
strongly
and they're telling me
they're saying
use your willpower
for this message and if you make it to
the end of this message it'll make
sense.
But we're going to start in a place that
might not make any sense to you.
So, what I'm hearing
is that the angels are scheming. The
angels are scheming. Okay,
this is about love.
But the angels are saying that they
pulled you into this message
specifically using the title of this
message
because
it's actually the complete opposite.
So stay with me. Like I said,
patience,
good things come to those who wait.
Okay.
I'm feeling
a sense of
anger at love.
I'm feeling a sense of anger at
yourself.
And I'm feeling a sense of I almost want
to say like there's just this part of
you that's like rising that's like a a
little bit angry at the universe but
like not at the same time. Okay.
And this energy is um
swirling around inside of you
and creating this deafening silence. I
feel like there is a part of you
that feels kind of disgusted by the
thought of love right now. And when I
say disgusted, it's because love hasn't
stopped teaching you lessons.
Love hasn't softened. It's not that love
hasn't softened. I feel like love has
softened if you really look at your
history of love. But I'm getting love
hasn't softened in the way that you
feel like you know that it's supposed to
soften. Okay.
And I feel like this is a
funny message because it's almost like
the angels called you here to be like,
"We're going to tell you some truths
right now. We're going to give you some
truth bombs.
So, as I was driving this morning, I was
like, "Okay, I'm just going to open my
channel to the angels and I'm going to
see what they want to say and I'm going
to give them space and I'm going to give
them time because I didn't even know if
I was going to channel today. I've woken
up super late. Everything has gone so
much slower than I expected it to." And
I feel like that's very um reflective of
your journey in love.
I feel like there's going to be a bit of
a throat block coming through here in
this message. So, if I'm coughing or if
I'm like um slowing down to take drinks
and I drink or breathe, it's because
there is a lot
coming up and clearing in this message.
Okay. And
again, so I was driving this morning
and I was like,
I'm going to get a coffee today. coffee
could be significant for someone. It's
like I'm gonna get a coffee. And as I
was going to get my coffee, I heard the
angels say.
Now's not the time.
They didn't say exactly that. There's
like a white bird on the fence right
now. This could be significant for
someone. Hi, buddy. Are you trying to
say hi to people?
He literally like peeked his neck out
and he was like,
"Um,
okay.
Love has been slower for you than I feel
like it has been for other people."
And I think it pisses you off to be
completely honest. I think it like it
doesn't really because I feel like
you've been softening into that but
there's also this part of you I feel
like there's this really divine sense of
anger inside of you or rage like a
divine rage that has been coming up
inside of you recently and it's funny
because it's tied to love and it's also
tied to your love for yourself. So, what
I heard from the angels is that this
message called you in because there's a
part of you that's like, "Oh, is love
coming?" Like, ew, like I don't want
love, but like, "Oh, I do want love."
You know, like there's this part of you
that's like you're opening yourself for
it. And at the exact same time, you're
angry at it, but it's because you're
angry at yourself in the terms of love.
Okay? It's not like you're like looking
at yourself and you're like, I'm not I'm
not happy with you. Okay? It's not that
kind of an energy.
I told you mucus. I don't know.
There's going to be clearing in this
message. I'm like I can I can feel that.
But the angels called you into this
message to basically say
it's not time yet.
But they called you in by making you
think it's time.
So, that's what I mean by they're being
a little sneaky. They're being a little
sneaky with you because they're
basically trying to sit you down and say
right now, the only person that you're
supposed to be in love with is yourself.
Right now, the only person that you're
supposed to be showing up for is
yourself.
right now, the only person that you're
supposed to be diving into and giving
your energy to is yourself. And I think
that that's um I think you know this,
which is why this is like hard. And I
also think that recently
the journey of love for you has been
slower than expected, has had weird
twists or turns and has really brought
up this anger inside of you or this part
of you that's like feeling that divine
rage. And it's brought it up because
there's a part of yourself which has
been abandoning yourself in order to
make love happen. Okay? When love is
meant to happen for you, you're not
supposed to make it happen.
And this is a super uncomfortable
energy. And I'm moving the camera a
bunch because you know me, that's just
what happens. I move the camera when I'm
really uncomfortable. Um,
but I'm also getting this energy of
nothing is as it seems. So, it's funny
because all this all this divine rage
that's coming up in you right now in
terms of love is coming up for a reason.
And it's coming up because you're
finally ready to face the ways that
you've abandoned yourself in the pursuit
of love. Okay? Because this is very
significant because all of your energy
and essence is meant to be redirected
back onto you and
it's a hard decision to make.
It is hard to choose yourself. And the
way that your divine partner comes in is
through the choosing of yourself. And
what's funny is that I'm getting this
vibe of like you kind of have this part
of you that's also angry at everything
that's being said right now because
you're like I have been choosing myself.
Like I have been showing up for myself
more than I've ever shown up for myself.
Ooh, confirmation in my entire life.
Like I have showed up for myself. What
are you talking about? Like I've worked
so hard to show up for myself and I'm
getting that energy. Okay. And that's
that divine rage, right? Let that come
up
first. You're allowed to be angry.
You're also allowed to witness where the
anger stems from. Okay, which is that
self-abandonment.
And that's hard. Okay, this isn't an
easy energy.
But what I am getting is that
you're supposed to be
in this journey right now, which you're
already in, but you're in this journey
where you're learning to choose yourself
over
I'm almost getting like over the pursuit
of love
in ways that you know, love isn't fully
meant to arrive for you. Okay, so
kind of vague, but kind of specific.
It's almost as if you've been choosing
yourself and then you get to this point
where you've been choosing yourself and
then an opportunity comes in to love.
And in the pursuit of love, you choose
love and you choose that experience
of loving
But I almost get this vibe that you're
someone who just like loves like I feel
like and this is I'm getting such a hard
energy like such a throat block because
I feel like when you love you give away
love instead of loving through loving
yourself and choosing yourself. And I
think that's the lesson that you're
learning right now. And it's not really
that you're like being taught this hard
lesson.
It's more so that you're learning to
love yourself, to love others, and to
give to yourself, to give to others, and
to choose yourself,
to choose others, and for others to
choose you. And it's in this journey
that it it's so it's so important
for you to be learning to choose
yourself right now. Even though it feels
hard, even though you're angry, even
though you're pissed off at love or
blaming whatever concept you want to
blame, right? whatever comes up inside
of you, even though you're wanting to do
that, it's this this is so important for
you to be feeling these things. And
that's what I'm feeling from your angels
right now is that this is such an
important time for you to be in this
energy and to let all of this come up
because something that is happening in
this journey specifically for you is
this really beautiful unmasking of the
ways that you've abandoned yourself and
this really beautiful witnessing of the
versions of yourself that haven't shown
up for you so that you can be more of
you. And I feel like it's so important
because your divine lover
is going to love all of you. And they
are not meant to show up until you love
all of you. And in order to love all of
you, you have to unmask all the versions
of you. All the versions of you that are
angry, all the versions of you that are
sad, all of the versions of you that
have abandoned yourself. And you have to
merge with them. And this is that
process that is happening right now. And
it's happening through your pursuit of
love and learning how to be in the
pursuit of loving thyself in order to
love others. And I feel like this is so
important, so significant for you
because there's just something so
profound about the connection that
you're truly meant to be in. And
I just get this vibe that you have a
deeper purpose in love. like you have
it's almost like I feel like you really
came here with a like part of your sole
purpose being on earth is to love. Okay,
it's not as simple as like yeah love is
cool but it's like it's part of your
written prophecy to love and to love in
a way that teaches others how to love
fully. And in order to do that, I just
feel like this is so powerful for you
because in order to do that, you have to
go through the heroine journey or the
hero's journey. Sorry. I've never done
female before male before. That's funny.
That's cute. Um, but you have to go
through that journey in order to
be that person that teaches. Okay. So I
like your angels are basically saying
that you have to experience it first if
you're bound to teach it by being okay.
And so that's why it feels um s like
such a challenge. Like love for you
feels like a challenge.
And love for you feels like a challenge
that keeps getting steeper. It's like
you're you thought you were climbing a
mountain and then you thought you were
climbing a snowy mountain and then you
got to the deeper parts of the snow and
it got colder and suddenly suddenly the
oxygen became minimal and you were like
I thought this was hard before but like
now I can't breathe
and then you realize oh I'm climbing
Mount Everest.
You're like, "My my challenge is Mount
Everest.
What the [ __ ] bro?"
And you're like reserving oxygen at the
same time. And you're like,
I don't know why this is so good, but
I'm just
It's funny because it's not funny. And
there's so much anger in this and like
irritation
in this journey that you're on that it's
actually funny. Like I feel like there
are moments in your journey of the
pursuit of love where you have genuinely
looked at everything or had things
happen in your journey of love and
you've been like this is [ __ ] You
know, like I just get this vibe that you
think it's funny but it's like not at
the same time. Like I feel like you've
been like real irritated and like mad at
love and like whatever, right? like
however it has come up for you, I'm
getting this vibe of like it's just been
like not cool. But then I think that
there's these really random moments that
you have where you sit back and you
laugh and you go, "This is a [ __ ]
joke, bro." Like, okay, I see I see how
my angels are probably laughing on the
other side at me trying to do this love
thing because what the [ __ ] bro?
Like I just get this this vibe from you.
And I do think that you have this really
great humor to you. I feel like that is
so significant.
But here's the thing. Okay,
now we can start talking about like the
love part because if you've made it this
far again, like I said that in the
beginning of this message and the angels
told me to go so slow with this energy
cuz they were like it's only the people
that have the willpower to stick around
that are really meant to receive this
message. And they told me that on the
drive. They they showed me how to start
this channelneled message and how to go
slow with it and breathe with it. Okay?
Because
that's also in representation of your
patience. Like your patience is about to
be rewarded, but you're still climbing
Mount Everest.
Like I'm getting this energy that like
you are about to be rewarded in
significant ways in love in a partner, a
divine partner that you know is meant
for you, that you've had dreams about,
that you have literally always felt for
you. They're going to blow your [ __ ]
mind. Like they're going to show you
that there are worlds that you have
never really truly like understood exist
when they arrive.
It's happening for you, okay? And it's I
am getting that it's sooner than you
think it is, but it's also set up in
your reality to arrive in a way that you
will never know when it's going to
happen. And that's like that's really
hard, too, cuz I can feel for you. This
is so good that your lover is set up to
be hidden from you until the day they
are meant to arrive. So, you're not
going to [ __ ] know, bro. Like, you're
you're not going to see it coming. And
that's the best part about this entire
thing. I literally feel like you're h
What's that one song? The white bird is
back over there.
It's called Love in the Dark.
I can't play it for you, but that's kind
of what I'm feeling. Like I feel like
you're like learning to love in the
unknown, like in the dark, and you're
not supposed to see what's coming next
for you. But there's this really really
significant journey that you're on right
in this exact moment when this message
has found you. Right.
And I'm also getting an ache in the back
of my masculine side.
Like I almost feel like
I feel like love has pronounced you
to be the leader
in a partnership that was always meant
to be masculine and feminine. And I'm
almost getting that like you have had to
take on the role of the opposing
end. And I I feel like a majority of
this collective is feminine. I'm going
to be honest with you. Um, but there are
some masculines here. So, I'm going to
keep it um open to all energies, but I'm
just feeling that like for the majority
or for everyone in this collective
literally, you have had to take on the
opposing end of the energy of your
divine partner
because you were almost like what
they're telling me is that you
This is so cool.
They're saying that you have lived both
ends of a divine partnership through
yourself. And that's what's still
happening right now where you've taken
on the role of both your divine partner
and yourself in this connection. So that
when this person does arrive also,
you're going to have a level of
compassion, respect, and gratitude for
them in your reality because you
understand how much effort and love they
put in because you've done it for
yourself and done it in the ways that
they're going to show up. Like I just
feel like there's a part of you that
like almost doesn't even believe in love
anymore. It's not that you don't believe
in love, okay, that's kind of harsh, but
I I feel like there's this part of you
that's just like kind of fed up with
love and you're just like, I'm kind of
like sick of wanting it, you know? Like
there's a part of you that's just like
annoyed at the fact that you still want
love. But deep down, you know that
you're meant to experience love. And so
this is just so significant because when
it does come in for you, it is going to
literally like you're going to have so
much gratitude for it because of how
much you have experienced both ends of
it. And also the parts of it that like
you in your divine like union are meant
to be more melty in one end of it.
you've done both ends for so long that
you're going to you're never ever going
to forget. And I feel like that's really
important too because there's a part of
you that like when you enter into love,
you may have like a fear that like Yeah,
I feel this coming through.
Hold on.
I feel like there's a part of you that
has a fear that when love does finally
come in and you really want it and you
really
know it's your person, I feel like
there's you're someone who's going to
know who your person is when you meet
them. Oo, that's a confirmation, too.
Like, you're going to know in your bones
that that's your person. And yet, I feel
like there's a part of you that's going
to worry that you're going to fall out
of love.
like and I I think that's one of your
fears actually. Like it really feels
like it's coming up as like a fear in
love is that there's a part of you that
worries that you won't continue to fall
more and more in love because there's a
part of you that I feel like you've
experienced this in past relationships
or uh connections where you've been able
to love fall in love fall so deeply in
love and then and then fall out of love.
I feel like that's been a repetitive
pattern and you I don't think you have
ever found someone that you've fallen
more in love with over time like again
and again and again and I think that
that's because you haven't met your
divine person yet and that's also hard
because it's almost like your your your
reality has taught you that or made you
think I don't want to say like really
taught you because there's a part of you
that knows deeper but your reality has
made you think that or has created this
fear inside of you that you don't know
if there is someone out there that will
rise to the occasion of you and
continue to be someone that you want to
rem meet over and over and over and
refell in love with over and over and
over and over. Like it almost feel like
there's a part of you that almost like
again like you feel fed up with love and
you almost like don't believe it
anymore. Even though there's a part of
you because this is such a part of your
purpose in this world. There's a part of
you that knows better and knows stronger
and knows more divinely that that it's
there. And so when you get mad at it,
it's almost like this reflective Hold
on. It's it's almost like this
reflective energy that happens for you
where you get angry at love, but then
you get angry at yourself because you
know that love is there. And so instead,
you're just like getting mad in this
circle and then it gets like I feel like
there's this big part of love and the
anger that you feel with love that gets
like turned on to yourself and I think
that that's something that you're also
growing through cuz how long is this
message going to be? because this is a
much deeper, longer message than I
expected it to be. Um,
what I'm feeling for you is that right
now, cuz let's talk about right this
moment, right?
Because I feel like right now in this
moment, you're like, "Ew, what the
fuck?" And I feel like there's this
energy that you have where you're just
kind of like fade or faded. There's this
part of you that's just like
irritated with love where you're just
like I'm done. Like I almost get this
like fed up energy. That's what I was
trying to say. Fed up. It's a fed up
energy at love. And it's actually,
again, we already talked about this.
It's a fed up energy at the version of
you that has abandoned yourself every
single time love has been an option. and
you've abandoned yourself in order to
try and attain that love even though you
knew deeper down that that wasn't it for
you that there was something deeper out
there and I think that that's something
that's also really hard for you because
I think you understand that there are
certain lessons that you asked for in
love to of course bring you to this part
of yourself like again this like this
present storyline that you're living
is about you
falling in love with yourself. It's
about you choosing yourself. And that's
why you're getting these opportunities
also to love where it's almost like
you're getting these amazing
opportunities that look like shiny gold
stars, right? And you're like, "Oh my
god, I want the gold star. I want the
gold star." And it's almost like the
gold star is twodimensional.
It's a sticker, but you thought it was a
3D opportunity at love. You know what I
mean? Like you thought it was like a 5D
opportunity. You were like, "Oh my god."
But then you give all of yourself over
to reaching for this star and when you
reach it, you peel it off and you're
like, "It's a sticker. It's a 2D
sticker."
You're like, "Okay, I'm mad. I'm mad.
Why did I just completely unoute myself
in order to reach this 2D sticker?" And
so I feel like you've had a lot of these
experiences in love where you've done
this over and over and over again. And
you've done this because you're you're
getting these experiences to basically
reroute you on the path of choosing
yourself. Okay, my battery I'm going to
change it really quick. Anyways,
you're on these experiences. is you're
getting all these experiences so that
you can be rerouted back again and again
and again to choosing yourself. And I
feel like this message is arriving for
you at a really it's an irritable time,
but it's an awesome time because this
message is arriving when you're finally
feeling like you're not going to take
the gold star. Like there's a part of
you that's like, I don't want another 2D
star. I want to stay on my path of
choosing myself and a star will appear
on my path. I'm seeing Mario Kart right
now like a star when they're driving and
they're like it's just right there
available for you. That's what I feel is
coming for you. Okay. And I I do just
keep getting this message and this vibe
that like right now I know that like
everyone wants to hear like your
soulmate's coming and they're right
around the corner and they're going to
show up for you and they're going to be
here for you. And
this is not that message. It's not that
that's not true, but this message is
your soulmate will you will not know
they're coming till the day that they
show up. And that's the honest truth of
it. And the honest truth of it is that
they're not going to show up unless you
choose yourself. So this message is
pretty much also your angels cheering
you on and giving you guidance to say
choose you. Like if you want to feel
chosen, if you want a partner that's
going to choose you, choose you first
and stick the stick to the guns. You
know what I mean? Like
do not veer off your own path and let a
gold star concept pull you away from
your divine destiny because this is such
a big lesson for you and it's almost
like your partner I feel is also on this
journey where like they keep getting
disappointed by love too and it's
because you guys are meant for each
other. Like I know that I know that
there's all that energy that's like are
there really soulmates and are people
really meant for us and like don't you
just choose them and all the reasons
that you could say in your head is to
get mad at at love again, right? But
what I'm feeling is that there really is
something so divine about you
specifically
and your your purpose in love. I feel
like this is a message for a collective
of beings that are genuinely meant to
teach in love and teach in love by being
in love and by finding love in a very
specific way. And I feel like that's a
lesson or like a something that you're
meant to continue to teach throughout
the rest of your life. And your story is
going to be so powerful in that journey.
like your story and the way that you
talk about love, especially in the years
to come. I feel like especially because
there's that throat block that we had
come through too. Anytime that there's a
throat block, I think it has to do with
the fact that your voice is so powerful
and you're meant to speak. Okay? And I
feel like you're meant to speak upon
love. You're going to be telling stories
throughout your life, maybe even some of
you for mass collectives
about the ways that you found love. And
it's really important that the story
that you're telling is about how you
chose yourself first. And I feel like
that's part of your divine destiny of
love because you came here also at this
time on earth in order to bring love to
a new a new
I'm hearing dimension like to basically
like create a new level of love that
exists on this planet and that has to
happen through loving thyself and you're
one of the I'm getting like you could be
a thought leader, but I'm getting like a
thought leader in terms of love in this
world. Um, so it's almost like you're
one of the first wave of people that's
here to tell a story about love that has
been
unwritten or written over is what I'm
getting. So, it's almost like your story
of love is going to be a story that
writes
or rewrites a concept that has been long
forgotten about love that has been
removed from history books about love
that has been written over or unwritten.
I'm getting confirmation of this, too.
So, I feel like I also like get the vibe
that like this comes from a soul that
has
a dimensional history is what I'm
hearing. So, I feel like you could be a
very old soul, but I'm getting that your
soul may have lived in many places other
than just Earth. Okay? feel like your
soul is dimensionally historic and
that's why you have the memory in you
already to tell a story and experience a
story of love in this way and it's to
bring it back. I also feel like
there is a lot of that happening on
earth at this time where there's a lot
of historic souls that have knowledge
deeper inside them in their aosic
history that has been forgotten,
unwritten or written over by humanity.
And I feel like a lot of these teachings
and this knowledge that has always
existed but has been forgotten is being
brought back through souls like yours
which are meant to
retell the story and make new history.
Like I Ooh, I just got full body chills
for that. It's like in the concept of
Earth, you're going to be making history
with these stories that you're living to
tell, but they're actually such a
historic natural phenomenon that has
existed before, but has been unwritten
by um Earth Earth society.
That is so [ __ ] cool, bro. I have
like also sworn a lot in this message.
I'm so sorry. Pardon my French. Um,
this was a cool message. I
hold strong, my friend.
I actually really feel like this is
going to be like got a message the other
day that was like the new you or this
version of you is about to shatter the
paradigm. And I really feel like that is
so true for this part of this journey,
this part of your story as well, because
I feel like this is that moment where
you stop taking turns off of your own
path to grab stars that look 3D but end
up being two-dimensional or look 5D and
end up being two-dimensional, right?
Like this is that's going to be such a
this is such a big time for you because
you're choosing you. And that's so
incredibly powerful. I don't think you
even realize how powerful that is
because you may even have confirmation
of this in your physical world where
like certain moves that you're making
right now like some people are looking
at you and being like, "Oh, that's like
actually really [ __ ] cool that you're
doing that." Like that's actually like
really inspirational. Like, and you
might have confirmation of that through
people in your life where you're like,
"Oh, like this is huge. Like this is a
big deal that like and I'm not doing
this for anyone. and I'm doing this for
me. And also, I feel like there's
another little message here about this
anger that you've been feeling, this
divine anger. And I feel like again,
it's an opportunity. I don't know why
this is coming through again, but it's
an opportunity for you to look at
yourself and hold yourself in all the
ways that you have abandoned yourself.
Okay?
because you have literally gone off path
and that was a version of you that
abandoned your rightful
um abundance.
It's a version of you that
has you've always known that you have
this beautiful divine path, but you've
literally run off course. And that anger
that you're feeling is for the version
of you that let something false or some
kind of an illusion lead you astray.
You're feeling anger for that. But in
reality, it's just like running through
a maze. Okay, I'm seeing like a video
game of a maze. You don't get mad at
Pac-Man when Pac-Man goes up and goes
left and goes down and then accidentally
runs into a corner that has nowhere else
to go, but you have to turn back around.
You don't get mad at Pac-Man. You just
go, "Oh shit." And then you just twist
and you go back the other way until you
can go eat the other things. And so
that's kind of like how your angels are
guiding you to be like instead of
looking like that abandonment. Um you're
looking at it with like a view of that
was wrong
in reality it was just you exploring and
that's okay.
It may may feel like you could have
gotten things sooner like love. It may
feel like, oh, if I didn't do that,
maybe I would have hit love sooner. But
in reality, you probably wouldn't have
like you, even if you didn't take that
turn, you would have gone up ahead and
you probably would have still needed the
experience that you had in order to know
that that was a wrong turn. And I feel
like there's a part of you that just um
is almost being like guided right now.
Bang, bang, bang.
I don't know if you guys could hear
that, but someone was banging on
something.
Um, there's a part of you that's being
guided right now, too. Uh, remember that
every turn that you have made has been
an opportunity for soul growth. And
that's beautiful. And that rage, yes,
you can feel it, but also don't direct
it towards yourself.
Remember that you learned a turn was a
dead end. And that's knowledge. That's
education. That's power for you because
now you know not to do that again,
right? And even if you do accidentally
do it again, that's okay. I feel like
you won't, but if you do, it's okay.
You'll be like, "Oh [ __ ] like Pac-Man."
It's just it's fun and you'll you'll get
there. And I know that love has felt
slow for you. I know that it feels like
sometimes love is never actually going
to be real for you, that it's never
actually going to arrive. But through
this message and the energies that I
have felt um it's not possible for it
not to arrive. Like you have too much of
a divine connection to love for it not
to arrive in your lifetime, this
lifetime. And it is going to. But
remember, just take all of your energy
right now to hold yourself, love
yourself, witness the versions of you
that you feel have abandoned you, and
thank them for being a part of you and
for teaching you a lesson, and move on
and say, "I'm going up and right and
left now."
Okay? And your lover is going to
surprise the [ __ ] out of you when they
just come out of absolutely nowhere. And
it's going to be epic. It's going to be
epic, dude.
Okay. I love you so much. And if this
message resonated with you or found you,
I would literally love to know. Send me
a cute little message on Instagram um
about about love and I'll know that you
came from this message. Uh but I love
you guys and I will see you in the next
message.