Gemini, in the next few days, you're
going to be hit with a wave of abundance
that's going to make you very acutely
aware of how good you are at creating
abundance. Um, this is going to be a
physical um material or a practical gain
that's going to be highlighted. It's
going to be money. It's going to be
resources. It's going to be
opportunities. Okay? You're entering a
season where your independence and your
prosperity
are clearly rising. The nine of
pentacles is a card of the visible signs
of progress. It's going to be something
that you can measure. It's going to be
something that you can point to and say
objectively like it's working, you know.
So, enjoy the gain. Enjoy that abundance
as it's flowing in and let it change how
you see yourself. Okay. Now, Gemini,
this is a general reading for the one
one portal. Try to be open and receptive
to whatever may come through during our
time together. I am merely the messenger
and I ask you to connect directly with
each of these cards and use your own
intuition to take you beyond the details
that I provide. Wow, look at that. Look
at all this water energy. Wheel of
Fortune, a little five of swords, sure,
three of wands, 10 of pentacles. Holy
smokes, and the high priestess. There's
your intuition right there. I think
really spirit's saying continue to
follow your intuition because it's
obviously leading you in the right
direction. All right. Now, let's select
our mystery card, bonus card,
confirmation card. This is a random card
from the Smith Weight Tarot. This is the
factor infinite and unknown. We're going
to set it right here with Mr. Dao, the
yin-yang duck right there on top.
We're not going to look at that card
until the very end. It will tie
everything together and it will give us
the confirmation that we need at the end
of the reading. If at any moment during
this message you feel like you might
know what that card is, put your
prediction in the comments right below
the video. Now, what we're going to do
is select our spirit animal card. And
for you,
we have the giraffe spirit and it says
see the big picture. Okay, let me know
in the comments your experiences with
giraffes, if you've ever seen one in
person. Um, and what your what your
intuition tells you about this giraffe.
Okay. Um, about the long the long neck,
right? Being able to see above
everything else and and see the bigger
picture. Yeah. Um, and also I kind of
feel like there's some joke about um
about the time it takes for a giraffe to
swallow something. I don't I don't know
what that joke is, but what popped into
my head is that you're not so quick to
accept everything that that um that you
hear. You know, you don't swallow
anything too quickly. Like you you're
going to be rather cautious. And I think
that's really the high priestess, your
intuition, um guiding you and telling
you not everything is what it seems. Not
everything is um can be taken at face
value, right? So you have this ability
to look kind of between the lines and to
like to look in the shadows of things
and look behind the appearances and
really feel the subtle feelings. Um
especially when it comes to other people
and what they tell you and that sort of
thing. Seeing the big picture, but then
also being able to um to not be
gullible, right? to not swallow
everything too quickly. Um, and to to
use your own kind of higher discernment.
I think this is really really awesome.
Now, as we look around the room now,
again, let me know in the comments what
you're feeling about this giraffe.
We have some good majors here, right?
The High Priestess and the Wheel of
Fortune. Got some fire. We certainly
have water, water, water. Um, little bit
of air makes sense. And we have our our
earth cards here and here and here which
are also really extraordinary. Not
really a challenging card in the bunch,
right? Except for the five of swords,
but obviously this is not that bad. Um
there are way worse cards to get. I
think that the five of swords here is
saying that like you're skeptical that
you you'll see a nine of pentacles and
you'll see like you'll see the the line
going up and to the right, right? You'll
see the visible signs of progress, but
you're still thinking, I'm not going to
get carried away.
You know, I'm not going to um I'm not
going to rush to the bank yet. I'm just
going to keep my eye on it. I'm not
going to overreact. You know, you're not
like a you're not doubting everything.
You're not suspicious of everything,
but you you know, you're cautious and
you're a little bit skeptical. And I
think that is absolutely perfect right
here. This is the right amount of swords
cards to have in a reading. In any
reading, we got your intuition and you
got your logical mind that's saying,
"Okay, you know what? We're going to
work together and we're going to figure
out exactly how to keep this thing going
and make sure that what we are
experiencing is real and and all this
kind of stuff." I think also the five of
swords is saying that you've you've
sometimes doubted your own abilities,
right? Because the nine of pentacles to
me is telling you that
you can create abundance, that you can
create stability in your life. And like
I said at the beginning, enjoy the enjoy
the gain, enjoy the harvest, enjoy the
abundance, but also let it change how
you see yourself.
Okay? And now that we have the five of
swords, that statement makes a little
bit more sense to me. Um, you know,
since it just kind of popped into my
head. Now it makes sense because it's
like you you didn't always see yourself
as someone that that could create
abundance, you know, or or that like you
always you always knew that you were
strong. You always knew that you were
capable, but I wonder if there was a
period of doubt about whether it would
actually work or you know whether it
would um whether it would it would bear
any fruit. Okay. But this is something
that is really truly strengthening your
independence. And I think it's probably
financial. It could be something to do
with property or an estate or or
something uh in terms of legacy or
generational wealth. But I feel like
there's a real real independence here.
Enjoy the comfort that you're that
you're going to be experiencing,
especially that nine. Ooh, the nine of
cups. The nine of cups is happiness. Um,
it's not just financial
increase, but it's an increase of the
quality of your life. Okay, the nine,
the nines are the increase cards.
Now, pardon me if I hit the cough button
a few times during the reading today.
Okay. All right. So, uh, the nine of,
uh, cups is the increase of the quality
of life. So, your life is going to be
visibly better. Like, okay, your bank
account's going up. Okay, sure. Your
there's more money in your in your
wallet. Okay, good.
But there's also more joy in your heart.
There's also uh more of a of an
abundance in your spirit. You know, like
the quality of your life is increasing.
Um you're you're uh you're eliminating
suffering for yourself and others,
right? And and so there's this physical
increase, but then also this kind of
spiritual or emotional increase or
fulfillment and this kind of
satisfaction or just like the um
the uh the bliss, you know. Um it's uh
to me it feels like a deeper
a deeper kind of love and a deeper kind
of uh appreciation
for yourself and for the people around
you. It's almost a contentment,
you know.
I think that what it is, it's it's kind
of like your wishes are coming true.
[snorts] Yeah. They're showing visible
signs of coming true. And I think this
overflows your heart with love. Yeah.
And um it's that joy of like of
realizing that okay, it's it's working
and I can I'm starting to feel like I
can believe in this now. And you know um
it's it's going to feel almost
overwhelmingly good. That's a pretty
good problem to have, isn't it? Um,
share this good mood with other people.
Okay. Share your good fortune with other
people. To me, these two cards together
is an empress life. It's the best life
that's that's taking shape.
So, Gemini, I think the one- one portal
is really going to be a significant
turning point for you where something
goes from being like, well, I don't know
if it's going to work to, oh my gosh,
it's working. And not only is it sort of
working, but oh my gosh, it's working,
working, working. Um, so there's no
guilt over this, right? There's no like
apprehension. It's like you're realizing
that you can feel abundant, that you can
create abundance and stability in your
life and also that you're allowed to
feel emotional stability and emotional
safety.
Happiness is like, you know, is kind of
teaching you that it's a you're you're
allowed to be joyful. You're allowed to
feel good and be happy about the life
that you're creating. Okay. Um happiness
is how the path should feel when it's
working. See the nine of pentacles, what
you're doing is working. You're running
a business. It's working. It's making
money. Okay? It should feel good, you
know. It should feel should feel
extraordinary.
And I think that this is that that kind
of satisfaction. Yeah. Down beneath the
surface with the Ace of Cups though, it
kind of feels like it's not always easy
for you to to let yourself feel feel
those those kinds of uh feelings, right?
And maybe because there's that little
five of swords there that's a little bit
of that doubt or a little bit of that um
I don't know almost like a feeling that
no matter how much you're creating, no
matter how good you're objectively doing
in life, there's always this feeling of
I'm not doing enough or I'm not good
enough or even I don't deserve it. So
all that stuff's got to go right out the
window because you do deserve it because
you've created this. Your efforts, your
virtues, your sacrifices, your
sufferings have have created this
success.
And with the Ace of Cups, this is now
your heart is opening. You're allowing
this love to flow. Okay? This is really
like um you're not
you're not going to feel as if you have
to kind of like quiet down your joy. You
know, I don't want to I don't want
anyone to see me celebrating. you know,
you're going to celebrate out in the
open with all your friends and family,
you know,
but at the same time, you're going to
see the bigger picture. And I think the
bigger picture really is that like all
the success here is something for you to
share. It's really so my gosh, it's so
awesome to have the nine of cups, 10 of
cups, nine of pentacles, 10 of pentacles
because this is like the the bigger
picture here is that uh the nines are
the verbs. This is like the happiness,
the success that keeps on happening, you
know. This is the gain that just keeps
on gaining, the the the profit that
keeps on building up, you know, but the
tens are the bigger picture. The tens
are like, what are you creating with all
of this success and happiness? You're
creating a a happy life. You're creating
a legacy. You're creating generational
wealth. You're creating, you know, a a
stable environment for your family and
friends and loved ones and, you know,
your pets, your plants, your people.
You're creating your best life. And I
think that this is the ideal that you
have for your best life. And this is you
creating it, doing the verb stuff, the
actual actions
that are creating this this ideal form.
Okay?
I think it's not always easy for you to
to receive joy or to receive pleasure or
to to receive even like recognition. So
to me, it feels like this Ace of Cups is
a it's kind of you with your heart open
being very very ready to receive. It's
your time, right? It's your you're due.
You're overdue for some reception, for
some uh harvest, and for some abundance
coming in. Okay? And I think it's
because you're always the one that's
giving out. You're always the one that's
that's providing and putting in the work
and putting in the hours and and making
sacrifices on I'm not going to have the
ice cream today cuz I'm I'm working on
my goals. You know, I think that this is
now like you're realizing that you're
you've got your your cup and uh you're
ready to receive all the blessings. All
the blessings. Yeah. Um the four of
pentacles back here I think is really
nice too cuz this to me feels like
stability.
You know to for one thing it feels like
um you invested a lot in something
and that investment um was a risk. You
had to roll the dice in a way. You had
to take what you had and put it into
something else and hope that it gives
you back more than what you put in or
hope you don't like lose everything, you
know. So whether this was you saying I
believe in my dream, I'm going allin. Or
if this is you saying like, I I believe
in this in this business and I'm going
to I'm going to commit myself to it or
or going to school or I don't know what
it was, right? It could be all sorts of
things. Um this is your willingness to
to put in
um the resources that you had. Okay,
your power. The four of pentacles is
called power. Your power is how you
manage your resources.
Doesn't matter how much or how little
you have. It's how you manage those
resources that really determine where
you're going to go, what you're going to
do in life. You know, time, effort,
energy, money, space, and spirit.
How you manage those resources. And I
think that you you invested them. you
invested yourself into something that
can grow into something bigger. It's
also telling me that you probably come
from very humble backgrounds.
Um that maybe when you grew up you
didn't have a lot. The cupboards weren't
bare, but they weren't overflowing
either. And uh and so I think that it's
you're kind of in almost a a constant
like not a not a poverty mindset, but
it's just like you know how to live
below your means. And so even when even
[clears throat] when you get super rich
in life, um you're still going to for
the most part operate in the the old
way, you know, the more frugal way and
the really the more responsible way. you
know, like your lifestyle isn't going to
creep up um as your as your success
rises in life because you know what it's
like to be um you know what it's like to
be maybe paycheck to paycheck.
Okay. And I think that's given you this
bigger picture thing too because when
you have this I think I feel like it's a
windfall. I feel like it's suddenly I
don't know suddenly something starts
flowing in for you. Yeah. It would be
very easy to just feel like I just got
to spend it now. My job is to just spend
all this wonderful money that's coming
in. But that's not you. You got the
bigger picture. You're saying no, I'm
going to be responsible. You're the sort
of um you're the the caretaker of this
in a way. Yeah. It's your responsibility
to sort of maintain this and to make
sure that there is something left or to
make sure that it keeps growing for, you
know, the future and make sure it lasts
you, you know, into the into your
retirement or into the next generations
of your family or something. And so, um,
it's not just your job to to spend all
of this energy that's coming in, but for
you to preserve it. Yeah. And I and I
think that you grew up in a way that
that kind of taught you the the nec
necessity of that or taught you the
skills needed to do that. Yeah.
Anyway, um the 10 of cups here at the
top, this is all that this is that that
family energy. This is just like it
really is the the overflowing uh life of
just abundance. And I think um
in a way like the the complete absence
of suffering
and that's not going to ever be real,
right? I mean a 10 is kind of like
it's an open-ended card there. There
really is no achieving perfection, but
it really is like peak emotions.
Okay, peak peak emotions. And I think
that um you know you you can let your
cup overflow, but you got to stay
conscious. You can enjoy and indulge in
what your uh the energy that's coming
in, but you're going to keep the bigger
picture in mind.
Okay?
And most of all, I think that this is
you sharing
and appreciating your people, your
family, friends, partners, your pets. Um
watch out for overindulgence,
okay? Don't drown yourself in what you
enjoy.
Yeah, this is something for you to
savor, but also keep the bigger picture
in mind. It's not your job to just spend
everything that's coming in now. Okay?
It's your job to keep this going. It's
your job to continue building. It's your
job to to think of the um think of how
much good you can do with with what's
coming in. Yeah. So, it's not about how
much money you're you're making. It's
about like what you're doing with that
money. And you're doing something for
the future. You're doing something that
is going to um it's going to benefit
people beyond just you. Yeah. And I
think that's um
I think that really shows where your
heart is and where your priorities are.
Now, Wheel of Fortune, moving forward,
spirit is going to continue to put the
right people, places, and things on your
path. Spirit will line you up. Spirit
will set up the pins. You got to knock
them down. Okay? You got to keep
knocking the pins down, and you'll
continue to keep this wheel of fortune
moving in your favor. Okay? Um once the
wheel of fortune starts turning, it can
stop. The thing is, through our actions
and our interactions with the universe,
we can keep this wheel going.
And this is the wheel of profit, the
wheel of prosperity, the wheel of
business, right? The wheel of fortune.
Um, and so spirit will set up the pins
and you got to knock them down. And so
in other words, don't stop doing what
you've been doing.
Okay?
um the practices, the habits, the
techniques, the behaviors, the decisions
um that have got you here. Those are the
ones that are going to take you even
further. So those are the ones that you
got to lock in. Don't stop doing what
you've been doing. Maybe the four of
pentacles too is that idea of like you
have very solid habits.
you have a very good rhythm to your
life. Now, just because you're getting
all this money and all this happiness,
don't let it throw you off your your
habits or your rhythm or your routine.
Now, of course, you can celebrate and
you can, you know, um you can make some
indulgences here and there, but overall
see the big picture and stick to the
routine. Stick to the habit. Okay? Don't
let this this uh this big energy change
the way you do things because it is
exactly the way you've done things that
have has brought those nines here, you
know. And I think that's the message of
the wheel of fortune that we got to keep
that wheel turning. And we do that by
showing up and being
being in our best energy, having our
integrity and our virtue, continuing to
do hard things, continuing to have the
the sort of vision and the foresight and
the insight um to, you know, to know how
to engage because like I said, spirit's
going to put the right people, places,
and things on your path when and where
you need them. It's up to you to know
how to interact with those things. You
got to be at the right place at the
right time and you got to make the right
decisions. You know, spirit can only set
up the pins. You got to knock them down.
All right. Now, that five of swords, uh,
like I said, this could be a little bit
of doubt. This could be a little bit of
like kind of disbelieving that this is
real, you know, and I think it's
important that you acknowledge out loud
you are capable of this. You know what I
we should do is a well let's do an
oracle of manifestation
because see sometimes the five of swords
is a little bit of this fear that um you
know it's it's uh it's a mistake you
know we're getting all this abundance
all this energy but then there's just
like no it can't be for me cuz I'm I've
never had this before this can't be real
you know and when we have those kinds of
negative thoughts then we end up making
poor decisions and then of course these
things can leave. So, here's an oracle
of manifestation for you. We have inner
peace. Cultivate inner calm through
meditation or mindful practices. I let
go and have faith. Exactly. Right.
Because what do I say about the five?
Anytime we get a five, we start looking
around for the four. What's the four of
swords?
Meditation, breath work, mindfulness
practices that will cultivate an inner
calm. This is a card of kind of like
stress or doubt or like um you know some
self-defeating thoughts kind of thing,
right? Our our inner tone is not all
that kind sometimes. Yeah. Um [snorts]
and uh I think that what this is is is
literally saying like just calm calm
your mind down. choose to let go and
choose to have faith and choose to
believe
that you've done this, that you've
created this and you are capable of
this. Well, that's what the high
priestess is asking you to to have
faith, hope, and trust. She's saying,
"Take my hand and follow me and we will
go to Big Rock Candy Mountain."
Okay, but you're saying, "I don't know
if this is really for me or you know,
there's this kind of internal turmoil
here. What we need to do is the the the
inner calm. Cultivate that, right? The
inner calm is the intercom with spirit.
[snorts] Yeah. So, meditation,
mindfulness practices, let go and have
faith. Put that in the comments. Say, I
let go and have faith because that's
what's going to continue to push this
forward for you. Okay. Um trusting in
your intuition, taking the hand of
spirit, and letting that high priestess
guide you. Okay. The three of wands here
is um is a card of virtue and it's in
the position of your environment and
your relationships. I feel like there
may be a very challenging decision
you're going to have to make very soon
about a a person in your life. Um, and
it may be that it's going to have to be
like a goodbye or even like
even like maybe like a reprimand like I
don't know if if you work with somebody
that you're that you have a personal
relationship with um or that you kind of
got to be a little bit blunt with
somebody,
okay? Maybe it's a friend, maybe it's a
family member where um you can't just
kind of let things keep going the way
they've been going. that you need to
kind of uh step up and and say things
directly, not in a cruel way, but I
think um I don't I don't necessarily
think it's a goodbye, but I do think
it's it's kind of um uh it has to be
very direct.
Okay? And it's going to change the
nature of the relationship a little bit.
But I think that it's it's important
that you you start early with
maintaining the boundaries and the
expectations for yourself and for other
people because especially when you start
getting all this success coming in and
this big wave of abundance that's coming
in, there going to be a lot of people
coming out of the woodwork, okay, that
are going to think they know you or
they're going to think that you owe
them. So, I feel like this is really
about you protecting your boundaries and
enforcing your boundaries, but also
being willing to um being willing to do
the difficult things because you believe
that they are the right things. Yeah.
And you know, doing the right thing is
not always the most difficult thing.
um the you know the
um
the high road is not always the most
difficult road but I think sometimes um
you know sometimes it's going to seem
like you are being kind of harsh but
that's
kind of in the eye of the beholder right
um when you have to enforce a boundary
with somebody
that person's probably going to get
pissed
Okay, if that's somebody with whom you
need to enforce a boundary, then that's
probably somebody that's going to get
mad about it. Okay, that does that's no
reflection on you. I think as long as
you can honestly say that you are kind
and respectful, but also firm. Um,
do what you need to do because you're
you're protecting something here. It's
not just about you protecting yourself.
you're protecting um a a business, a
company, a legacy, an an estate or
something. You know what I mean? It's a
bigger it's a bigger picture that you're
that you're protecting. It's not just
you and your personal interests. Uh the
10 of Pentacles here is that legacy. It
is um generational wealth. It's the
long-term plans and the long-term goals.
What is the bigger picture here for you?
Um, I think that's something that you
probably already know like what that is.
But the card is in this position of kind
of the the jail, the prison. Um,
[snorts] it's the card that's kind of
locked up right now. And the reason is,
I think, because prior to to this energy
coming in, maybe you didn't quite
believe that the future that you aspired
to was actually possible.
Something's happening in the next few
days that's going to unlock this future.
And it's going to show you
visible signs of progress that this
future is real.
Okay? It's unlocking it from that that
prison of doubt.
Okay? You're going to fully believe and
I think you you have to already believe
that this future is real.
Okay? And the high priestess,
you know, the high priestess is that
faith, that hope, and that trust uh is
the guiding force. And so the the cards
really are saying that the way forward
for you, okay, the long-term trajectory,
your bigger arc here is all about you
trusting yourself. And maybe the five of
swords is is kind of saying that in the
past, you haven't always trusted your
decisions or you've doubted yourself.
You know, you've you've uh taken an
action and then you kind of, you know,
you secondguess it later on and stuff. I
think the high priestess is saying you
need to learn to trust yourself cuz you
know what you're doing and you know how
to navigate this life and you know how
to make good decisions. So make the good
decisions and don't second guessess
yourself. Listen inward, okay? Is your
soul is whispering to you and I think
that your your intuition is um is
guiding you every second. Okay. Um, I
also feel that there is like there
this has to do with that that person.
Again, I think in a in a few days, very
soon, there's going to be a change in
the nature of a relationship in your
life. And I think that you probably
already know who I'm talking about
because this is like you've already
started to sense something about
someone.
And I think that you're going to have to
set a boundary or put your foot down
somewhere very soon. Okay. Uh this is
also a card that is saying you don't
have to share everything with everybody
that you need to again with that giraffe
and the really long neck. Um take your
time when you when you swallow
something, you know, don't don't just uh
um don't be too gullible that you're
just accepting and believing everything
everybody tells you. Uh so be a little
bit skeptical. Okay? Trust in your own
intuition. you got a bad vibe about
something, you know, give yourself some
some uh room, some meditation, right? Uh
for clarity before you just kind of um
swallow it, hookline and sinker as they
say, right? And so I think your
intuition is is guiding you both into
deeper prosperity, but helping you to
avoid the pitfalls and the calamities
along the way. Let's look at the mystery
card. Gemini.
Uh, this is probably going to be some
nasty swords cards. I feel uh if you
have a prediction, put it in the
comments. Let's see.
Oh, no. Okay. The judgment card. Yeah,
this is kind of the similar vibe that I
was thinking with the I was thinking
with the swords cards. Yeah, there's
going to be some kind of a there's going
to be friction with this person. I don't
know who they are, but their vibe is
coming in pretty strong here.
I think that this is you trusting your
own judgment
about this person. And I think if it has
to be goodbye excommunication, then
that's what you're going to do. And
you're not going to let them convince
you or feed you a story.
You're not you're not just going to
swallow that story like it's truth, you
know. Um
they're not just going to feed you a
line. Yeah. Um, [snorts]
so you may have to kind of cut somebody
off or or or um block somebody from your
life, but I think that this is a
judgment that you're making about a
relationship and you have to trust in
your judgment because you are making the
right call. Okay. Uh the judgment card
is also a doorway card and I think that
this is the moment the one- one portal
for you is the moment where your life
shifts where you realize that you're now
on the other side. um you're on the
other side of this this doorway where
your future is is here, you know, uh
that this prosperity is now. Um and it's
to me it's a pivotal moment. It's the
moment where you go from this just being
like I hope it's true or I hope it's
going to work to like wow it's working.
It's more than working. You know, again,
with the visible sign of progress. This
is something that marks a a definite
turning point in your life. All right,
we're going to do an extended reading as
well. If you want to stick around,
there's a link in the corner. There's a
link down below in the video
description. New readings for Gemini on
Mondays and Fridays. Be sure to watch
both readings. Subscribe to the channel
if you haven't yet. Leave a comment and
let me know where in the world you're
watching from. I want you to know that
you are the most important part of Dove
and Serpent Tarot. I thank you and I
love you and we are all in this
together.